[[{"No": 1, "Stem": "Teachers and parents can learn and share ideas for helping to work for more successful outcomes in the ____ from school to adult life.", "Opt_1": "transition", "Opt_2": "symbol", "Opt_3": "survey", "Opt_4": "phenomenon", "Answer": "transition", "Opt_1_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_2_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_3_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_4_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Why do some children seem willing to ____ while others do not?", "Opt_1": "protest", "Opt_2": "cooperate", "Opt_3": "commence", "Opt_4": "acquire", "Answer": "cooperate", "Opt_1_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_2_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_3_def": "to start", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Even more extraordinary, every child ____ one was more than willing to state his or her name to the stranger.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I am hoping that the students will ____ a non-native speaker onto the school council.", "Opt_1": "advise", "Opt_2": "elect", "Opt_3": "attain", "Opt_4": "adjust", "Answer": "elect", "Opt_1_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_2_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_3_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You will need to explain your ____ as clearly as possible and provide appropriate supporting documentation.", "Opt_1": "bulk", "Opt_2": "range", "Opt_3": "situation", "Opt_4": "instinct", "Answer": "situation", "Opt_1_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_2_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_3_def": "circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "natural feeling or reaction"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Please ____ me by email if you need help understanding your assignment.", "Opt_1": "undertake", "Opt_2": "postpone", "Opt_3": "contact", "Opt_4": "advocate", "Answer": "contact", "Opt_1_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_2_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_3_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_4_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Recent research shows bias ____ African American mothers of any class who don't work.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Although the agreement was compulsory rather than voluntary, it led to ____ military reforms along French lines.", "Opt_1": "substantial", "Opt_2": "frequent", "Opt_3": "abnormal", "Opt_4": "visual", "Answer": "substantial", "Opt_1_def": "large", "Opt_2_def": "often", "Opt_3_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "to do with sight and seeing"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "When reporting scores, both the student's ____ and the number of students in the class must be stated.", "Opt_1": "affair", "Opt_2": "status", "Opt_3": "event", "Opt_4": "rank", "Answer": "rank", "Opt_1_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_2_def": "position, standing", "Opt_3_def": "a happening", "Opt_4_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is no need to ____ in detail the contributions of science to that war effort.", "Opt_1": "refute", "Opt_2": "notice", "Opt_3": "allege", "Opt_4": "enumerate", "Answer": "enumerate", "Opt_1_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_2_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to list"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Psychologist Peter Wason discovered that we have ____ difficulty understanding certain sentences that contradict common sense.", "Opt_1": "various", "Opt_2": "enormous", "Opt_3": "mobile", "Opt_4": "voluntary", "Answer": "enormous", "Opt_1_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_2_def": "very big", "Opt_3_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_4_def": "done freely; from personal choice"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The Hershey Corporation, however, already had a ____ to provide chocolate for the troops.", "Opt_1": "fund", "Opt_2": "fee", "Opt_3": "disaster", "Opt_4": "deal", "Answer": "deal", "Opt_1_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_2_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_3_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "From the end of the Great Depression to the mid-1970s economic growth was ____ and its benefits were widely spread throughout the society.", "Opt_1": "flexible", "Opt_2": "technical", "Opt_3": "convenient", "Opt_4": "rapid", "Answer": "rapid", "Opt_1_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_2_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_3_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_4_def": "quick"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "They are planning to ____ a new bridge behind the school.", "Opt_1": "employ", "Opt_2": "recur", "Opt_3": "construct", "Opt_4": "add", "Answer": "construct", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_2_def": "to happen again", "Opt_3_def": "to make", "Opt_4_def": "to include; to give or say extra"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "School need to base their curricula on the needs of the students who ____ them.", "Opt_1": "attend", "Opt_2": "focus", "Opt_3": "illuminate", "Opt_4": "signify", "Answer": "attend", "Opt_1_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_2_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_3_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to be a sign of"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The company was fined a large ____ of money for attempting to violate pollution regulations.", "Opt_1": "sum", "Opt_2": "struggle", "Opt_3": "treatment", "Opt_4": "layer", "Answer": "sum", "Opt_1_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_2_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_3_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_4_def": "level"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Mr. Elliott was at fault for delegating that ____ to a person who lacked the experience to perform the job properly.", "Opt_1": "function", "Opt_2": "prospect", "Opt_3": "rise", "Opt_4": "struggle", "Answer": "function", "Opt_1_def": "job or role", "Opt_2_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_3_def": "to go up", "Opt_4_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The current generation of children is usually thought to be less polite and hard-working than the ____ one.", "Opt_1": "former", "Opt_2": "chief", "Opt_3": "previous", "Opt_4": "smooth", "Answer": "previous", "Opt_1_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "the one before", "Opt_4_def": "easy, unproblematic"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "When does the unborn baby become an ____ separate from its mother?", "Opt_1": "entity", "Opt_2": "conflict", "Opt_3": "evidence", "Opt_4": "target", "Answer": "entity", "Opt_1_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_2_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_3_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_4_def": "aim, goal"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Those who will be attending the ____ should try to make it to the Speedway early to avoid the rush hour traffic.", "Opt_1": "goal", "Opt_2": "event", "Opt_3": "context", "Opt_4": "interval", "Answer": "event", "Opt_1_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_2_def": "a happening", "Opt_3_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_4_def": "a period of time"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You can ____ this book until the end of the school year.", "Opt_1": "explore", "Opt_2": "invent", "Opt_3": "stimulate", "Opt_4": "retain", "Answer": "retain", "Opt_1_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_2_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_3_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_4_def": "to keep"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It's difficult to ____ why he made such a foolish decision.", "Opt_1": "comprehend", "Opt_2": "involve", "Opt_3": "respect", "Opt_4": "revise", "Answer": "comprehend", "Opt_1_def": "to understand", "Opt_2_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_3_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_4_def": "to change (in order to improve)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is surprising what you can ____ if you make an effort.", "Opt_1": "drain", "Opt_2": "facilitate", "Opt_3": "lessen", "Opt_4": "accomplish", "Answer": "accomplish", "Opt_1_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_2_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_3_def": "to reduce", "Opt_4_def": "to do or achieve"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government's priority in his second ____ of office is to reduce child poverty.", "Opt_1": "term", "Opt_2": "sum", "Opt_3": "topic", "Opt_4": "boundary", "Answer": "term", "Opt_1_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_2_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_4_def": "limit, extent"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ German family has 1.8 children.", "Opt_1": "proper", "Opt_2": "deficient", "Opt_3": "average", "Opt_4": "political", "Answer": "average", "Opt_1_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_2_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_3_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_4_def": "to do government and politics"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Many of the students were unable to ____ the relevance of the mathematics they had learned and so could not make use of it.", "Opt_1": "perceive", "Opt_2": "offend", "Opt_3": "stimulate", "Opt_4": "regard", "Answer": "perceive", "Opt_1_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_2_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_3_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_4_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The company's financial performance has been ____ affected by the rising cost of oil.", "Opt_1": "indeed", "Opt_2": "somewhat", "Opt_3": "thus", "Opt_4": "greatly", "Answer": "greatly", "Opt_1_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_2_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_3_def": "so", "Opt_4_def": "very much"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "These ____ and assessment strategies meet the needs of learners who are diverse (e.g., in culture, ethnicity, race, language, special needs).", "Opt_1": "instruction", "Opt_2": "forecast", "Opt_3": "programme", "Opt_4": "contrast", "Answer": "instruction", "Opt_1_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_2_def": "prediction", "Opt_3_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_4_def": "difference"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You will not have to seek permission to publish if the ____ of your work falls under one of the following criteria.", "Opt_1": "manner", "Opt_2": "interpretation", "Opt_3": "diagnosis", "Opt_4": "purpose", "Answer": "purpose", "Opt_1_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_3_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_4_def": "reason, goal"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Recent years have seen significant growth in scholarship on the history of telecommunications and ____ technologies.", "Opt_1": "related", "Opt_2": "immense", "Opt_3": "credible", "Opt_4": "wise", "Answer": "related", "Opt_1_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "believable", "Opt_4_def": "intelligent; sensible"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He was inspired by the dreams and disappointments of those individual schoolteachers who dared to challenge the ____ and follow their own visions toward a better future.", "Opt_1": "hierarchy", "Opt_2": "term", "Opt_3": "minimum", "Opt_4": "extract", "Answer": "hierarchy", "Opt_1_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_2_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_3_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_4_def": "to remove; to take out and use"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Curiously ____ from the report is any mention of the type of action that the State would have taken against the diverse sources of TCE.", "Opt_1": "absent", "Opt_2": "cautious", "Opt_3": "compulsory", "Opt_4": "elaborate", "Answer": "absent", "Opt_1_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_2_def": "careful", "Opt_3_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_4_def": "detailed; complex"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There are ____ students from Korea at Frankfurt International School.", "Opt_1": "dynamic", "Opt_2": "imaginary", "Opt_3": "averse", "Opt_4": "numerous", "Answer": "numerous", "Opt_1_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_2_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_3_def": "against", "Opt_4_def": "very many"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It operated below 60%, was generally poorly designed and ____ not worth considering.", "Opt_1": "generally", "Opt_2": "rather", "Opt_3": "absolutely", "Opt_4": "therefore", "Answer": "therefore", "Opt_1_def": "usually", "Opt_2_def": "instead", "Opt_3_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_4_def": "so, as a result"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Most people have a ____ notion of their financial goals even if they have never written them down.", "Opt_1": "vague", "Opt_2": "chief", "Opt_3": "essential", "Opt_4": "widespread", "Answer": "vague", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "common"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The school received an ____ email with complaints against one of the teachers.", "Opt_1": "infinite", "Opt_2": "instant", "Opt_3": "anonymous", "Opt_4": "royal", "Answer": "anonymous", "Opt_1_def": "without an end", "Opt_2_def": "immediate", "Opt_3_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_4_def": "of kings and queens"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Your ____ is to learn the English words that will help you be successful in your school subjects.", "Opt_1": "custom", "Opt_2": "episode", "Opt_3": "level", "Opt_4": "priority", "Answer": "priority", "Opt_1_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_4_def": "first and most important task"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Costrell also found it disturbing that the administration failed to ____ its responsibility to ensure that the funds were appropriately spent.", "Opt_1": "deduce", "Opt_2": "exert", "Opt_3": "oppose", "Opt_4": "displace", "Answer": "exert", "Opt_1_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to use", "Opt_3_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_4_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "To accurately determine mass balance, stakes were placed in the ____ clean ice areas of the glacier.", "Opt_1": "adjacent", "Opt_2": "appropriate", "Opt_3": "mental", "Opt_4": "rigid", "Answer": "adjacent", "Opt_1_def": "next to", "Opt_2_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_3_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_4_def": "strict, unbending"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Due to its association with the churches and schools, the Samoan language enjoyed high ____ in Tokelau for a long time.", "Opt_1": "prestige", "Opt_2": "level", "Opt_3": "exercise", "Opt_4": "belief", "Answer": "prestige", "Opt_1_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_2_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_3_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_4_def": "what you think; what you believe in"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "However, you may also include a citation at a natural breaking point within the sentence, for ____ before a comma or a conjunction.", "Opt_1": "instance", "Opt_2": "effect", "Opt_3": "state", "Opt_4": "performance", "Answer": "instance", "Opt_1_def": "example", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_4_def": "action or achievement"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Due to a rapid increase in the number of students the school needs to ____ 4 new teachers.", "Opt_1": "complicate", "Opt_2": "appoint", "Opt_3": "suspect", "Opt_4": "evaluate", "Answer": "appoint", "Opt_1_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_3_def": "to believe", "Opt_4_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you want to make an ____ measurement of the weight of very small objects, you will need a special electronic balance.", "Opt_1": "accurate", "Opt_2": "passive", "Opt_3": "necessary", "Opt_4": "mental", "Answer": "accurate", "Opt_1_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_2_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_3_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_4_def": "of the brain or mind"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The course is ____ concerned with the social relations of power that developed along with the major revolutionary currents of the eighteenth century.", "Opt_1": "generally", "Opt_2": "indeed", "Opt_3": "predominantly", "Opt_4": "nevertheless", "Answer": "predominantly", "Opt_1_def": "usually", "Opt_2_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "however (although / despite that)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Many people ____ pictures to the emails they send.", "Opt_1": "assure", "Opt_2": "allege", "Opt_3": "attach", "Opt_4": "refuse", "Answer": "attach", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to put together with", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I experienced her as a very ____ teacher who had empathy for her students.", "Opt_1": "local", "Opt_2": "political", "Opt_3": "competent", "Opt_4": "drastic", "Answer": "competent", "Opt_1_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_2_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_3_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_4_def": "severe; great"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "After listening to the students' assurance, the ____ decided not to block their plan for a sleepover in the school gym.", "Opt_1": "principal", "Opt_2": "global", "Opt_3": "local", "Opt_4": "valuable", "Answer": "principal", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "world", "Opt_3_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_4_def": "worth a lot of money; important"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The different religious groups gradually came to realize that none of them could hope to ____ over all the others.", "Opt_1": "dictate", "Opt_2": "assemble", "Opt_3": "offer", "Opt_4": "prevail", "Answer": "prevail", "Opt_1_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_2_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_3_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed; to overcome"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A ____ to save life has recently been waged at the Kwangtze Hospital in Shanghai. This ____ is not yet over, but it has already caused a great sensation.", "Opt_1": "battle", "Opt_2": "minimum", "Opt_3": "region", "Opt_4": "interpretation", "Answer": "battle", "Opt_1_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_2_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_3_def": "part of a place", "Opt_4_def": "explanation; assessment"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The computer lab is ____ to the library.", "Opt_1": "adjacent", "Opt_2": "moderate", "Opt_3": "instant", "Opt_4": "valid", "Answer": "adjacent", "Opt_1_def": "next to", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_3_def": "immediate", "Opt_4_def": "correct"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It should be ____ that the consumption habits of the wealthy countries are the prime cause of environmental problems.", "Opt_1": "fundamental", "Opt_2": "obvious", "Opt_3": "intense", "Opt_4": "averse", "Answer": "obvious", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_3_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_4_def": "against"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Recent research has investigated the traits that may ____ the development of drug addiction.", "Opt_1": "assume", "Opt_2": "underlie", "Opt_3": "separate", "Opt_4": "assert", "Answer": "underlie", "Opt_1_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_2_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_3_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_4_def": "to claim, to say strongly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "What do western Louisville and the Appalachian region have in common ____ being two of the poorest areas in Kentucky?", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is feared that disagreement about what to do in Iraq will damage the ____ between the USA and the UK.", "Opt_1": "aspect", "Opt_2": "relationship", "Opt_3": "shift", "Opt_4": "shortage", "Answer": "relationship", "Opt_1_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_2_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_3_def": "change", "Opt_4_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Despite the overall satisfaction that the program was ____ successful, there are several ways in which the program could have been improved.", "Opt_1": "perhaps", "Opt_2": "predominantly", "Opt_3": "nevertheless", "Opt_4": "conversely", "Answer": "predominantly", "Opt_1_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_4_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Our aim was to determine whether the association between HPV infection and cervical cancer is ____ worldwide.", "Opt_1": "consistent", "Opt_2": "local", "Opt_3": "discrete", "Opt_4": "current", "Answer": "consistent", "Opt_1_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_2_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_3_def": "separate", "Opt_4_def": "happening now"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Good teachers must ____ their students as they find them, as they present themselves, walking in the door.", "Opt_1": "declare", "Opt_2": "attempt", "Opt_3": "engage", "Opt_4": "assert", "Answer": "engage", "Opt_1_def": "to state", "Opt_2_def": "to try", "Opt_3_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_4_def": "to claim, to say strongly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A close study of this volume will ____ any reader.", "Opt_1": "deny", "Opt_2": "reward", "Opt_3": "select", "Opt_4": "criticize", "Answer": "reward", "Opt_1_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_2_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "to choose", "Opt_4_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Give me a ____ explanation of how the accident happened.", "Opt_1": "global", "Opt_2": "positive", "Opt_3": "essential", "Opt_4": "brief", "Answer": "brief", "Opt_1_def": "world", "Opt_2_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "short"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Doing so will probably provoke a strong negative ____ from the group's normal readership.", "Opt_1": "gain", "Opt_2": "response", "Opt_3": "design", "Opt_4": "exhibit", "Answer": "response", "Opt_1_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_2_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_3_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_4_def": "to show"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is typical to do market ____ before bringing out a new product.", "Opt_1": "aspect", "Opt_2": "access", "Opt_3": "research", "Opt_4": "prospect", "Answer": "research", "Opt_1_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_2_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_3_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_4_def": "chance, likelihood"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Some institutions did not ____ these issues because they predicted them and dealt with them in advance.", "Opt_1": "encounter", "Opt_2": "discern", "Opt_3": "manage", "Opt_4": "preserve", "Answer": "encounter", "Opt_1_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_2_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_3_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_4_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon."}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There is a very clear ____ in the school for expelling students who do not follow the rules.", "Opt_1": "aim", "Opt_2": "mechanism", "Opt_3": "profession", "Opt_4": "pattern", "Answer": "mechanism", "Opt_1_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_2_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_3_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_4_def": "clear and consistent behaviour"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There is land ____ the ice in Antarctica, but water ____ it at the North Pole.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ was that starving the brain of sugar would kill marginally functioning brain cells, but the therapy was soon phased out because it was considered too dangerous.", "Opt_1": "boundary", "Opt_2": "criterion", "Opt_3": "theory", "Opt_4": "attack", "Answer": "theory", "Opt_1_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_2_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_4_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government shows little ____ into the reasons why so many young people become addicted to drugs and alcohol.", "Opt_1": "attitude", "Opt_2": "section", "Opt_3": "insight", "Opt_4": "atmosphere", "Answer": "insight", "Opt_1_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_2_def": "part", "Opt_3_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_4_def": "mood among people or groups"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He said that he did not want to ____ the issue until the committee meeting.", "Opt_1": "enter", "Opt_2": "represent", "Opt_3": "discuss", "Opt_4": "oppose", "Answer": "discuss", "Opt_1_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_3_def": "to talk about", "Opt_4_def": "to be against or fight against something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A new class of antibiotic drugs is not expected to ____ in the immediate future.", "Opt_1": "annotate", "Opt_2": "evolve", "Opt_3": "appear", "Opt_4": "signify", "Answer": "appear", "Opt_1_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_3_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to be a sign of"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Stephen Krashen, a distinguished scholar and leading ____ in the field of language acquisition, held an open forum to present his findings on five topics.", "Opt_1": "symptom", "Opt_2": "expert", "Opt_3": "license", "Opt_4": "individual", "Answer": "expert", "Opt_1_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_2_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_3_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_4_def": "one person"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government did not ____ with the recommendations regarding the disability program and decided to review changes to the program.", "Opt_1": "proceed", "Opt_2": "donate", "Opt_3": "form", "Opt_4": "reform", "Answer": "proceed", "Opt_1_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_2_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_3_def": "to make (into a shape)", "Opt_4_def": "to change and improve"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The school is constructing a new science ____ beyond the sports field.", "Opt_1": "deduce", "Opt_2": "coordinate", "Opt_3": "appoint", "Opt_4": "block", "Answer": "block", "Opt_1_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_3_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_4_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There was not a big difference in the negative description of Saddam Hussein ____ the three newspapers, and these descriptions did not occupy much space.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you come from an EU country and follow a study ____ in the Netherlands, you may be eligible for a grant for these tuition fees.", "Opt_1": "crisis", "Opt_2": "manner", "Opt_3": "supply", "Opt_4": "programme", "Answer": "programme", "Opt_1_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_2_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "provision, store", "Opt_4_def": "a course of lessons; a project"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Kaiya reminds him that they have never been apart before, and it is ____ that Willow is experiencing feelings of guilt.", "Opt_1": "minor", "Opt_2": "apparent", "Opt_3": "abstract", "Opt_4": "numerous", "Answer": "apparent", "Opt_1_def": "small, not important", "Opt_2_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_3_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_4_def": "very many"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government gave an ____ of its plans to change taxation. The full report will not be ready until next year.", "Opt_1": "behalf", "Opt_2": "outline", "Opt_3": "entity", "Opt_4": "policy", "Answer": "outline", "Opt_1_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_2_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_3_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_4_def": "formal rules"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Individual academies apply the curriculum in the manner that best fits local ____ and opportunities.", "Opt_1": "victory", "Opt_2": "function", "Opt_3": "treatment", "Opt_4": "facilities", "Answer": "facilities", "Opt_1_def": "win", "Opt_2_def": "job or role", "Opt_3_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_4_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In history class this year, we will ____ the French and Russian revolutions.", "Opt_1": "apply", "Opt_2": "pursue", "Opt_3": "disturb", "Opt_4": "cover", "Answer": "cover", "Opt_1_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_2_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_4_def": "to do; to complete"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ collection is complete and available for online access.", "Opt_1": "basic", "Opt_2": "public", "Opt_3": "entire", "Opt_4": "formal", "Answer": "entire", "Opt_1_def": "first or easy", "Opt_2_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_3_def": "whole, all", "Opt_4_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Hopkins argues that the district court committed three ____ errors in determining his sentence.", "Opt_1": "discrete", "Opt_2": "aware", "Opt_3": "basic", "Opt_4": "averse", "Answer": "discrete", "Opt_1_def": "separate", "Opt_2_def": "knowing", "Opt_3_def": "first or easy", "Opt_4_def": "against"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The information that you receive in today's lesson will enable you to ____ your project on nuclear energy.", "Opt_1": "complete", "Opt_2": "rapid", "Opt_3": "brief", "Opt_4": "deliberate", "Answer": "complete", "Opt_1_def": "full or finished", "Opt_2_def": "quick", "Opt_3_def": "short", "Opt_4_def": "intentional, not by accident"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The soldier shot the dog for no ____ reason.", "Opt_1": "relevant", "Opt_2": "compatible", "Opt_3": "apparent", "Opt_4": "supplementary", "Answer": "apparent", "Opt_1_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_2_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_3_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_4_def": "extra; additional"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Students and non-students alike can be criminally charged if they don't ____ with police orders to disperse from riot or crowd situations.", "Opt_1": "elect", "Opt_2": "absorb", "Opt_3": "invent", "Opt_4": "comply", "Answer": "comply", "Opt_1_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_3_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_4_def": "to do what someone asks or orders"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If your ____ is not relevant at all to the subject line, start a new thread with a fresh subject line.", "Opt_1": "image", "Opt_2": "potential", "Opt_3": "opinion", "Opt_4": "reply", "Answer": "reply", "Opt_1_def": "picture", "Opt_2_def": "good possibility", "Opt_3_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "an answer"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is extremely important that you establish a strong ____ to return to your country after you complete your studies.", "Opt_1": "course", "Opt_2": "challenge", "Opt_3": "motive", "Opt_4": "outcome", "Answer": "motive", "Opt_1_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_2_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_3_def": "reason", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I MUST see the headmaster at once! It's ____ !", "Opt_1": "uniform", "Opt_2": "visual", "Opt_3": "urgent", "Opt_4": "economic", "Answer": "urgent", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_2_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_3_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_4_def": "financial; to do with money"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Cor-----nd: The dashes ____ to the number of letters missing from the word.", "Opt_1": "culminate", "Opt_2": "exploit", "Opt_3": "communicate", "Opt_4": "correspond", "Answer": "correspond", "Opt_1_def": "to end", "Opt_2_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_3_def": "to convey information", "Opt_4_def": "to be related to"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In 1986, 23 percent of parents said obedience was the most important ____ they expected from their children.", "Opt_1": "outline", "Opt_2": "penalty", "Opt_3": "trait", "Opt_4": "institution", "Answer": "trait", "Opt_1_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_2_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_4_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The University will ____ the cost of the premiums for graduate students during the coming academic year.", "Opt_1": "subsidize", "Opt_2": "employ", "Opt_3": "appoint", "Opt_4": "convince", "Answer": "subsidize", "Opt_1_def": "to support financially", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_3_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_4_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The police chief gave a very different ____ of the incident than the TV reporter the previous day.", "Opt_1": "rate", "Opt_2": "version", "Opt_3": "episode", "Opt_4": "liberty", "Answer": "version", "Opt_1_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_2_def": "form", "Opt_3_def": "period of time", "Opt_4_def": "freedom"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In the third example, we see a wind field which changes direction from north to south but has a constant ____ at all heights.", "Opt_1": "contrary", "Opt_2": "exercise", "Opt_3": "speed", "Opt_4": "apparatus", "Answer": "speed", "Opt_1_def": "opposite", "Opt_2_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_3_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_4_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ability to communicate accurately and effectively is a ____ component of the curriculum.", "Opt_1": "vital", "Opt_2": "obvious", "Opt_3": "obsolete", "Opt_4": "immense", "Answer": "vital", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_3_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It's always better to be overly ____ and to protect yourself by asking for a written contract.", "Opt_1": "cautious", "Opt_2": "identical", "Opt_3": "apart", "Opt_4": "commercial", "Answer": "cautious", "Opt_1_def": "careful", "Opt_2_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_3_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_4_def": "to do with business"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "While a considerable degree of agreement was attained, a ____ approach to food policy could not be reached.", "Opt_1": "familiar", "Opt_2": "intrinsic", "Opt_3": "inevitable", "Opt_4": "uniform", "Answer": "uniform", "Opt_1_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_2_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_3_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Younger students usually have no ____ in what they study.", "Opt_1": "reluctance", "Opt_2": "choice", "Opt_3": "code", "Opt_4": "factor", "Answer": "choice", "Opt_1_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_2_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_3_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_4_def": "an aspect to be considered"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This position is the ____ chance to learn about the many different areas of marketing and business operations in a hands-on environment.", "Opt_1": "secure", "Opt_2": "ultimate", "Opt_3": "mental", "Opt_4": "infinite", "Answer": "ultimate", "Opt_1_def": "safe", "Opt_2_def": "final or most important", "Opt_3_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_4_def": "without an end"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "These notes are intended as a brief introduction to some of the ____ ideas and methods of calculus.", "Opt_1": "domestic", "Opt_2": "main", "Opt_3": "basic", "Opt_4": "legal", "Answer": "main", "Opt_1_def": "home", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "first or easy", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Bright flashing lights ____ headaches in some people.", "Opt_1": "persuade", "Opt_2": "transform", "Opt_3": "induce", "Opt_4": "trigger", "Answer": "trigger", "Opt_1_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_3_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_4_def": "to (cause to) start"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She should be able to ____ to take care of the children on \ufffd\ufffd200.00 per month.", "Opt_1": "manage", "Opt_2": "appear", "Opt_3": "cease", "Opt_4": "examine", "Answer": "manage", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_3_def": "to stop", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Standing on the table is certainly no way to ____ in the cafeteria!", "Opt_1": "reform", "Opt_2": "behave", "Opt_3": "monitor", "Opt_4": "block", "Answer": "behave", "Opt_1_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_2_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_3_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_4_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Honesty is not an attribute that most people ____ with occupations such as politician or used-car salesman.", "Opt_1": "publish", "Opt_2": "assert", "Opt_3": "associate", "Opt_4": "investigate", "Answer": "associate", "Opt_1_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_2_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_4_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We need to ____ access to new lands made possible by road expansion.", "Opt_1": "fade", "Opt_2": "regulate", "Opt_3": "compile", "Opt_4": "exploit", "Answer": "regulate", "Opt_1_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_2_def": "to control", "Opt_3_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_4_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "These drug companies were extremely negligent in that they failed to ____ consumers of the potential dangers associated with the use of their products.", "Opt_1": "exaggerate", "Opt_2": "warn", "Opt_3": "protect", "Opt_4": "tend", "Answer": "warn", "Opt_1_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_2_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_3_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_4_def": "to often behave in a certain way"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There is a serious ____ of workers in the profession of computer science. The government is hoping to attract qualified workers from overseas to fill the vacancies.", "Opt_1": "plenty", "Opt_2": "shortage", "Opt_3": "bias", "Opt_4": "entity", "Answer": "shortage", "Opt_1_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_2_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_3_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_4_def": "thing; body; organization"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "As migration is a spatial choice process, it is important to ____ how migrants perceive space and choose a destination in the space.", "Opt_1": "fear", "Opt_2": "comprehend", "Opt_3": "refute", "Opt_4": "consult", "Answer": "comprehend", "Opt_1_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_2_def": "to understand", "Opt_3_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_4_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Previous experience in such areas, especially microscopy, would be an ____ but is not essential.", "Opt_1": "advantage", "Opt_2": "constraint", "Opt_3": "growth", "Opt_4": "prospect", "Answer": "advantage", "Opt_1_def": "benefit", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_3_def": "development, increase", "Opt_4_def": "chance, likelihood"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Did anyone manage to ____ question 11?", "Opt_1": "oppose", "Opt_2": "negotiate", "Opt_3": "convert", "Opt_4": "solve", "Answer": "solve", "Opt_1_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_2_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_3_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_4_def": "to find an answer"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Most of the school's ____ comes from the school fees paid by the companies who send their employees to work in Germany.", "Opt_1": "revenue", "Opt_2": "experience", "Opt_3": "defeat", "Opt_4": "element", "Answer": "revenue", "Opt_1_def": "money, income", "Opt_2_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_3_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_4_def": "aspect, part"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "German businesses have started to employ an increasing number of older people. They are often better, more ____ workers.", "Opt_1": "invisible", "Opt_2": "rare", "Opt_3": "reliable", "Opt_4": "sound", "Answer": "reliable", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_2_def": "unusual", "Opt_3_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_4_def": "good; strong"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The supply of new doctors is getting low. Some ____ parts of the country will be without medical services if this situation does not change.", "Opt_1": "remote", "Opt_2": "characteristic", "Opt_3": "ordinary", "Opt_4": "practical", "Answer": "remote", "Opt_1_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_2_def": "typical", "Opt_3_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_4_def": "useful; possible"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "They faced problems for which they did not have the ____ or the training.", "Opt_1": "ability", "Opt_2": "condition", "Opt_3": "argument", "Opt_4": "equipment", "Answer": "equipment", "Opt_1_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_2_def": "state", "Opt_3_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ to the school grounds is the stream. You must not cross it.", "Opt_1": "boundary", "Opt_2": "surplus", "Opt_3": "rate", "Opt_4": "procedure", "Answer": "boundary", "Opt_1_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_2_def": "to be, go or make all the way around", "Opt_3_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_4_def": "the way to do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The headmaster was unable to ____ his proposal to lengthen the school day.", "Opt_1": "deduce", "Opt_2": "signify", "Opt_3": "confirm", "Opt_4": "defend", "Answer": "defend", "Opt_1_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_3_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_4_def": "to give reasons for"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "At no point in our deliberations are numbers employed in a way that would trigger an ____ decision to offer or deny admission.", "Opt_1": "automatic", "Opt_2": "precise", "Opt_3": "slight", "Opt_4": "feasible", "Answer": "automatic", "Opt_1_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_2_def": "exact", "Opt_3_def": "small", "Opt_4_def": "possible"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you work hard all lesson, I will ____ you by letting you go to lunch five minutes early.", "Opt_1": "reward", "Opt_2": "replace", "Opt_3": "review", "Opt_4": "own", "Answer": "reward", "Opt_1_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_4_def": "to have or possess"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This situation is certain to improve over the next few years, given the ____ of research now being done on the effectiveness of complementary medicine.", "Opt_1": "survey", "Opt_2": "quantity", "Opt_3": "concern", "Opt_4": "challenge", "Answer": "quantity", "Opt_1_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_4_def": "difficult situation; problem"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "When we ask people to describe their characters when they are at their best, they ____ confident, hopeful, humorous, optimistic, resourceful.", "Opt_1": "assume", "Opt_2": "refuse", "Opt_3": "prohibit", "Opt_4": "mention", "Answer": "mention", "Opt_1_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_3_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_4_def": "to say; state"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Above all, World War II was an episode of American history in which more American people bonded together in a common ____ than ever before or ever since.", "Opt_1": "resident", "Opt_2": "cause", "Opt_3": "summary", "Opt_4": "pressure", "Answer": "cause", "Opt_1_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_2_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_3_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_4_def": "force; influence; stress"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The partners realized that their small fund was not sufficient to ____ early stage start-ups in the environment of the early 2000s.", "Opt_1": "support", "Opt_2": "member", "Opt_3": "privilege", "Opt_4": "materials", "Answer": "support", "Opt_1_def": "help", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_3_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need to do something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government has made ____ any progress towards reducing environmental pollution.", "Opt_1": "hardly", "Opt_2": "furthermore", "Opt_3": "barely", "Opt_4": "fairly", "Answer": "barely", "Opt_1_def": "not very much", "Opt_2_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_4_def": "quite, somewhat"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The controversy resulted from the fact that the Jews agreed to the resolution but the local Arabs refused to ____ the Israeli State.", "Opt_1": "associate", "Opt_2": "acknowledge", "Opt_3": "store", "Opt_4": "refute", "Answer": "acknowledge", "Opt_1_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_2_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_3_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_4_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "How can I restrict ____ to my Web pages?", "Opt_1": "level", "Opt_2": "area", "Opt_3": "access", "Opt_4": "penalty", "Answer": "access", "Opt_1_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_2_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_3_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_4_def": "negative consequence; punishment"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A half century ago the conflict over state regulation of railroads was the ____ issue in Alabama politics.", "Opt_1": "secure", "Opt_2": "principal", "Opt_3": "urgent", "Opt_4": "chief", "Answer": "chief", "Opt_1_def": "safe", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Although Katrina affected the material ____ of Louisiana, it did not diminish the great spirit of the people here.", "Opt_1": "property", "Opt_2": "interval", "Opt_3": "proportion", "Opt_4": "environment", "Answer": "environment", "Opt_1_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_2_def": "a period of time", "Opt_3_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_4_def": "the world around us"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "We recognize that circumstances beyond a family's control may ____ a family's ability to contribute to educational expenses.", "Opt_1": "highlight", "Opt_2": "evolve", "Opt_3": "inhibit", "Opt_4": "predict", "Answer": "inhibit", "Opt_1_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_2_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_3_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_4_def": "to say what will happen in the future"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The Euro has taken on a ____ far greater than its economic substance.", "Opt_1": "guarantee", "Opt_2": "property", "Opt_3": "dimension", "Opt_4": "balance", "Answer": "dimension", "Opt_1_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_2_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_3_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_4_def": "equalness"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Overpraising a person's ____ achievements can be just as discriminatory as undervaluing them.", "Opt_1": "severe", "Opt_2": "smooth", "Opt_3": "constant", "Opt_4": "moderate", "Answer": "moderate", "Opt_1_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_2_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_3_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The good result in the election does not give the government ____ to do whatever it wants.", "Opt_1": "opportunity", "Opt_2": "penalty", "Opt_3": "license", "Opt_4": "image", "Answer": "license", "Opt_1_def": "chance", "Opt_2_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_3_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_4_def": "picture"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This was a ____ attempt at addressing the issue, and not a very scholarly or intellectual attempt.", "Opt_1": "obvious", "Opt_2": "stable", "Opt_3": "spontaneous", "Opt_4": "brief", "Answer": "spontaneous", "Opt_1_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_2_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_3_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_4_def": "short"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The debate over whether North Korea will collapse and whether the United States should ____ its collapse has paralyzed American policymaking.", "Opt_1": "override", "Opt_2": "underlie", "Opt_3": "accelerate", "Opt_4": "promote", "Answer": "promote", "Opt_1_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_2_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_3_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_4_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The Iowa State Theater group will ____ \"The Complete Works of William Shakespeare\" five times during the festival.", "Opt_1": "fare", "Opt_2": "present", "Opt_3": "evolve", "Opt_4": "contradict", "Answer": "present", "Opt_1_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_2_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_3_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_4_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Powerpoint presentations do not always impress, ____ if the actual content is poor.", "Opt_1": "gradually", "Opt_2": "virtually", "Opt_3": "definitely", "Opt_4": "especially", "Answer": "especially", "Opt_1_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_2_def": "almost", "Opt_3_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_4_def": "particularly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The most serious ____ raised against the survey questions the use of self-report scales to assess prejudice.", "Opt_1": "objection", "Opt_2": "issue", "Opt_3": "site", "Opt_4": "desire", "Answer": "objection", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_2_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_3_def": "place", "Opt_4_def": "a want or wish for something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "As a result of the efforts over this last year, SAGE was able to ____ books to more than 30 deserving schools in Illinois.", "Opt_1": "speculate", "Opt_2": "donate", "Opt_3": "attach", "Opt_4": "conduct", "Answer": "donate", "Opt_1_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_2_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_3_def": "to put together with", "Opt_4_def": "to do or perform; to behave"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you don't start working harder, we will ____ your right to leave the school at lunchtime.", "Opt_1": "reverse", "Opt_2": "invent", "Opt_3": "overcome", "Opt_4": "withdraw", "Answer": "withdraw", "Opt_1_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_2_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_3_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_4_def": "to go back or take away"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If you are ____ for Financial Aid in excess of your tuition and fees then you do not owe Ivy Tech Community College money.", "Opt_1": "political", "Opt_2": "permanent", "Opt_3": "eligible", "Opt_4": "automatic", "Answer": "eligible", "Opt_1_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_2_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_3_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_4_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government must not hesitate in taking harsh actions ____ communism and all its supporters.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Many people look back on their years at university as the happiest ____ in their lives.", "Opt_1": "role", "Opt_2": "episode", "Opt_3": "standard", "Opt_4": "manner", "Answer": "episode", "Opt_1_def": "job or function", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "quality", "Opt_4_def": "way of doing something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is not easy to ____ an abstract idea in picture form so that ESL students can understand it.", "Opt_1": "enumerate", "Opt_2": "represent", "Opt_3": "tolerate", "Opt_4": "contain", "Answer": "represent", "Opt_1_def": "to list", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_4_def": "to have in it; to hold inside"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Customers found no ____ in comparison -shopping, since price uniformity was nearly absolute.", "Opt_1": "phase", "Opt_2": "income", "Opt_3": "diagram", "Opt_4": "benefit", "Answer": "benefit", "Opt_1_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_2_def": "money earned", "Opt_3_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_4_def": "advantage"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is only one error in your writing. You put: He play tennis ____ of He plays tennis.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is difficult to judge how much her excellent grade is ____ to hard work and how much to natural talent.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "High school students who have completed this difficult ____ deserve a reward.", "Opt_1": "sufficient", "Opt_2": "novel", "Opt_3": "major", "Opt_4": "obvious", "Answer": "novel", "Opt_1_def": "enough", "Opt_2_def": "new", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "clear, evident"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "For this year's mathematics course, you will need to ____ a good graphics calculator.", "Opt_1": "absorb", "Opt_2": "procure", "Opt_3": "emerge", "Opt_4": "ensure", "Answer": "procure", "Opt_1_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_2_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_3_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_4_def": "to make sure (of)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "How can you tell if the book, article, website, or other ____ you located is a valid, credible source?", "Opt_1": "loss", "Opt_2": "directions", "Opt_3": "truth", "Opt_4": "resource", "Answer": "resource", "Opt_1_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_2_def": "instructions", "Opt_3_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_4_def": "a source of information or material"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Dairy farmers have led the latest in a long series of protests by agricultural associations, ____ the record high prices for farm products.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you saved a file to a library PC running Windows prior to a crash or being logged out, you should be able to ____ it.", "Opt_1": "emerge", "Opt_2": "fear", "Opt_3": "recover", "Opt_4": "criticize", "Answer": "recover", "Opt_1_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_2_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_3_def": "to get back", "Opt_4_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She made it clear many times throughout the work that she did not believe in and did not want to participate in the concept and ____ of marriage.", "Opt_1": "resident", "Opt_2": "schedule", "Opt_3": "institution", "Opt_4": "committee", "Answer": "institution", "Opt_1_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_2_def": "timetable", "Opt_3_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "These questions are meant to help you research the background information you will need to ____ some of the water quality issues in NYC.", "Opt_1": "seek", "Opt_2": "suspect", "Opt_3": "qualify", "Opt_4": "evaluate", "Answer": "evaluate", "Opt_1_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_2_def": "to believe", "Opt_3_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_4_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The contributors ____ that teaching is a gendered occupation with low status and relatively low pay.", "Opt_1": "terminate", "Opt_2": "assert", "Opt_3": "postpone", "Opt_4": "survive", "Answer": "assert", "Opt_1_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_4_def": "to not die"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The difference between Japanese and Korean prices ____ decreased until virtually zero where it has remained over the past few years.", "Opt_1": "overly", "Opt_2": "gradually", "Opt_3": "rather", "Opt_4": "dramatically", "Answer": "gradually", "Opt_1_def": "too", "Opt_2_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_3_def": "instead", "Opt_4_def": "very strongly, significantly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Mobile phones have made it ____ to contact someone anytime and anywhere.", "Opt_1": "probable", "Opt_2": "immediate", "Opt_3": "feasible", "Opt_4": "firm", "Answer": "feasible", "Opt_1_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_2_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_3_def": "possible", "Opt_4_def": "strong, cannot be changed"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "His idea is simply not ____ - no one is going to pay that kind of money.", "Opt_1": "immense", "Opt_2": "stable", "Opt_3": "feasible", "Opt_4": "distinct", "Answer": "feasible", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_3_def": "possible", "Opt_4_def": "clear and strong"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It was not a ____ of which he was particularly proud.", "Opt_1": "profession", "Opt_2": "debt", "Opt_3": "hierarchy", "Opt_4": "deed", "Answer": "deed", "Opt_1_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_2_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_3_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_4_def": "an action"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The most ____ animal class is the insect. Insects come in thousands of shapes and colors.", "Opt_1": "inherent", "Opt_2": "sole", "Opt_3": "diverse", "Opt_4": "ultimate", "Answer": "diverse", "Opt_1_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_2_def": "only", "Opt_3_def": "many and different", "Opt_4_def": "final or most important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The U.S. government likely approached China on this matter prior to the announcement of sanctions, but did not ____ a satisfactory response.", "Opt_1": "transmit", "Opt_2": "receive", "Opt_3": "combine", "Opt_4": "manipulate", "Answer": "receive", "Opt_1_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_4_def": "to (use and) change"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The developing world does not create many industrial wastes; thus it has had little opportunity to develop ____ disposal techniques.", "Opt_1": "proper", "Opt_2": "suitable", "Opt_3": "slight", "Opt_4": "averse", "Answer": "proper", "Opt_1_def": "correct, appropriate", "Opt_2_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "small", "Opt_4_def": "against"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The main reason for not responding to terrorism was not an ____ issue, but an internal one: the government failed to fulfill its duties.", "Opt_1": "ambiguous", "Opt_2": "particular", "Opt_3": "external", "Opt_4": "prime", "Answer": "external", "Opt_1_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_2_def": "specific", "Opt_3_def": "outside", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ addresses teacher attitudes toward the assignment of homework.", "Opt_1": "research", "Opt_2": "category", "Opt_3": "expert", "Opt_4": "figure", "Answer": "research", "Opt_1_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_2_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_3_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_4_def": "number"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "While a considerable degree of agreement was attained, a ____ approach to food policy could not be reached.", "Opt_1": "rare", "Opt_2": "ancient", "Opt_3": "minor", "Opt_4": "uniform", "Answer": "uniform", "Opt_1_def": "unusual", "Opt_2_def": "very old", "Opt_3_def": "small, not important", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She rejects, thereby, traditional feminine ideals of marriage and ____ behavior.", "Opt_1": "homogeneous", "Opt_2": "capable", "Opt_3": "smooth", "Opt_4": "proper", "Answer": "proper", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_2_def": "able", "Opt_3_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_4_def": "correct, appropriate"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You do not need to be an ____ in computers to make a web page or send an email.", "Opt_1": "authority", "Opt_2": "concern", "Opt_3": "expert", "Opt_4": "generation", "Answer": "expert", "Opt_1_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_2_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_3_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_4_def": "group of people all born around the same time"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "By the late 1960's it was ____ that another relocation of the laboratory was going to be necessary.", "Opt_1": "deliberate", "Opt_2": "inherent", "Opt_3": "evident", "Opt_4": "consistent", "Answer": "evident", "Opt_1_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_2_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_3_def": "clear", "Opt_4_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Doctors are ____ encouraged by the reduction in the numbers of young people starting to smoke.", "Opt_1": "overly", "Opt_2": "somewhat", "Opt_3": "especially", "Opt_4": "occasionally", "Answer": "somewhat", "Opt_1_def": "too", "Opt_2_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_3_def": "particularly", "Opt_4_def": "sometimes"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "She is unlikely to rise above the ____ of teacher helper; she is not very hard-working, and too often absent.", "Opt_1": "hypothesis", "Opt_2": "power", "Opt_3": "quantity", "Opt_4": "rank", "Answer": "rank", "Opt_1_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_2_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The points that you ____ should be proportional to the individual's contribution to your team for the quarter to date.", "Opt_1": "encounter", "Opt_2": "control", "Opt_3": "conform", "Opt_4": "allocate", "Answer": "allocate", "Opt_1_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_2_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_4_def": "to give to (to promise to give)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The one ____ in the classroom that belongs to me is the old typewriter.", "Opt_1": "obligation", "Opt_2": "circumstances", "Opt_3": "defeat", "Opt_4": "object", "Answer": "object", "Opt_1_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_2_def": "situation", "Opt_3_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_4_def": "thing"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Doctors ____ make mistakes which can have serious or even fatal consequences for their patients.", "Opt_1": "hardly", "Opt_2": "especially", "Opt_3": "namely", "Opt_4": "occasionally", "Answer": "occasionally", "Opt_1_def": "not very much", "Opt_2_def": "particularly", "Opt_3_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_4_def": "sometimes"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In my ____ the government should undertake more to prevent young people drinking and driving.", "Opt_1": "opinion", "Opt_2": "friction", "Opt_3": "insight", "Opt_4": "layer", "Answer": "opinion", "Opt_1_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_4_def": "level"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Examples of everyday fitness programs include walking during lunch hour, parking farther away from one's place of work, and taking stairs ____ of an elevator.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "With regret, we have had to ____ the upcoming program on \"The Nervous System\" due to an unavoidable change in schedules.", "Opt_1": "attain", "Opt_2": "cancel", "Opt_3": "deviate", "Opt_4": "reflect", "Answer": "cancel", "Opt_1_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_2_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_3_def": "to be different", "Opt_4_def": "to think or consider"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ethnographic reports were clear and did not ____ conflicting information.", "Opt_1": "underlie", "Opt_2": "constitute", "Opt_3": "contain", "Opt_4": "arrange", "Answer": "contain", "Opt_1_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_3_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_4_def": "to plan to happen; to group together"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "All of his projects ____ the idea of flexibility within different, changing environments.", "Opt_1": "maintain", "Opt_2": "associate", "Opt_3": "correspond", "Opt_4": "embody", "Answer": "embody", "Opt_1_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_2_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_3_def": "to be related to", "Opt_4_def": "to be a good example of .."}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The committee needs to ____ of both teachers and parents.", "Opt_1": "arise", "Opt_2": "derive", "Opt_3": "consist", "Opt_4": "presume", "Answer": "consist", "Opt_1_def": "to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_3_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_4_def": "to believe, assume"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Many people believe that the invasion of Iraq was a ____ mistake.", "Opt_1": "related", "Opt_2": "superficial", "Opt_3": "fundamental", "Opt_4": "positive", "Answer": "fundamental", "Opt_1_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_2_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "good; optimistic"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Perhaps the very hot, dry weather we have had for the last 6 weeks will ____ some doubters that global warming is really happening.", "Opt_1": "convince", "Opt_2": "analyze", "Opt_3": "refer", "Opt_4": "assume", "Answer": "convince", "Opt_1_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_2_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_3_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_4_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I need to ____ the importance of meeting the project deadlines.", "Opt_1": "emphasize", "Opt_2": "enhance", "Opt_3": "convey", "Opt_4": "warn", "Answer": "emphasize", "Opt_1_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_2_def": "to make something better", "Opt_3_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_4_def": "to notify (of possible danger)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If we are to ____ in creating a true sense of citizenship in our students, we won't do so by offering an all-purpose, first-year global civics course.", "Opt_1": "spread", "Opt_2": "accept", "Opt_3": "succeed", "Opt_4": "advocate", "Answer": "succeed", "Opt_1_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_2_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_3_def": "to do well", "Opt_4_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "All students whose college/university will be forwarding tuition payments will need to contact the OSA to find out the ____ procedure.", "Opt_1": "fortunate", "Opt_2": "exact", "Opt_3": "abnormal", "Opt_4": "convenient", "Answer": "exact", "Opt_1_def": "lucky", "Opt_2_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_3_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "easy, not causing problems"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Requiring students to leave the school building at lunchtime is not a very popular ____ from the new principal.", "Opt_1": "sum", "Opt_2": "rise", "Opt_3": "innovation", "Opt_4": "layer", "Answer": "innovation", "Opt_1_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_2_def": "to go up", "Opt_3_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_4_def": "level"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government has no right to ____ what a woman should do with her body.", "Opt_1": "utilize", "Opt_2": "dictate", "Opt_3": "reject", "Opt_4": "prove", "Answer": "dictate", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_3_def": "to refuse", "Opt_4_def": "to show to be true"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He reported that the presidential search committee has been formed and thanked some groups for forwarding ____ nominees.", "Opt_1": "passive", "Opt_2": "diverse", "Opt_3": "trivial", "Opt_4": "probable", "Answer": "diverse", "Opt_1_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_2_def": "many and different", "Opt_3_def": "not important", "Opt_4_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers."}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It was a very ____ problem. All the students were able to solve it within 5 minutes.", "Opt_1": "preliminary", "Opt_2": "confident", "Opt_3": "unique", "Opt_4": "elementary", "Answer": "elementary", "Opt_1_def": "first; initial", "Opt_2_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_3_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Mrs. Cassells did not view us as young children in need of constant guidance, but ____ thought we should have the opportunity to make our own decisions.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The police ____ that they are doing all they can to find the missing child.", "Opt_1": "insist", "Opt_2": "combine", "Opt_3": "require", "Opt_4": "solve", "Answer": "insist", "Opt_1_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_2_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_3_def": "to need", "Opt_4_def": "to find an answer"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We reserve the right to ____ alcohol service to anyone who cannot provide proper identification.", "Opt_1": "refuse", "Opt_2": "convince", "Opt_3": "defend", "Opt_4": "harm", "Answer": "refuse", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_2_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_3_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_4_def": "to damage or injure"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Because of their ____ lifestyle, they did not accumulate many objects.", "Opt_1": "widespread", "Opt_2": "common", "Opt_3": "mobile", "Opt_4": "unique", "Answer": "mobile", "Opt_1_def": "common", "Opt_2_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_3_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_4_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government made the ____ decision to kill all cows in the area before the disease could spread.", "Opt_1": "prompt", "Opt_2": "key", "Opt_3": "steady", "Opt_4": "basic", "Answer": "prompt", "Opt_1_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_4_def": "first or easy"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The Court determined, however, that ____ concerning Ms. Lewinsky was not essential to the core issues in this case.", "Opt_1": "domain", "Opt_2": "evidence", "Opt_3": "programme", "Opt_4": "compensation", "Answer": "evidence", "Opt_1_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_3_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_4_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I suspect that difficulties at home ____ her recent poor performance in school.", "Opt_1": "assemble", "Opt_2": "underlie", "Opt_3": "interact", "Opt_4": "exhaust", "Answer": "underlie", "Opt_1_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_2_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_3_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_4_def": "to use up"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In about 5 billion years, the sun will ____ its fuel supply, and will puff up into a bloated star called a red giant.", "Opt_1": "notice", "Opt_2": "convey", "Opt_3": "exhaust", "Opt_4": "transfer", "Answer": "exhaust", "Opt_1_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_2_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_3_def": "to use up", "Opt_4_def": "to move to a different place or job"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you want to ____ what is happening in Afghanistan, it is necessary to go there yourself.", "Opt_1": "comprehend", "Opt_2": "accelerate", "Opt_3": "launch", "Opt_4": "accept", "Answer": "comprehend", "Opt_1_def": "to understand", "Opt_2_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_3_def": "to begin", "Opt_4_def": "to agree (to have)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If you wish to remain at this school, you will have to ____ to its rules.", "Opt_1": "occupy", "Opt_2": "combine", "Opt_3": "respect", "Opt_4": "conform", "Answer": "conform", "Opt_1_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_2_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_3_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_4_def": "to do what is required"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There was a ____ in the cafeteria at lunch today. The oil for cooking French fries ignited and set fire to the wooden ceiling.", "Opt_1": "response", "Opt_2": "crisis", "Opt_3": "event", "Opt_4": "reply", "Answer": "crisis", "Opt_1_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_2_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_3_def": "a happening", "Opt_4_def": "an answer"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Medical science now uses a computer scanning ____ to examine the interior of the human body.", "Opt_1": "mechanism", "Opt_2": "response", "Opt_3": "treatment", "Opt_4": "technique", "Answer": "technique", "Opt_1_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_2_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_3_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The school has a ____ of approximately one teacher for every fifteen students.", "Opt_1": "incentive", "Opt_2": "innovation", "Opt_3": "shortage", "Opt_4": "ratio", "Answer": "ratio", "Opt_1_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_2_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_3_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_4_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Computers are a much more ____ way of storing and retrieving large amounts of data than keeping it on paper in huge cabinets.", "Opt_1": "efficient", "Opt_2": "scarce", "Opt_3": "essential", "Opt_4": "absent", "Answer": "efficient", "Opt_1_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_2_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "being not there; missing"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In a world of infinite problems but finite resources, competition for adequate ____ and funding is substantial.", "Opt_1": "fee", "Opt_2": "attention", "Opt_3": "shortage", "Opt_4": "potential", "Answer": "attention", "Opt_1_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_2_def": "focus", "Opt_3_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_4_def": "good possibility"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The teacher did not completely ____ the students' suggestion, but she first needed to discuss it with the principal.", "Opt_1": "dismiss", "Opt_2": "proceed", "Opt_3": "express", "Opt_4": "install", "Answer": "dismiss", "Opt_1_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_2_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_3_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Most people ____ the airport's plans to finger-print all passengers as an expensive waste of time.", "Opt_1": "view", "Opt_2": "interact", "Opt_3": "allocate", "Opt_4": "inspect", "Answer": "view", "Opt_1_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_2_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_3_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A very effective way to check how the use of an English word is to look in Google for pages that ____ it.", "Opt_1": "receive", "Opt_2": "contain", "Opt_3": "attain", "Opt_4": "warn", "Answer": "contain", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_3_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_4_def": "to notify (of possible danger)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She thinks that the homeless children probably will ____ more poorly, educationally, than the children who come from homes.", "Opt_1": "reinforce", "Opt_2": "discuss", "Opt_3": "consider", "Opt_4": "fare", "Answer": "fare", "Opt_1_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_2_def": "to talk about", "Opt_3_def": "to think", "Opt_4_def": "to do or succeed"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In an effective group, each person can exert ____ influence on the decisions of the group to prevent the group from setting unattainable goals.", "Opt_1": "royal", "Opt_2": "temporary", "Opt_3": "public", "Opt_4": "sufficient", "Answer": "sufficient", "Opt_1_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_2_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_3_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_4_def": "enough"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The demand for oil is likely to increase as people in developing countries such as China and India ____ cars.", "Opt_1": "deny", "Opt_2": "disturb", "Opt_3": "acquire", "Opt_4": "deteriorate", "Answer": "acquire", "Opt_1_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to get worse"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "We had to make sure that our customers in China knew that what we were doing was not an attack on Chinese industry, but a dispute over a ____ issue.", "Opt_1": "classic", "Opt_2": "principal", "Opt_3": "legitimate", "Opt_4": "relevant", "Answer": "legitimate", "Opt_1_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_4_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "She was making a ____ distinction between causing something and making something happen.", "Opt_1": "odd", "Opt_2": "economic", "Opt_3": "subtle", "Opt_4": "apart", "Answer": "subtle", "Opt_1_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "not together, separate"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "His problems are largely due to ____ concentration in class.", "Opt_1": "poor", "Opt_2": "prompt", "Opt_3": "authentic", "Opt_4": "intrinsic", "Answer": "poor", "Opt_1_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_2_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_3_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_4_def": "belonging to; inherent in"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Mathematics course: Students will read aloud ____ problems in class and state the meaning in their own words.", "Opt_1": "arbitrary", "Opt_2": "verbal", "Opt_3": "inherent", "Opt_4": "competent", "Answer": "verbal", "Opt_1_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_2_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_3_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_4_def": "good at something (often a job)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Unlike normal children she cannot attach its ____ meaning to the word \"blue\", so she cannot fully understand basic sentences.", "Opt_1": "appropriate", "Opt_2": "obsolete", "Opt_3": "suitable", "Opt_4": "ordinary", "Answer": "ordinary", "Opt_1_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_2_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_3_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "usual, typical, every day"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I do not ____ about your right to an opinion, but I do ____ about your inability to see the truth when it is explained to you.", "Opt_1": "diminish", "Opt_2": "reward", "Opt_3": "cooperate", "Opt_4": "protest", "Answer": "protest", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_2_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_4_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The department may admit students of superior promise but ____ preparation, provided that such students correct their deficiencies.", "Opt_1": "deficient", "Opt_2": "ideal", "Opt_3": "brief", "Opt_4": "adequate", "Answer": "deficient", "Opt_1_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_2_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_3_def": "short", "Opt_4_def": "good enough; ok"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The problem is that parents start to develop the expectation that we will ____ unlimited services and that's just not feasible.", "Opt_1": "communicate", "Opt_2": "revive", "Opt_3": "exhaust", "Opt_4": "provide", "Answer": "provide", "Opt_1_def": "to convey information", "Opt_2_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_3_def": "to use up", "Opt_4_def": "to give"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The last death occurred on Thursday morning when a deaf man apparently walking to work did not obey a police order to ____ and was shot.", "Opt_1": "recognize", "Opt_2": "halt", "Opt_3": "rotate", "Opt_4": "denote", "Answer": "halt", "Opt_1_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to be a sign of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Does this report ____ to this year or last year?", "Opt_1": "assimilate", "Opt_2": "affect", "Opt_3": "refer", "Opt_4": "hesitate", "Answer": "refer", "Opt_1_def": "to take in", "Opt_2_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_3_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_4_def": "to pause before saying or doing something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Water is very ____ in many parts of North Africa.", "Opt_1": "initial", "Opt_2": "scarce", "Opt_3": "complete", "Opt_4": "adequate", "Answer": "scarce", "Opt_1_def": "starting, first", "Opt_2_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_3_def": "full or finished", "Opt_4_def": "good enough; ok"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We need to put our minds together and decide if we need to ____ among our institutions to provide a new service.", "Opt_1": "depend", "Opt_2": "disrupt", "Opt_3": "collaborate", "Opt_4": "procure", "Answer": "collaborate", "Opt_1_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_3_def": "to work together", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Any student who is at least 13 years old on September 30 is eligible to ____ the mathematics competition.", "Opt_1": "gather", "Opt_2": "enter", "Opt_3": "express", "Opt_4": "enable", "Answer": "enter", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_2_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_3_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to make something or someone able to do something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government has failed to reduce unemployment ____ all its efforts over the last 5 years.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The school cafeteria has made the ____ decision not to offer hamburgers, hot dogs and French fries to the younger students .", "Opt_1": "sane", "Opt_2": "dense", "Opt_3": "precise", "Opt_4": "former", "Answer": "sane", "Opt_1_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_2_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_3_def": "exact", "Opt_4_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The employees are ____ opposed to the management's plans to increase working hours.", "Opt_1": "thus", "Opt_2": "somewhat", "Opt_3": "absolutely", "Opt_4": "namely", "Answer": "absolutely", "Opt_1_def": "so", "Opt_2_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_3_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_4_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government has failed in its primary task, ____ to reduce unemployment.", "Opt_1": "namely", "Opt_2": "simultaneously", "Opt_3": "greatly", "Opt_4": "predominantly", "Answer": "namely", "Opt_1_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_2_def": "at the same time", "Opt_3_def": "very much", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There is very little difference in the quality of learning received by distance education students and ____ students, according to a study.", "Opt_1": "valuable", "Opt_2": "strict", "Opt_3": "sufficient", "Opt_4": "regular", "Answer": "regular", "Opt_1_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_2_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_3_def": "enough", "Opt_4_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There is an obvious ____ to her absences from school: Monday mornings and Friday afternoons!", "Opt_1": "revenue", "Opt_2": "pattern", "Opt_3": "rank", "Opt_4": "range", "Answer": "pattern", "Opt_1_def": "money, income", "Opt_2_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_4_def": "extent, distance between two points"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Your final writing must correlate to your research notes, otherwise you ____ being accused of plagiarism.", "Opt_1": "risk", "Opt_2": "amend", "Opt_3": "retreat", "Opt_4": "convey", "Answer": "risk", "Opt_1_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_2_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_3_def": "to go back", "Opt_4_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "That was a ____ question. Let me ask you any easier one.", "Opt_1": "novel", "Opt_2": "tough", "Opt_3": "contemporary", "Opt_4": "key", "Answer": "tough", "Opt_1_def": "new", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_3_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is not in the best interests of children if their parents are ____ protective of them.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "eventually", "Opt_3": "respectively", "Opt_4": "overly", "Answer": "overly", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "in the end", "Opt_3_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_4_def": "too"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Therefore he was unable to ____ that he was breaking new methodological ground.", "Opt_1": "maintain", "Opt_2": "withdraw", "Opt_3": "add", "Opt_4": "eliminate", "Answer": "maintain", "Opt_1_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_2_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_3_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_4_def": "to dispose of"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She ignored an ____ warning that she would be expelled if she did not start working harder.", "Opt_1": "explicit", "Opt_2": "consistent", "Opt_3": "comprehensive", "Opt_4": "certain", "Answer": "explicit", "Opt_1_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_2_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_3_def": "full, complete", "Opt_4_def": "sure"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Some people say that there should be ____ schools for students who are not so interested in writing or learning from books.", "Opt_1": "poor", "Opt_2": "conscious", "Opt_3": "legitimate", "Opt_4": "technical", "Answer": "technical", "Opt_1_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_2_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_3_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_4_def": "to do with machines or the way things work"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Military power is not an appropriate tool to ____ the Middle East.", "Opt_1": "transform", "Opt_2": "abandon", "Opt_3": "attain", "Opt_4": "stimulate", "Answer": "transform", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_3_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_4_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is no ____ in the master plan to assess whether or not we are doing what we are supposed to do.", "Opt_1": "format", "Opt_2": "justice", "Opt_3": "mechanism", "Opt_4": "responsibility", "Answer": "mechanism", "Opt_1_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_2_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_3_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_4_def": "job, duty to do something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "These grades ____ that the student has attained an acceptable level of competence.", "Opt_1": "prevent", "Opt_2": "denote", "Opt_3": "solve", "Opt_4": "fail", "Answer": "denote", "Opt_1_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_3_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The army sent 2,000 of its soldiers to ____ clothing to the refugees driven out of their homes by fighting.", "Opt_1": "distribute", "Opt_2": "adapt", "Opt_3": "eliminate", "Opt_4": "culminate", "Answer": "distribute", "Opt_1_def": "to give out", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_3_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_4_def": "to end"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "People are more likely to take risks they would not take when sober, and are unable to ____ accurately their ability to drive.", "Opt_1": "attain", "Opt_2": "emphasize", "Opt_3": "judge", "Opt_4": "highlight", "Answer": "judge", "Opt_1_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_2_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to show (the important features of something)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The police could find no ____ of the girl who was kidnapped from her hotel.", "Opt_1": "passage", "Opt_2": "perspective", "Opt_3": "trace", "Opt_4": "tradition", "Answer": "trace", "Opt_1_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_2_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_3_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_4_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The police have arrested a man who they say is a ____ of a terrorist organization.", "Opt_1": "responsibility", "Opt_2": "member", "Opt_3": "influence", "Opt_4": "episode", "Answer": "member", "Opt_1_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The author had failed to ____ his report, so it was impossible to check the truth of his claims.", "Opt_1": "gather", "Opt_2": "subsidize", "Opt_3": "annotate", "Opt_4": "accuse", "Answer": "annotate", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_2_def": "to support financially", "Opt_3_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_4_def": "to blame"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The teacher said that he could not ____ to grade all the papers by the next lesson.", "Opt_1": "guarantee", "Opt_2": "compensation", "Opt_3": "sample", "Opt_4": "career", "Answer": "guarantee", "Opt_1_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_2_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_3_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_4_def": "a long-term job"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "US companies have too often viewed the social sector as a dumping ground for their ____ cash, obsolete equipment, and tired executives.", "Opt_1": "likely", "Opt_2": "official", "Opt_3": "complex", "Opt_4": "spare", "Answer": "spare", "Opt_1_def": "probable", "Opt_2_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_3_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_4_def": "not needed"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ authority in the country is the President.", "Opt_1": "thorough", "Opt_2": "equivalent", "Opt_3": "characteristic", "Opt_4": "ultimate", "Answer": "ultimate", "Opt_1_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_2_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_3_def": "typical", "Opt_4_def": "final or most important"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Sunnis believe that the Prophet Mohammed did not appoint a successor and ____ gave permission to Muslims to elect or choose their own leader after his death.", "Opt_1": "therefore", "Opt_2": "universally", "Opt_3": "somewhat", "Opt_4": "dramatically", "Answer": "therefore", "Opt_1_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_2_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_3_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_4_def": "very strongly, significantly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It's not enough to ____ something; you have to work hard to achieve it.", "Opt_1": "desire", "Opt_2": "means", "Opt_3": "assent", "Opt_4": "income", "Answer": "desire", "Opt_1_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_2_def": "way", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "money earned"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "When the Powhatans did not want to trade with the settlers, Smith used ____ to acquire food.", "Opt_1": "distribute", "Opt_2": "force", "Opt_3": "refute", "Opt_4": "reflect", "Answer": "force", "Opt_1_def": "to give out", "Opt_2_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_3_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_4_def": "to think or consider"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government has set a clear ____ on how much pollution factories are allowed to release into the atmosphere every year.", "Opt_1": "term", "Opt_2": "sample", "Opt_3": "custom", "Opt_4": "limit", "Answer": "limit", "Opt_1_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_2_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_3_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_4_def": "extent, boundary"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government minister expressed regret at her thoughtless ____ about 'lazy incompetent teachers'.", "Opt_1": "insight", "Opt_2": "error", "Opt_3": "comment", "Opt_4": "volume", "Answer": "comment", "Opt_1_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_2_def": "a mistake", "Opt_3_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "To ____ the highest positions in American politics it is necessary to come from a rich family.", "Opt_1": "neglect", "Opt_2": "manufacture", "Opt_3": "induce", "Opt_4": "attain", "Answer": "attain", "Opt_1_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_2_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_3_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_4_def": "to get, achieve"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We believe that individuals who respect and support a ____ global society will prosper as leaders in schools, universities, businesses, and human service.", "Opt_1": "global", "Opt_2": "necessary", "Opt_3": "competent", "Opt_4": "diverse", "Answer": "diverse", "Opt_1_def": "world", "Opt_2_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_3_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_4_def": "many and different"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ____ of social work is based on the values of service, social and economic justice, dignity and worth of the person, importance of human relationships, and integrity and competence in practice.", "Opt_1": "profession", "Opt_2": "deed", "Opt_3": "level", "Opt_4": "scale", "Answer": "profession", "Opt_1_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_2_def": "an action", "Opt_3_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_4_def": "extent"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government cannot ____ to be passive about the numbers of young people who fail to find any kind of employment.", "Opt_1": "afford", "Opt_2": "perceive", "Opt_3": "resist", "Opt_4": "prove", "Answer": "afford", "Opt_1_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_2_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_3_def": "to fight against", "Opt_4_def": "to show to be true"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This is the room where we ____ the science equipment ready for use in the classroom.", "Opt_1": "ban", "Opt_2": "create", "Opt_3": "strain", "Opt_4": "store", "Answer": "store", "Opt_1_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_2_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_3_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_4_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "An analysis of the historical causes of slavery is beyond the ____ of this course.", "Opt_1": "debate", "Opt_2": "description", "Opt_3": "scope", "Opt_4": "evidence", "Answer": "scope", "Opt_1_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_2_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_3_def": "extent, range", "Opt_4_def": "proof, signs"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It was difficult for the two sides in the dispute to find a ____ time to meet.", "Opt_1": "convenient", "Opt_2": "thorough", "Opt_3": "economic", "Opt_4": "diverse", "Answer": "convenient", "Opt_1_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_2_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_3_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_4_def": "many and different"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Her ____ was that the Korean people believe that the U.S. policy is to have a divided Korea and that the U.S. is the reason the two countries are not united.", "Opt_1": "statistic", "Opt_2": "perspective", "Opt_3": "deal", "Opt_4": "ignorance", "Answer": "perspective", "Opt_1_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_2_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "lack of knowledge"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school is not a business. Its goal is not to make a large profit, but to earn enough money to ____ the best possible education.", "Opt_1": "provide", "Opt_2": "avoid", "Opt_3": "mention", "Opt_4": "belong", "Answer": "provide", "Opt_1_def": "to give", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_3_def": "to say; state", "Opt_4_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The course will develop the knowledge base ____ the finance of community education programs.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "While you may not admit to political pressure, you must be aware of its almost ____ presence; and you must recognize it and be prepared to deal with it.", "Opt_1": "fortunate", "Opt_2": "valuable", "Opt_3": "constant", "Opt_4": "compulsory", "Answer": "constant", "Opt_1_def": "lucky", "Opt_2_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_3_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_4_def": "required, must be done"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It's a serious ____ on any community's authority to develop and implement housing policies without consultation.", "Opt_1": "individual", "Opt_2": "summary", "Opt_3": "income", "Opt_4": "attack", "Answer": "attack", "Opt_1_def": "one person", "Opt_2_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_3_def": "money earned", "Opt_4_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The lack of available parking spaces is a significant ____ to faculty and students.", "Opt_1": "custom", "Opt_2": "intention", "Opt_3": "layer", "Opt_4": "detriment", "Answer": "detriment", "Opt_1_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_2_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_3_def": "level", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I ____ to sit next to John any more. He never lets me work.", "Opt_1": "diminish", "Opt_2": "indicate", "Opt_3": "refuse", "Opt_4": "detect", "Answer": "refuse", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_2_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_4_def": "to see, find or notice"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This project will ____ in a major research essay of 2000 words.", "Opt_1": "justify", "Opt_2": "allocate", "Opt_3": "contribute", "Opt_4": "culminate", "Answer": "culminate", "Opt_1_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_3_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_4_def": "to end"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You should ____ your name from the copies of the items you submit.", "Opt_1": "omit", "Opt_2": "exaggerate", "Opt_3": "strain", "Opt_4": "attract", "Answer": "omit", "Opt_1_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_2_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_3_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_4_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you do not ____ the rules of the classroom, you will be sent to the headmaster.", "Opt_1": "depend", "Opt_2": "deduce", "Opt_3": "obey", "Opt_4": "improve", "Answer": "obey", "Opt_1_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_2_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_4_def": "to get better"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The former is preferable for a field of inquiry that is still in its infancy, whereas the latter is ____ for fields that have a developed theory.", "Opt_1": "visual", "Opt_2": "actual", "Opt_3": "suitable", "Opt_4": "prime", "Answer": "suitable", "Opt_1_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_2_def": "real", "Opt_3_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I often find it difficult to ____ my advice so that the ESL beginners in the class can understand me.", "Opt_1": "perceive", "Opt_2": "formulate", "Opt_3": "explore", "Opt_4": "announce", "Answer": "formulate", "Opt_1_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_2_def": "to express", "Opt_3_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_4_def": "to state (often in an official way)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "We do not yet know the implication for the government of the ____ rise in house prices.", "Opt_1": "rapid", "Opt_2": "vital", "Opt_3": "original", "Opt_4": "harsh", "Answer": "rapid", "Opt_1_def": "quick", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_4_def": "hard, unfair"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "My father has a workshop in the garage so I have a lot of ____ knowledge.", "Opt_1": "external", "Opt_2": "medium", "Opt_3": "technical", "Opt_4": "forthcoming", "Answer": "technical", "Opt_1_def": "outside", "Opt_2_def": "in the middle", "Opt_3_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_4_def": "coming soon"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "He was absent yesterday for the third time this month. I ____ he has been having problems with his back again.", "Opt_1": "fulfill", "Opt_2": "presume", "Opt_3": "own", "Opt_4": "modify", "Answer": "presume", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_3_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_4_def": "to change"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Seed cleaning is not an ____ that requires a large amount of labor.", "Opt_1": "trait", "Opt_2": "anomaly", "Opt_3": "fragment", "Opt_4": "operation", "Answer": "operation", "Opt_1_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_2_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_3_def": "part of something", "Opt_4_def": "procedure; happening; process"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You will need to ____ the images and present them as a narrative or the story of destruction in New Orleans after Katrina.", "Opt_1": "advise", "Opt_2": "diminish", "Opt_3": "clarify", "Opt_4": "annotate", "Answer": "annotate", "Opt_1_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_3_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_4_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This is a controversial point that will ____ much debate in the classroom, mainly among graduate students.", "Opt_1": "store", "Opt_2": "generate", "Opt_3": "connect", "Opt_4": "obtain", "Answer": "generate", "Opt_1_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_2_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The priests of this institution did not give their answers by inspiration, but occupied themselves chiefly with the ____ of dreams", "Opt_1": "tool", "Opt_2": "habit", "Opt_3": "policy", "Opt_4": "interpretation", "Answer": "interpretation", "Opt_1_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_3_def": "formal rules", "Opt_4_def": "explanation; assessment"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Newspaper headline: MIT scientists ____ a new way to deliver gene therapy.", "Opt_1": "persuade", "Opt_2": "reserve", "Opt_3": "hesitate", "Opt_4": "devise", "Answer": "devise", "Opt_1_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_2_def": "to keep", "Opt_3_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to create or think up"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Your low grades will ____ you of the chance of taking part in sports trips.", "Opt_1": "produce", "Opt_2": "promote", "Opt_3": "define", "Opt_4": "deprive", "Answer": "deprive", "Opt_1_def": "to make or create", "Opt_2_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_3_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_4_def": "to take away (the opportunity)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some historians still hesitate to ____ the incidents of 1915 as 'genocide ', choosing to use words like 'massacre ' or 'atrocities ' to describe the events instead.", "Opt_1": "control", "Opt_2": "label", "Opt_3": "proceed", "Opt_4": "participate", "Answer": "label", "Opt_1_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_4_def": "to take part"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Research has indicated that the majority of teachers failed to ____ computers in direct classroom instruction.", "Opt_1": "utilize", "Opt_2": "advance", "Opt_3": "regret", "Opt_4": "constitute", "Answer": "utilize", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_3_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_4_def": "to be; to make up"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "One of the most common laments we hear from instructor is that they can't get their students to undertake ____ revisions.", "Opt_1": "arbitrary", "Opt_2": "substantial", "Opt_3": "smooth", "Opt_4": "extraordinary", "Answer": "substantial", "Opt_1_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_2_def": "large", "Opt_3_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_4_def": "very unusual"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Counselors will begin on-going sessions with a student only after having obtained signed assent of the student and signed ____ of the parent.", "Opt_1": "consent", "Opt_2": "correspond", "Opt_3": "control", "Opt_4": "entitle", "Answer": "consent", "Opt_1_def": "to agree", "Opt_2_def": "to be related to", "Opt_3_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to give the right to do something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ____ of the Olympic Games is five overlapping rings.", "Opt_1": "experiment", "Opt_2": "dimension", "Opt_3": "image", "Opt_4": "symbol", "Answer": "symbol", "Opt_1_def": "test", "Opt_2_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_3_def": "picture", "Opt_4_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The existence of such ____ measures was not imaginary; the Commission had already suggested several possibilities.", "Opt_1": "alternative", "Opt_2": "privilege", "Opt_3": "lecture", "Opt_4": "interval", "Answer": "alternative", "Opt_1_def": "other possibility", "Opt_2_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_3_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "a period of time"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The syllabus must ____ how attendance and participation affect, if at all, the student's course grade.", "Opt_1": "collapse", "Opt_2": "assess", "Opt_3": "advance", "Opt_4": "clarify", "Answer": "clarify", "Opt_1_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_2_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_3_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_4_def": "to make something clear, explain"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "These ____ and assessment strategies meet the needs of learners who are diverse (e.g., in culture, ethnicity, race, language, special needs).", "Opt_1": "province", "Opt_2": "instruction", "Opt_3": "principle", "Opt_4": "justice", "Answer": "instruction", "Opt_1_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_3_def": "rule", "Opt_4_def": "fairness in law"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Dairy farmers have led the latest in a long series of protests by agricultural associations, ____ the record high prices for farm products.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Worse yet, 1992 was no anomaly but the culmination of bad trends, most of them directly related to the company's ____ of focus.", "Opt_1": "region", "Opt_2": "condition", "Opt_3": "lack", "Opt_4": "procedure", "Answer": "lack", "Opt_1_def": "part of a place", "Opt_2_def": "state", "Opt_3_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_4_def": "the way to do something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "All campus party noise must ____ by 12:00 Midnight.", "Opt_1": "cease", "Opt_2": "exhaust", "Opt_3": "afford", "Opt_4": "abuse", "Answer": "cease", "Opt_1_def": "to stop", "Opt_2_def": "to use up", "Opt_3_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_4_def": "to treat someone or something badly"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "His research helped establish that identical DNA sequences may behave differently depending on ____ and condition.", "Opt_1": "symbol", "Opt_2": "error", "Opt_3": "context", "Opt_4": "occasion", "Answer": "context", "Opt_1_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_2_def": "a mistake", "Opt_3_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_4_def": "time (opportunity)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The current ____ of our anatomy information system has evolved from several previous systems.", "Opt_1": "quality", "Opt_2": "concern", "Opt_3": "battle", "Opt_4": "version", "Answer": "version", "Opt_1_def": "worth or value", "Opt_2_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_3_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_4_def": "form"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Many parents ____ their children to the bedroom when they behave badly.", "Opt_1": "confine", "Opt_2": "entitle", "Opt_3": "exhaust", "Opt_4": "suppose", "Answer": "confine", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to use up", "Opt_4_def": "to think, imagine"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I gave him clear ____ how to do the experiment, but he obviously wasn't listening.", "Opt_1": "property", "Opt_2": "version", "Opt_3": "directions", "Opt_4": "transition", "Answer": "directions", "Opt_1_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_2_def": "form", "Opt_3_def": "instructions", "Opt_4_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The PBL method is rather time-consuming and requires the teacher to ____ a lot of effort over an extended period of time.", "Opt_1": "allege", "Opt_2": "subsidize", "Opt_3": "invest", "Opt_4": "prosper", "Answer": "invest", "Opt_1_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_2_def": "to support financially", "Opt_3_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_4_def": "to do well; to become rich"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Are you ____ of the fact that you may fail the course?", "Opt_1": "utter", "Opt_2": "conscious", "Opt_3": "sane", "Opt_4": "passive", "Answer": "conscious", "Opt_1_def": "complete, total", "Opt_2_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_3_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_4_def": "not active; unresponsive"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Harvard is probably the most famous education ____ in the USA.", "Opt_1": "license", "Opt_2": "quality", "Opt_3": "atmosphere", "Opt_4": "institution", "Answer": "institution", "Opt_1_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_2_def": "worth or value", "Opt_3_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ problem results from the authors' basic misunderstanding of economics and politics.", "Opt_1": "urgent", "Opt_2": "effective", "Opt_3": "inherent", "Opt_4": "imaginary", "Answer": "imaginary", "Opt_1_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_2_def": "good, working well", "Opt_3_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_4_def": "not real; from the imagination"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The women did not ____ emotionally to the comedy, but the men did, Filipowicz concludes.", "Opt_1": "react", "Opt_2": "indicate", "Opt_3": "persist", "Opt_4": "promote", "Answer": "react", "Opt_1_def": "to respond", "Opt_2_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_4_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Major Smith occupied the city as ordered but was unable to ____ the bridge, lacking both a drill and powder.", "Opt_1": "sustain", "Opt_2": "destroy", "Opt_3": "confine", "Opt_4": "evolve", "Answer": "destroy", "Opt_1_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_2_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_3_def": "to limit", "Opt_4_def": "to develop (into something better)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "For the first time in history, the federal government will ____ college and university admissions.", "Opt_1": "regulate", "Opt_2": "lessen", "Opt_3": "commence", "Opt_4": "conclude", "Answer": "regulate", "Opt_1_def": "to control", "Opt_2_def": "to reduce", "Opt_3_def": "to start", "Opt_4_def": "to finish; to make a judgment"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The police chief gave a very different ____ of the incident than the TV reporter the previous day.", "Opt_1": "supply", "Opt_2": "version", "Opt_3": "assent", "Opt_4": "duration", "Answer": "version", "Opt_1_def": "provision, store", "Opt_2_def": "form", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you change your address or place of study, please ____ your log-in details accordingly.", "Opt_1": "amend", "Opt_2": "illuminate", "Opt_3": "culminate", "Opt_4": "devote", "Answer": "amend", "Opt_1_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_2_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_3_def": "to end", "Opt_4_def": "to give (time) to"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I will ____ my presentation with an example of sea pollution.", "Opt_1": "conclude", "Opt_2": "extend", "Opt_3": "require", "Opt_4": "displace", "Answer": "conclude", "Opt_1_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_2_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_3_def": "to need", "Opt_4_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is not really her ____ that she comes late to school so often. She lives a long way away, and often gets stuck in a traffic jam.", "Opt_1": "structure", "Opt_2": "fault", "Opt_3": "industry", "Opt_4": "finance", "Answer": "fault", "Opt_1_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_3_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_4_def": "to do with money and payment"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is advisable that you put your name on these waiting lists ____ to your arrival.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is not difficult to speculate on what could happen to these laws if the computer really does change our ____ to knowledge.", "Opt_1": "mechanism", "Opt_2": "drawback", "Opt_3": "attitude", "Opt_4": "crisis", "Answer": "attitude", "Opt_1_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_2_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_3_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_4_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This book has much ____ text that will make it difficult for ESL students.", "Opt_1": "dense", "Opt_2": "ultimate", "Opt_3": "radical", "Opt_4": "initial", "Answer": "dense", "Opt_1_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_2_def": "final or most important", "Opt_3_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_4_def": "starting, first"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Since most employers spend less than a minute scanning a resume, it is necessary to be ____ and to highlight all that is important.", "Opt_1": "brief", "Opt_2": "previous", "Opt_3": "certain", "Opt_4": "minor", "Answer": "brief", "Opt_1_def": "short", "Opt_2_def": "the one before", "Opt_3_def": "sure", "Opt_4_def": "small, not important"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Research shows that earnings ____ strongly with IQ levels.", "Opt_1": "conduct", "Opt_2": "construct", "Opt_3": "correlate", "Opt_4": "occupy", "Answer": "correlate", "Opt_1_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_2_def": "to make", "Opt_3_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_4_def": "to up space or time"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ solution to this problem would be for everyone to say sorry and then just forget the whole thing.", "Opt_1": "suitable", "Opt_2": "ideal", "Opt_3": "necessary", "Opt_4": "preliminary", "Answer": "ideal", "Opt_1_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_3_def": "needed; very important", "Opt_4_def": "first; initial"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The Supreme Court held that the free exercise of religion did not entitle an Orthodox Jew to wear a yarmulke when he was on ____ as an officer of law.", "Opt_1": "duty", "Opt_2": "formula", "Opt_3": "credit", "Opt_4": "plenty", "Answer": "duty", "Opt_1_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_4_def": "many, lots of"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The court concluded that schools could not ____ disabled students whose disability causes their disruptive conduct.", "Opt_1": "comprise", "Opt_2": "communicate", "Opt_3": "comprehend", "Opt_4": "expel", "Answer": "expel", "Opt_1_def": "to be made up of; to include", "Opt_2_def": "to convey information", "Opt_3_def": "to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to drive or push out"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ____ family is expected to drive past the school tomorrow morning. The children will be standing by the road waving flags.", "Opt_1": "royal", "Opt_2": "urgent", "Opt_3": "concise", "Opt_4": "positive", "Answer": "royal", "Opt_1_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_2_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_3_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_4_def": "good; optimistic"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This has been the province of scientists and engineers for many years and has only ____ been considered a hot research topic with real business potential.", "Opt_1": "merely", "Opt_2": "recently", "Opt_3": "largely", "Opt_4": "approximately", "Answer": "recently", "Opt_1_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_2_def": "in the near past", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "about; not exactly"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "For republicans since Cicero there can be no liberty without law, and no ____ law or legal system when liberty is disregarded.", "Opt_1": "dynamic", "Opt_2": "subsequent", "Opt_3": "effective", "Opt_4": "valid", "Answer": "valid", "Opt_1_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_2_def": "next, following", "Opt_3_def": "good, working well", "Opt_4_def": "correct"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "These two-word verbs present one other problem, ____ not appearing as separate entries in the dictionary.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He also was able to assist in identifying ____ science curriculum materials for the teachers in the district to review.", "Opt_1": "elaborate", "Opt_2": "principal", "Opt_3": "contemporary", "Opt_4": "outstanding", "Answer": "outstanding", "Opt_1_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_4_def": "excellent"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A lasting peace in Iraq will remain but a ____ hope.", "Opt_1": "faint", "Opt_2": "capable", "Opt_3": "neutral", "Opt_4": "loose", "Answer": "faint", "Opt_1_def": "not strong", "Opt_2_def": "able", "Opt_3_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_4_def": "not firm or finished"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school is planning to bring in an external tax ____ to analyze its finance methods.", "Opt_1": "expert", "Opt_2": "response", "Opt_3": "region", "Opt_4": "constraint", "Answer": "expert", "Opt_1_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_2_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_3_def": "part of a place", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to prevent"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Computer disk drives have been known to suffer from ____ cycle failure, but this is not a concern for broadband modems.", "Opt_1": "insight", "Opt_2": "power", "Opt_3": "concept", "Opt_4": "justice", "Answer": "power", "Opt_1_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_2_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_3_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_4_def": "fairness in law"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Some people ____ poor immigrants - employing them as house cleaners for very low pay.", "Opt_1": "prefer", "Opt_2": "exploit", "Opt_3": "protect", "Opt_4": "identify", "Answer": "exploit", "Opt_1_def": "to like better", "Opt_2_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_3_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_4_def": "to know or say who or what something is"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The school has decided to impose a ____ on smoking anywhere on campus. This also applies to teachers.", "Opt_1": "identify", "Opt_2": "afford", "Opt_3": "depart", "Opt_4": "ban", "Answer": "ban", "Opt_1_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_2_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_3_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to prohibit or forbid"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "ESS is for students who envision getting involved in the social ____ in any capacity: as volunteer consultants, board members, managers, or entrepreneurs.", "Opt_1": "education", "Opt_2": "schedule", "Opt_3": "sector", "Opt_4": "shift", "Answer": "sector", "Opt_1_def": "schooling", "Opt_2_def": "timetable", "Opt_3_def": "part; area", "Opt_4_def": "change"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The continued presence of a huge ____ force in the Gulf area provides the necessary element of pressure to ensure implementation of obligations.", "Opt_1": "remote", "Opt_2": "substantial", "Opt_3": "concise", "Opt_4": "military", "Answer": "military", "Opt_1_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_2_def": "large", "Opt_3_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_4_def": "to do with army"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If you want to travel at half-price on the trains and buses in Frankfurt, you need a ____ identity card with the school stamp.", "Opt_1": "valid", "Opt_2": "crucial", "Opt_3": "spare", "Opt_4": "appropriate", "Answer": "valid", "Opt_1_def": "correct", "Opt_2_def": "extremely important", "Opt_3_def": "not needed", "Opt_4_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The tree responds this way because the tree needs to ____ food again before it starves.", "Opt_1": "resist", "Opt_2": "manufacture", "Opt_3": "join", "Opt_4": "ignore", "Answer": "manufacture", "Opt_1_def": "to fight against", "Opt_2_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_3_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_4_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We can separate white light into its component colors with a prism and use an ____ prism to recombine the light.", "Opt_1": "arbitrary", "Opt_2": "identical", "Opt_3": "mental", "Opt_4": "brief", "Answer": "identical", "Opt_1_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_2_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_3_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_4_def": "short"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This looks like a copy. Can you please give me the ____ sheet.", "Opt_1": "wise", "Opt_2": "original", "Opt_3": "prime", "Opt_4": "widespread", "Answer": "original", "Opt_1_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_2_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "common"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She made it clear many times throughout the work that she did not believe in and did not want to participate in the concept and ____ of marriage.", "Opt_1": "rise", "Opt_2": "institution", "Opt_3": "profit", "Opt_4": "ignorance", "Answer": "institution", "Opt_1_def": "to go up", "Opt_2_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_3_def": "money gained", "Opt_4_def": "lack of knowledge"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "London is becoming more and more unpleasant. The government needs to drastically ____ the penalty for dropping litter.", "Opt_1": "constitute", "Opt_2": "increase", "Opt_3": "deteriorate", "Opt_4": "abandon", "Answer": "increase", "Opt_1_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to leave or give up"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Should the counselor attempt to identify him and ____ him that there is a risk to his future children?", "Opt_1": "deviate", "Opt_2": "inform", "Opt_3": "ignore", "Opt_4": "request", "Answer": "inform", "Opt_1_def": "to be different", "Opt_2_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_3_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_4_def": "to ask politely"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We engage outside ____ to work on particular matters when considerations such as cost and highly specialized subject matter make it appropriate to do so.", "Opt_1": "pattern", "Opt_2": "counsel", "Opt_3": "liberty", "Opt_4": "gain", "Answer": "counsel", "Opt_1_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_3_def": "freedom", "Opt_4_def": "to get; to increase in .."}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The teaching ____ is usually not attractive to those who are still pupils themselves. This choice of career is normally made much later.", "Opt_1": "profession", "Opt_2": "perspective", "Opt_3": "equipment", "Opt_4": "effect", "Answer": "profession", "Opt_1_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_2_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "By studying these financial transactions, it is possible to estimate the ____ of money that people are willing to pay for the essentials.", "Opt_1": "manner", "Opt_2": "supply", "Opt_3": "amount", "Opt_4": "degree", "Answer": "amount", "Opt_1_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "provision, store", "Opt_3_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The scientists that ____ the committee all work in the field of cancer research.", "Opt_1": "enforce", "Opt_2": "intervene", "Opt_3": "constitute", "Opt_4": "inform", "Answer": "constitute", "Opt_1_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_2_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_3_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_4_def": "to say, give information"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Younger students usually have no ____ in what they study.", "Opt_1": "choice", "Opt_2": "truth", "Opt_3": "support", "Opt_4": "technique", "Answer": "choice", "Opt_1_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_2_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_3_def": "help", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "All the forms below can be electronically filled and submitted with the exception of Form B, which must ____ personal copies of material.", "Opt_1": "intervene", "Opt_2": "accompany", "Opt_3": "perceive", "Opt_4": "control", "Answer": "accompany", "Opt_1_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_2_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_3_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_4_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Clinton certainly did not ____ these word games, but in recent years they have risen to a high art form in Washington.", "Opt_1": "investigate", "Opt_2": "inspect", "Opt_3": "invent", "Opt_4": "sustain", "Answer": "invent", "Opt_1_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_2_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_4_def": "to keep going; to maintain"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Our experiments with SRM 1010a led us to the conclusion that this was too subjective a ____ of evaluating results.", "Opt_1": "method", "Opt_2": "interior", "Opt_3": "policy", "Opt_4": "forecast", "Answer": "method", "Opt_1_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "inside", "Opt_3_def": "formal rules", "Opt_4_def": "prediction"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Upon completion of the course, students will be able to discern how grammar and usage errors can ____ with meaning.", "Opt_1": "discover", "Opt_2": "separate", "Opt_3": "destroy", "Opt_4": "interfere", "Answer": "interfere", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_2_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_3_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent; to harm"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "She made it clear many times throughout the work that she did not believe in and did not want to participate in the ____ and institution of marriage.", "Opt_1": "fund", "Opt_2": "concept", "Opt_3": "skill", "Opt_4": "equipment", "Answer": "concept", "Opt_1_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_2_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_3_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Banks that ____ the Equator Principles apply them globally to project financing in all industry sectors including mining, oil and gas, and forestry.", "Opt_1": "damage", "Opt_2": "adopt", "Opt_3": "reward", "Opt_4": "emphasize", "Answer": "adopt", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_3_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "to stress, to say something strongly"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The headmaster's decision is sure to provoke much discussion ____ teachers and students at the school.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You should write this again to ____ all the irrelevant details.", "Opt_1": "extract", "Opt_2": "staff", "Opt_3": "equipment", "Opt_4": "procedure", "Answer": "extract", "Opt_1_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_2_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_4_def": "the way to do something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "As a child, he began to stutter severely and, ____ the best efforts of his teachers and parents, he was unable to overcome it.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In all cases, employers must ____ alternative dates for a second-round interview if the date originally suggested is inconvenient.", "Opt_1": "pursue", "Opt_2": "protest", "Opt_3": "transmit", "Opt_4": "offer", "Answer": "offer", "Opt_1_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_2_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_3_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_4_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ethnographic reports were clear and did not ____ conflicting information.", "Opt_1": "own", "Opt_2": "conceal", "Opt_3": "persist", "Opt_4": "contain", "Answer": "contain", "Opt_1_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_2_def": "to hide", "Opt_3_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_4_def": "to have in it; to hold inside"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "When attempting to ____ a food service for an on-campus event, please be sure to ask the following questions.", "Opt_1": "deserve", "Opt_2": "select", "Opt_3": "prefer", "Opt_4": "hesitate", "Answer": "select", "Opt_1_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_2_def": "to choose", "Opt_3_def": "to like better", "Opt_4_def": "to pause before saying or doing something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Radio and TV stations often ____ for money from their audience in order to help people suffering from disasters.", "Opt_1": "accelerate", "Opt_2": "appeal", "Opt_3": "publish", "Opt_4": "focus", "Answer": "appeal", "Opt_1_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_2_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_3_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_4_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ of young men who walk around with large aggressive dogs is that they are from the working class and are criminals.", "Opt_1": "stereotype", "Opt_2": "theory", "Opt_3": "materials", "Opt_4": "contrast", "Answer": "stereotype", "Opt_1_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_2_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_4_def": "difference"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Illegal immigration is not the ____ reason so many poor young blacks are on the streets and why some turn to gangs, guns and drug dealing.", "Opt_1": "prime", "Opt_2": "vital", "Opt_3": "urgent", "Opt_4": "random", "Answer": "prime", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_4_def": "by chance; without any sequence"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Children in Experiment 2 did not exhibit any ____ of recognizing the familiarized words in the passages.", "Opt_1": "authority", "Opt_2": "minimum", "Opt_3": "task", "Opt_4": "evidence", "Answer": "evidence", "Opt_1_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_2_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_3_def": "job", "Opt_4_def": "proof, signs"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The xenon atoms need to accelerate to a ____ of 30 km/s.", "Opt_1": "speed", "Opt_2": "minimum", "Opt_3": "description", "Opt_4": "skill", "Answer": "speed", "Opt_1_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_2_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_3_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_4_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "People with mental disabilities are so marginalized that even human rights activists have failed to ____ for them.", "Opt_1": "refer", "Opt_2": "revive", "Opt_3": "advocate", "Opt_4": "fear", "Answer": "advocate", "Opt_1_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_2_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_3_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to be concerned or frightened about"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Kaiya reminds him that they have never been ____ before, and it is apparent that Willow is experiencing feelings of guilt.", "Opt_1": "imaginary", "Opt_2": "serious", "Opt_3": "absent", "Opt_4": "apart", "Answer": "apart", "Opt_1_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_2_def": "severe, large", "Opt_3_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_4_def": "not together, separate"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A simple and often effective means to reduce blood pressure is to reduce the ____ of body fluid with a diuretic.", "Opt_1": "volume", "Opt_2": "reluctance", "Opt_3": "friction", "Opt_4": "ability", "Answer": "volume", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_3_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If I make a comparison of England and Germany, I have to say I ____ Germany. The weather is better and the people are more friendly.", "Opt_1": "indicate", "Opt_2": "abuse", "Opt_3": "prefer", "Opt_4": "disturb", "Answer": "prefer", "Opt_1_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_2_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_3_def": "to like better", "Opt_4_def": "to interrupt, stop from working"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The many hours of practice that usually underlie exceptional performance ____ out of sight to the casual observer.", "Opt_1": "remain", "Opt_2": "warn", "Opt_3": "possess", "Opt_4": "attain", "Answer": "remain", "Opt_1_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_2_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_3_def": "to have or own", "Opt_4_def": "to get, achieve"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Therefore, if a calf has not received an adequate ____ of quality colostrum, the calf may not be able to resist disease.", "Opt_1": "phenomenon", "Opt_2": "amount", "Opt_3": "factor", "Opt_4": "magnitude", "Answer": "amount", "Opt_1_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_2_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_4_def": "size; amount"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Many students doing an important test try to ____ their answers with their hand or a book. They don't want their neighbour seeing what they have written.", "Opt_1": "offend", "Opt_2": "conceal", "Opt_3": "signify", "Opt_4": "install", "Answer": "conceal", "Opt_1_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_2_def": "to hide", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This alone makes the book a worthwhile read for students whose received knowledge about Africans is often little more than a ____ of passive victims.", "Opt_1": "stereotype", "Opt_2": "revenue", "Opt_3": "desire", "Opt_4": "supply", "Answer": "stereotype", "Opt_1_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_2_def": "money, income", "Opt_3_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_4_def": "provision, store"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Another significant ____ was provided by the results of the post-hoc test of Recognition Motivation.", "Opt_1": "description", "Opt_2": "limit", "Opt_3": "insight", "Opt_4": "principle", "Answer": "insight", "Opt_1_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_2_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_3_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_4_def": "rule"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If we accept your ____ to amend the information, we will make reasonable efforts to inform others, including people you have authorized, of the amendment.", "Opt_1": "predict", "Opt_2": "promote", "Opt_3": "abandon", "Opt_4": "request", "Answer": "request", "Opt_1_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_2_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_3_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_4_def": "to ask politely"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Many people have to ____ their houses when war breaks out in their country.", "Opt_1": "restore", "Opt_2": "edit", "Opt_3": "comprehend", "Opt_4": "abandon", "Answer": "abandon", "Opt_1_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_2_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to leave or give up"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The new committee just adds another layer to an already complex ____ -making process.", "Opt_1": "quantity", "Opt_2": "volume", "Opt_3": "surplus", "Opt_4": "decision", "Answer": "decision", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "to be, go or make all the way around", "Opt_4_def": "intention to do something, choice"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "My ____ tells me that there is more to her learning problems than the parents are willing to say.", "Opt_1": "instinct", "Opt_2": "proportion", "Opt_3": "outcome", "Opt_4": "habit", "Answer": "instinct", "Opt_1_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_2_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "something you do regularly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The course will develop the knowledge base regarding the ____ of community education programs.", "Opt_1": "growth", "Opt_2": "episode", "Opt_3": "generation", "Opt_4": "finance", "Answer": "finance", "Opt_1_def": "development, increase", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_4_def": "to do with money and payment"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You will need to provide a ____ of recent writing so that your English level can be assessed.", "Opt_1": "sample", "Opt_2": "gain", "Opt_3": "effect", "Opt_4": "symbol", "Answer": "sample", "Opt_1_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_2_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It operated below 60%, was generally poorly designed and therefore not ____ considering.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There is no magic ____ for getting better in English, but lots of reading is an easy and enjoyable way to improve.", "Opt_1": "skill", "Opt_2": "formula", "Opt_3": "progress", "Opt_4": "experience", "Answer": "formula", "Opt_1_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_4_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We did an ____ in science class to see if salt water boils more quickly than fresh water.", "Opt_1": "experiment", "Opt_2": "institution", "Opt_3": "location", "Opt_4": "ability", "Answer": "experiment", "Opt_1_def": "test", "Opt_2_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_3_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_4_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "As migration is a spatial choice process, it is important to ____ how migrants perceive space and choose a destination in the space.", "Opt_1": "comprehend", "Opt_2": "supervise", "Opt_3": "discuss", "Opt_4": "culminate", "Answer": "comprehend", "Opt_1_def": "to understand", "Opt_2_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to talk about", "Opt_4_def": "to end"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There has been no official ____ about the number of soldiers who were killed in the fighting.", "Opt_1": "standard", "Opt_2": "contract", "Opt_3": "attitude", "Opt_4": "statement", "Answer": "statement", "Opt_1_def": "quality", "Opt_2_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_3_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_4_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In a world of infinite problems but finite resources, competition for ____ attention and funding is substantial.", "Opt_1": "moderate", "Opt_2": "adequate", "Opt_3": "crucial", "Opt_4": "capable", "Answer": "adequate", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_2_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_3_def": "extremely important", "Opt_4_def": "able"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Some scientists believe that there is an ____ supply of oil waiting to be discovered at the bottom of deep oceans.", "Opt_1": "abundant", "Opt_2": "invisible", "Opt_3": "military", "Opt_4": "comprehensive", "Answer": "abundant", "Opt_1_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_3_def": "to do with army", "Opt_4_def": "full, complete"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A very ____ way to check how the use of an English word is to look in Google for pages that contain it.", "Opt_1": "effective", "Opt_2": "chief", "Opt_3": "profound", "Opt_4": "obsolete", "Answer": "effective", "Opt_1_def": "good, working well", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_4_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Most employers expect you to attach a photograph when you ____ for a job.", "Opt_1": "distort", "Opt_2": "manage", "Opt_3": "regulate", "Opt_4": "apply", "Answer": "apply", "Opt_1_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to control", "Opt_4_def": "to be relevant (to)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If you want to ____ the chess club, please sign your name on the list below.", "Opt_1": "join", "Opt_2": "establish", "Opt_3": "consume", "Opt_4": "combine", "Answer": "join", "Opt_1_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_2_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_3_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_4_def": "to put or go together"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We believe that individuals who ____ and support a diverse global society will prosper as leaders in schools, universities, businesses, and human service.", "Opt_1": "detect", "Opt_2": "depend", "Opt_3": "respect", "Opt_4": "manipulate", "Answer": "respect", "Opt_1_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_2_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_3_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_4_def": "to (use and) change"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you wish to remain at this school, you will have to ____ to its rules.", "Opt_1": "conform", "Opt_2": "integrate", "Opt_3": "cooperate", "Opt_4": "hesitate", "Answer": "conform", "Opt_1_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_2_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_3_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_4_def": "to pause before saying or doing something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "More than 70 percent of the surveyed firms said that the ____ of housing was not a constraint on their ability to expand.", "Opt_1": "habit", "Opt_2": "lack", "Opt_3": "profit", "Opt_4": "interpretation", "Answer": "lack", "Opt_1_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_2_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_3_def": "money gained", "Opt_4_def": "explanation; assessment"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The tree responds this way because the tree needs to ____ food again before it starves.", "Opt_1": "restore", "Opt_2": "reinforce", "Opt_3": "base", "Opt_4": "manufacture", "Answer": "manufacture", "Opt_1_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_2_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_3_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_4_def": "to produce (with machines)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The university has no obligation to refund the ____ after the second week of the semester.", "Opt_1": "fee", "Opt_2": "duty", "Opt_3": "responsibility", "Opt_4": "substitute", "Answer": "fee", "Opt_1_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_3_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_4_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "What the headlines failed to ____ was that democratic parties captured more than 60 percent of the ballots cast.", "Opt_1": "base", "Opt_2": "specify", "Opt_3": "rotate", "Opt_4": "highlight", "Answer": "highlight", "Opt_1_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_2_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_3_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_4_def": "to show (the important features of something)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ between Russia's dominant military power and our own inferior power could not be bridged overnight.", "Opt_1": "gap", "Opt_2": "custom", "Opt_3": "summary", "Opt_4": "component", "Answer": "gap", "Opt_1_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_2_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_3_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_4_def": "part of; an element of"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "People with eye problems often cannot ____ the colors red and green.", "Opt_1": "define", "Opt_2": "trigger", "Opt_3": "explore", "Opt_4": "differentiate", "Answer": "differentiate", "Opt_1_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_2_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_3_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_4_def": "to make different; to see the difference"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If a person tends to be ____ in relationships or at work, it is likely that her investment decisions will also be ____.", "Opt_1": "homogeneous", "Opt_2": "cautious", "Opt_3": "suitable", "Opt_4": "harsh", "Answer": "cautious", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_2_def": "careful", "Opt_3_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "hard, unfair"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This document explains why it is important to ____ a community assessment during a sustainability project.", "Opt_1": "presume", "Opt_2": "raise", "Opt_3": "conduct", "Opt_4": "define", "Answer": "conduct", "Opt_1_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_2_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_3_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_4_def": "to state what something is or means"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You should use the bathroom ____ to coming to class.", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "His grades have started to ____ since he has missed so much school.", "Opt_1": "decrease", "Opt_2": "force", "Opt_3": "dictate", "Opt_4": "accept", "Answer": "decrease", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_2_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_3_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_4_def": "to agree (to have)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is a truism that death - not just our own - affects all of us, even if it is a ____ most people do not want to contemplate for long.", "Opt_1": "purpose", "Opt_2": "topic", "Opt_3": "quality", "Opt_4": "surplus", "Answer": "topic", "Opt_1_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_3_def": "worth or value", "Opt_4_def": "to be, go or make all the way around"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This is an important finding that has implications for the diagnosis and ____ of children with PTSD.", "Opt_1": "treatment", "Opt_2": "controversy", "Opt_3": "detail", "Opt_4": "rate", "Answer": "treatment", "Opt_1_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_2_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_3_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_4_def": "quantity; proportion; speed"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Historically, there was ____ for crop and livestock losses, but the problem of estimating the damage and lack of funds for ____ programs has been significant.", "Opt_1": "schedule", "Opt_2": "standard", "Opt_3": "treatment", "Opt_4": "compensation", "Answer": "compensation", "Opt_1_def": "timetable", "Opt_2_def": "quality", "Opt_3_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_4_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Clinton certainly did not invent these word games, but in recent years they have risen to a high art ____ in Washington.", "Opt_1": "determine", "Opt_2": "form", "Opt_3": "abuse", "Opt_4": "develop", "Answer": "form", "Opt_1_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_2_def": "to make (into a shape)", "Opt_3_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_4_def": "to grow or improve"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is interesting to think about how teaching will evolve under the ____ of digital technologies.", "Opt_1": "sum", "Opt_2": "coincidence", "Opt_3": "influence", "Opt_4": "bulk", "Answer": "influence", "Opt_1_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_2_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "majority; largest part"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The geographer urges upon his students that they first master those principles and then consider the ____ problems.", "Opt_1": "enormous", "Opt_2": "valid", "Opt_3": "subsequent", "Opt_4": "absent", "Answer": "subsequent", "Opt_1_def": "very big", "Opt_2_def": "correct", "Opt_3_def": "next, following", "Opt_4_def": "being not there; missing"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is an advantage for a politician to be able to give a clear but ____ statement of what he or she believes in.", "Opt_1": "secure", "Opt_2": "apart", "Opt_3": "concise", "Opt_4": "public", "Answer": "concise", "Opt_1_def": "safe", "Opt_2_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_3_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_4_def": "open to all; not private"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This year you cannot choose which science course to do, but when you are in grade 9 you can ____ chemistry, physics or biology.", "Opt_1": "evaluate", "Opt_2": "select", "Opt_3": "protect", "Opt_4": "impress", "Answer": "select", "Opt_1_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "to choose", "Opt_3_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_4_def": "to create a favourable reaction"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We recognize that circumstances ____ a family's control may inhibit a family's ability to contribute to educational expenses.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "One of the most common laments we hear from instructor is that they can't get their students to undertake ____ revisions.", "Opt_1": "substantial", "Opt_2": "fundamental", "Opt_3": "independent", "Opt_4": "external", "Answer": "substantial", "Opt_1_def": "large", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_4_def": "outside"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There seemed to be no ____ of coping with the war debts that were overwhelming both nation and states.", "Opt_1": "prospect", "Opt_2": "pressure", "Opt_3": "impact", "Opt_4": "outline", "Answer": "prospect", "Opt_1_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_2_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "plan or summary"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The police have decided not to ____ the identity of the men arrested for planting the bombs.", "Opt_1": "reveal", "Opt_2": "ban", "Opt_3": "differentiate", "Opt_4": "represent", "Answer": "reveal", "Opt_1_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_2_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_3_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_4_def": "to be; to show or indicate"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If the student is determined to be ____ of their parents, the student must be a resident of Indiana since at least December 31 of the previous year.", "Opt_1": "intrinsic", "Opt_2": "serious", "Opt_3": "several", "Opt_4": "independent", "Answer": "independent", "Opt_1_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_2_def": "severe, large", "Opt_3_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_4_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Mr. Elliott was at fault for delegating that function to a person who lacked the ____ to perform the job properly.", "Opt_1": "instance", "Opt_2": "experience", "Opt_3": "prestige", "Opt_4": "statement", "Answer": "experience", "Opt_1_def": "example", "Opt_2_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_3_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_4_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This international ____ course has been especially created for international students in their final stage of studies in Law.", "Opt_1": "evidence", "Opt_2": "reply", "Opt_3": "site", "Opt_4": "degree", "Answer": "degree", "Opt_1_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_2_def": "an answer", "Opt_3_def": "place", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It was an ____ conservative institution, and did not enlarge its business to any extent.", "Opt_1": "virtually", "Opt_2": "extremely", "Opt_3": "absolutely", "Opt_4": "perhaps", "Answer": "extremely", "Opt_1_def": "almost", "Opt_2_def": "very", "Opt_3_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_4_def": "maybe, possibly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The new committee just adds another ____ to an already complex decision -making process.", "Opt_1": "battle", "Opt_2": "layer", "Opt_3": "doubt", "Opt_4": "disaster", "Answer": "layer", "Opt_1_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_2_def": "level", "Opt_3_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_4_def": "a huge problem or failure"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government ____ was cleared of protesters by riot police and police horses.", "Opt_1": "district", "Opt_2": "behalf", "Opt_3": "speed", "Opt_4": "shortage", "Answer": "district", "Opt_1_def": "region of a city", "Opt_2_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_3_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_4_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government has set the ____ target of halving child poverty by the year 2020.", "Opt_1": "optional", "Opt_2": "ambitious", "Opt_3": "commercial", "Opt_4": "major", "Answer": "ambitious", "Opt_1_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_2_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_3_def": "to do with business", "Opt_4_def": "important, large"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Please ____ yourselves in groups of 3 or 4, and then do the problem in the middle of the table.", "Opt_1": "arrange", "Opt_2": "enlarge", "Opt_3": "assist", "Opt_4": "offend", "Answer": "arrange", "Opt_1_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_2_def": "to make larger", "Opt_3_def": "to help", "Opt_4_def": "to go against; to upset"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It must have been about this time that Stalin took the most extraordinary decision of his career in order to ____ his political survival.", "Opt_1": "convert", "Opt_2": "compel", "Opt_3": "enlarge", "Opt_4": "assure", "Answer": "assure", "Opt_1_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_2_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_3_def": "to make larger", "Opt_4_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Spending months at a time in orbit, the scientists will be able to observe changes on the earth ____ them from day to day.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Her ____ efforts throughout the school year are certain to yield excellent results in her final examinations.", "Opt_1": "consistent", "Opt_2": "common", "Opt_3": "ancient", "Opt_4": "bold", "Answer": "consistent", "Opt_1_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_2_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_3_def": "very old", "Opt_4_def": "brave"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This position is the ____ chance to learn about the many different areas of marketing and business operations in a hands-on environment.", "Opt_1": "substantial", "Opt_2": "public", "Opt_3": "ultimate", "Opt_4": "wise", "Answer": "ultimate", "Opt_1_def": "large", "Opt_2_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_3_def": "final or most important", "Opt_4_def": "intelligent; sensible"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "As people are defining a process or a problem, sometimes solutions ____ in that moment, in the detail of their description.", "Opt_1": "mention", "Opt_2": "suggest", "Opt_3": "emerge", "Opt_4": "illuminate", "Answer": "emerge", "Opt_1_def": "to say; state", "Opt_2_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_3_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_4_def": "to show clearly; to light up"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Ultimately, this research will lessen the negative health impact of the hurricanes, which in turn will lessen the ____ burden on society.", "Opt_1": "minor", "Opt_2": "relevant", "Opt_3": "economic", "Opt_4": "valuable", "Answer": "economic", "Opt_1_def": "small, not important", "Opt_2_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_3_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_4_def": "worth a lot of money; important"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "These calculations are ____ to perform and are executed rapidly compared to Monte Carlo.", "Opt_1": "straightforward", "Opt_2": "visual", "Opt_3": "secure", "Opt_4": "immediate", "Answer": "straightforward", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_3_def": "safe", "Opt_4_def": "first (without delay)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If your condition is temporary and is impacting only attendance, make sure you follow up with your professors and ____ the Dean of Students Office.", "Opt_1": "correspond", "Opt_2": "contact", "Opt_3": "approach", "Opt_4": "master", "Answer": "contact", "Opt_1_def": "to be related to", "Opt_2_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_3_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_4_def": "to (gain) control"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Teachers identified aspects ____ to the task of teaching, such as their interactions with students and their capacity to influence student achievement.", "Opt_1": "familiar", "Opt_2": "conscious", "Opt_3": "intrinsic", "Opt_4": "rigid", "Answer": "intrinsic", "Opt_1_def": "known; well-known", "Opt_2_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_3_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_4_def": "strict, unbending"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Due to the new law, smokers will now have to ____ the pleasure of a cigarette with their drink in a restaurant or bar.", "Opt_1": "undertake", "Opt_2": "forego", "Opt_3": "force", "Opt_4": "define", "Answer": "forego", "Opt_1_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_2_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_3_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_4_def": "to state what something is or means"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is important that the government's proposals do not ____ the development of small businesses.", "Opt_1": "launch", "Opt_2": "join", "Opt_3": "disturb", "Opt_4": "inhibit", "Answer": "inhibit", "Opt_1_def": "to begin", "Opt_2_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent or stop"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The results represented an unusual ____ of old and modern practices.", "Opt_1": "item", "Opt_2": "mixture", "Opt_3": "contract", "Opt_4": "concept", "Answer": "mixture", "Opt_1_def": "thing, element", "Opt_2_def": "combination", "Opt_3_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_4_def": "idea; understanding"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The current program review process is not very ____ because there are neither rewards nor punishments for outcomes.", "Opt_1": "valuable", "Opt_2": "domestic", "Opt_3": "basic", "Opt_4": "appropriate", "Answer": "valuable", "Opt_1_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_2_def": "home", "Opt_3_def": "first or easy", "Opt_4_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The PBL method is rather time-consuming and requires the teacher to ____ a lot of effort over an extended period of time.", "Opt_1": "deprive", "Opt_2": "acquire", "Opt_3": "invest", "Opt_4": "offer", "Answer": "invest", "Opt_1_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_3_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_4_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is possible to ____ the world by boat in about three days.", "Opt_1": "represent", "Opt_2": "focus", "Opt_3": "circulate", "Opt_4": "override", "Answer": "circulate", "Opt_1_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_2_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_3_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_4_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A popular type of TV programme shows people who escape the ____ world and pretend to live as farmers did 100 years ago.", "Opt_1": "evident", "Opt_2": "contemporary", "Opt_3": "aware", "Opt_4": "political", "Answer": "contemporary", "Opt_1_def": "clear", "Opt_2_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_3_def": "knowing", "Opt_4_def": "to do government and politics"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She said sorry to the teacher and ____ avoided a detention.", "Opt_1": "thereby", "Opt_2": "virtually", "Opt_3": "accordingly", "Opt_4": "barely", "Answer": "thereby", "Opt_1_def": "by doing this", "Opt_2_def": "almost", "Opt_3_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; hardly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The Committee determines, in its sole discretion, whether the College is entitled to ____ ownership of the invention.", "Opt_1": "interact", "Opt_2": "dominate", "Opt_3": "claim", "Opt_4": "estimate", "Answer": "claim", "Opt_1_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_2_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_3_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_4_def": "to make an intelligent guess"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Army leadership must ____ the importance of reducing energy demand to decrease costs.", "Opt_1": "undergo", "Opt_2": "earn", "Opt_3": "emphasize", "Opt_4": "depend", "Answer": "emphasize", "Opt_1_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_2_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_3_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_4_def": "be influenced (by)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It was a time when priests were experiencing financial ____ and the Church was unable to subsidize many of their expenses.", "Opt_1": "component", "Opt_2": "crisis", "Opt_3": "portion", "Opt_4": "tradition", "Answer": "crisis", "Opt_1_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_2_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_3_def": "part, amount", "Opt_4_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Including future irrelevant costs generally will not lead to a poor choice; it will only ____ the analysis.", "Opt_1": "complicate", "Opt_2": "contact", "Opt_3": "occur", "Opt_4": "submit", "Answer": "complicate", "Opt_1_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_2_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_3_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_4_def": "to give; to send"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "I am ____ surprised I did so well in the test because I didn't work very hard this term.", "Opt_1": "somewhat", "Opt_2": "virtually", "Opt_3": "indeed", "Opt_4": "merely", "Answer": "somewhat", "Opt_1_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_2_def": "almost", "Opt_3_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_4_def": "only, just, simply"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There has been a recent ____ in language teaching towards more grammar and vocabulary.", "Opt_1": "constraint", "Opt_2": "community", "Opt_3": "experience", "Opt_4": "shift", "Answer": "shift", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people", "Opt_3_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_4_def": "change"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you want to ____ the chess club, please sign your name on the list below.", "Opt_1": "involve", "Opt_2": "condemn", "Opt_3": "join", "Opt_4": "absorb", "Answer": "join", "Opt_1_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_2_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_4_def": "to take in; to take up"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If you ____ your calculator like that, you'll break it.", "Opt_1": "trade", "Opt_2": "abuse", "Opt_3": "import", "Opt_4": "accelerate", "Answer": "abuse", "Opt_1_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_2_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_3_def": "to bring in (to a country)", "Opt_4_def": "to get or make faster"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Employees interested in participating in a ____ tax sheltered annuity program should contact their personnel officer.", "Opt_1": "voluntary", "Opt_2": "strict", "Opt_3": "fundamental", "Opt_4": "numerous", "Answer": "voluntary", "Opt_1_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_2_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "very many"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The doctor had to ____ the x-rays carefully to find any signs of abnormality.", "Opt_1": "inspect", "Opt_2": "receive", "Opt_3": "risk", "Opt_4": "obey", "Answer": "inspect", "Opt_1_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_4_def": "to do as commanded or expected"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Students who get in the athletic teams enjoy a high ____ in the school community.", "Opt_1": "behalf", "Opt_2": "controversy", "Opt_3": "proportion", "Opt_4": "prestige", "Answer": "prestige", "Opt_1_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_2_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_3_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_4_def": "fame and respect"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If he is correct this would certainly be an elementary solution to an ____ problem.", "Opt_1": "previous", "Opt_2": "subtle", "Opt_3": "ancient", "Opt_4": "urban", "Answer": "ancient", "Opt_1_def": "the one before", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "very old", "Opt_4_def": "of the town or city"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This ____ is subject to formal revision before publication in the university journal.", "Opt_1": "term", "Opt_2": "guide", "Opt_3": "opinion", "Opt_4": "outline", "Answer": "opinion", "Opt_1_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_2_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_3_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "plan or summary"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It was not until about 500 years ago that scientists and doctors began to examine the ____ of the human body.", "Opt_1": "detriment", "Opt_2": "method", "Opt_3": "interior", "Opt_4": "dispute", "Answer": "interior", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_2_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "inside", "Opt_4_def": "argument; conflict"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ criterion for successful teaching is the ability to interest the students.", "Opt_1": "latter", "Opt_2": "evident", "Opt_3": "essential", "Opt_4": "final", "Answer": "essential", "Opt_1_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_2_def": "clear", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "last"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "This week's anniversary of the US-led war against Iraq is an appropriate ____ to ask: Are Americans safer than we were a year ago?", "Opt_1": "battle", "Opt_2": "occasion", "Opt_3": "quality", "Opt_4": "growth", "Answer": "occasion", "Opt_1_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_2_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_3_def": "worth or value", "Opt_4_def": "development, increase"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The administration is planning to ____ the school day until 4pm.", "Opt_1": "fade", "Opt_2": "review", "Opt_3": "imply", "Opt_4": "extend", "Answer": "extend", "Opt_1_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_2_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to make longer in time or space"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "DeRosa's success is a genuine example of how the right ____ and excellent faculty really can cause a scholarly transformation.", "Opt_1": "environment", "Opt_2": "interpretation", "Opt_3": "proportion", "Opt_4": "liberty", "Answer": "environment", "Opt_1_def": "the world around us", "Opt_2_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_3_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_4_def": "freedom"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You need to do a better job when you ____ your work. There are far too many unnecessary spelling and punctuation errors.", "Opt_1": "fail", "Opt_2": "dispose", "Opt_3": "consist", "Opt_4": "edit", "Answer": "edit", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_2_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_4_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The grade will be amended but the former grade will remain on the record with an ____ notation.", "Opt_1": "radical", "Opt_2": "infinite", "Opt_3": "optional", "Opt_4": "appropriate", "Answer": "appropriate", "Opt_1_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_2_def": "without an end", "Opt_3_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_4_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "An even number multiplied by an odd number will always ____ an even number.", "Opt_1": "promote", "Opt_2": "reduce", "Opt_3": "investigate", "Opt_4": "yield", "Answer": "yield", "Opt_1_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_2_def": "to make smaller or shorter", "Opt_3_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_4_def": "to produce"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Please note that section 5 is the most important, and ____ it should constitute the majority of your journal entry.", "Opt_1": "accordingly", "Opt_2": "hence", "Opt_3": "roughly", "Opt_4": "dramatically", "Answer": "hence", "Opt_1_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_2_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_3_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_4_def": "very strongly, significantly"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The merger of two sellers of that product in the area could not enhance market ____ significantly.", "Opt_1": "credit", "Opt_2": "procedure", "Opt_3": "power", "Opt_4": "minimum", "Answer": "power", "Opt_1_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_2_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_3_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_4_def": "the smallest amount; the least"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You are more ____ to get a better grade if you check your work carefully.", "Opt_1": "artificial", "Opt_2": "liable", "Opt_3": "numerous", "Opt_4": "mobile", "Answer": "liable", "Opt_1_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_2_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_3_def": "very many", "Opt_4_def": "moving; able to move"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If the departure times are not ____ for you, there is a list of recommended car and taxi services available as well.", "Opt_1": "bold", "Opt_2": "straightforward", "Opt_3": "convenient", "Opt_4": "massive", "Answer": "convenient", "Opt_1_def": "brave", "Opt_2_def": "easy", "Opt_3_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The partners realized that their small fund was not sufficient to support early ____ start-ups in the environment of the early 2000s.", "Opt_1": "stage", "Opt_2": "drawback", "Opt_3": "detail", "Opt_4": "outcome", "Answer": "stage", "Opt_1_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_2_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_3_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Students are encouraged to focus not only on the skills and knowledge related to the high stakes tests but also the skills and knowledge to perform more ____ tasks.", "Opt_1": "authentic", "Opt_2": "hostile", "Opt_3": "vital", "Opt_4": "apparent", "Answer": "authentic", "Opt_1_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_2_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "clear; obvious"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Not all scientists agree with the ____ that the earth is getting warmer because of human pollution.", "Opt_1": "function", "Opt_2": "hypothesis", "Opt_3": "doubt", "Opt_4": "distance", "Answer": "hypothesis", "Opt_1_def": "job or role", "Opt_2_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_3_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_4_def": "how far it is from one place to another"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The bank did not ____ to make payment but insisted first on the signature of the husband.", "Opt_1": "prefer", "Opt_2": "refuse", "Opt_3": "explain", "Opt_4": "exploit", "Answer": "refuse", "Opt_1_def": "to like better", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_3_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Miller's path to UCSC was far from smooth, but her ____ and determination kept her moving toward her goal.", "Opt_1": "notice", "Opt_2": "judge", "Opt_3": "arise", "Opt_4": "focus", "Answer": "focus", "Opt_1_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_2_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There is a ____ belief among the public that the government lied about the reason for going to war.", "Opt_1": "firm", "Opt_2": "superior", "Opt_3": "trivial", "Opt_4": "widespread", "Answer": "widespread", "Opt_1_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_2_def": "better", "Opt_3_def": "not important", "Opt_4_def": "common"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Everyone should join together to ____ the environment.", "Opt_1": "accomplish", "Opt_2": "protect", "Opt_3": "exaggerate", "Opt_4": "collaborate", "Answer": "protect", "Opt_1_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_2_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_3_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_4_def": "to work together"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The B grade had come to signify work that was ____ acceptable.", "Opt_1": "nevertheless", "Opt_2": "furthermore", "Opt_3": "merely", "Opt_4": "barely", "Answer": "barely", "Opt_1_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_2_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_3_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; hardly"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "No matter how we talk and discuss normally, we now have to ensure that the way we talk must not ____ any religious, ethnic, cultural, or political group.", "Opt_1": "deprive", "Opt_2": "offend", "Opt_3": "precede", "Opt_4": "control", "Answer": "offend", "Opt_1_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_3_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Example: She doesn't have a very good ____ with her parents.", "Opt_1": "mixture", "Opt_2": "evidence", "Opt_3": "career", "Opt_4": "relationship", "Answer": "relationship", "Opt_1_def": "combination", "Opt_2_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_3_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_4_def": "the way to things are connected"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government has done a deal with the nurses union in order to ____ strikes in hospitals.", "Opt_1": "avoid", "Opt_2": "halt", "Opt_3": "deserve", "Opt_4": "receive", "Answer": "avoid", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You would ____ improve your chances of success if you made more effort.", "Opt_1": "accordingly", "Opt_2": "eventually", "Opt_3": "greatly", "Opt_4": "perhaps", "Answer": "greatly", "Opt_1_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_2_def": "in the end", "Opt_3_def": "very much", "Opt_4_def": "maybe, possibly"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "How could his final test scores ____ so strongly from the predictions we made?", "Opt_1": "separate", "Opt_2": "deviate", "Opt_3": "subsidize", "Opt_4": "correlate", "Answer": "deviate", "Opt_1_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_2_def": "to be different", "Opt_3_def": "to support financially", "Opt_4_def": "to have a close connection"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Consequently, the percentages will not ____ to 100% because many students were neutral on the questions in the survey.", "Opt_1": "sum", "Opt_2": "choice", "Opt_3": "education", "Opt_4": "labour", "Answer": "sum", "Opt_1_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_2_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_3_def": "schooling", "Opt_4_def": "work"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Doctors were unable to ____ the man who was pulled out of the icy river.", "Opt_1": "damage", "Opt_2": "revive", "Opt_3": "occupy", "Opt_4": "collapse", "Answer": "revive", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_2_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_3_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_4_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I think your ____ is wrong. You should be in science class now, not ESL.", "Opt_1": "schedule", "Opt_2": "site", "Opt_3": "obstacle", "Opt_4": "rise", "Answer": "schedule", "Opt_1_def": "timetable", "Opt_2_def": "place", "Opt_3_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_4_def": "to go up"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Eat less, ____ more: the formula for weight loss is so simple, yet so hard.", "Opt_1": "trend", "Opt_2": "counsel", "Opt_3": "order", "Opt_4": "exercise", "Answer": "exercise", "Opt_1_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_3_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of work, activity"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If a person tends to be ____ in relationships or at work, it is likely that her investment decisions will also be ____.", "Opt_1": "optional", "Opt_2": "major", "Opt_3": "logical", "Opt_4": "cautious", "Answer": "cautious", "Opt_1_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "making sense", "Opt_4_def": "careful"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Many people were very unhappy at the police's ____ of the demonstrators.", "Opt_1": "means", "Opt_2": "limit", "Opt_3": "assignment", "Opt_4": "treatment", "Answer": "treatment", "Opt_1_def": "way", "Opt_2_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_3_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_4_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Poor diet and drug ____ underlie many serious health problems.", "Opt_1": "address", "Opt_2": "review", "Opt_3": "align", "Opt_4": "abuse", "Answer": "abuse", "Opt_1_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_2_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_3_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_4_def": "to treat someone or something badly"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "But please keep in mind that the Internet doesn't replace ____ counseling.", "Opt_1": "choice", "Opt_2": "truth", "Opt_3": "occasion", "Opt_4": "career", "Answer": "career", "Opt_1_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_2_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_3_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_4_def": "a long-term job"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The elders in the village are fighting to retain their people's traditions, but the younger ones want to ____ the modern world of computers and mobile phones.", "Opt_1": "emerge", "Opt_2": "join", "Opt_3": "restore", "Opt_4": "induce", "Answer": "join", "Opt_1_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_2_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_3_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen; to force"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "From the airplane it was possible to see the ____ of the destruction caused in the earthquake.", "Opt_1": "circumstances", "Opt_2": "scale", "Opt_3": "defeat", "Opt_4": "procedure", "Answer": "scale", "Opt_1_def": "situation", "Opt_2_def": "extent", "Opt_3_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_4_def": "the way to do something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ between mother and child is said to be the strongest of any personal relationships.", "Opt_1": "directions", "Opt_2": "description", "Opt_3": "concept", "Opt_4": "bond", "Answer": "bond", "Opt_1_def": "instructions", "Opt_2_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_3_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_4_def": "link; tie"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This emphasis on improving student outcomes will ____ in the immediate future as the dominant factor in determining the success or failure of education reform strategies.", "Opt_1": "mention", "Opt_2": "suffer", "Opt_3": "persist", "Opt_4": "remove", "Answer": "persist", "Opt_1_def": "to say; state", "Opt_2_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_3_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_4_def": "to take away"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If these reports are not returned, we will presume that you have used all ____ sick leave for that particular reporting period.", "Opt_1": "available", "Opt_2": "mobile", "Opt_3": "optional", "Opt_4": "eligible", "Answer": "available", "Opt_1_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_2_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_3_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_4_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some people ____ that the US government knew in advance about the terrorist attack on the Twin Towers in New York.", "Opt_1": "suspect", "Opt_2": "preserve", "Opt_3": "prosper", "Opt_4": "illustrate", "Answer": "suspect", "Opt_1_def": "to believe", "Opt_2_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_3_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_4_def": "to show; to make clear"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You need to be careful not to ____ people that you meet on the internet They may not be who they claim to be..", "Opt_1": "retire", "Opt_2": "monitor", "Opt_3": "trust", "Opt_4": "illustrate", "Answer": "trust", "Opt_1_def": "to stop working", "Opt_2_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )", "Opt_3_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_4_def": "to show; to make clear"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The primary ____ of the Management Information Systems Department is to prepare students for exciting and challenging careers in the information technology.", "Opt_1": "justice", "Opt_2": "contract", "Opt_3": "manner", "Opt_4": "objective", "Answer": "objective", "Opt_1_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_2_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_3_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "aim or goal"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Coca-Cola is a drink that is ____ popular.", "Opt_1": "universally", "Opt_2": "eventually", "Opt_3": "therefore", "Opt_4": "merely", "Answer": "universally", "Opt_1_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_2_def": "in the end", "Opt_3_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_4_def": "only, just, simply"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Many people do not ____ a top engineering education with a liberal arts setting.", "Opt_1": "admit", "Opt_2": "associate", "Opt_3": "transmit", "Opt_4": "separate", "Answer": "associate", "Opt_1_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_2_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_3_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_4_def": "to pull or put apart"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The study finds they are more likely than their non-Latino white neighbors to ____ another stroke in the first two years after living through one.", "Opt_1": "occur", "Opt_2": "respect", "Opt_3": "decrease", "Opt_4": "suffer", "Answer": "suffer", "Opt_1_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_2_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_4_def": "to experience something bad or painful"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You must ____ the US using the visa document issued by the institution you will be attending.", "Opt_1": "label", "Opt_2": "infer", "Opt_3": "postpone", "Opt_4": "enter", "Answer": "enter", "Opt_1_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_3_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_4_def": "to go in or put in"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The syllabus must ____ how attendance and participation affect, if at all, the student's course grade.", "Opt_1": "clarify", "Opt_2": "precede", "Opt_3": "discover", "Opt_4": "affect", "Answer": "clarify", "Opt_1_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_2_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_4_def": "to have an influence on"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This interesting ____ offers the student of neuroscience access to an immense amount of information on the discipline.", "Opt_1": "license", "Opt_2": "advantage", "Opt_3": "site", "Opt_4": "component", "Answer": "site", "Opt_1_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_2_def": "benefit", "Opt_3_def": "place", "Opt_4_def": "part of; an element of"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The department may admit students of superior promise but ____ preparation, provided that such students correct their deficiencies.", "Opt_1": "immediate", "Opt_2": "deficient", "Opt_3": "neutral", "Opt_4": "annual", "Answer": "deficient", "Opt_1_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_2_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_3_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_4_def": "yearly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Calderone's insistence that sex education should begin as early as kindergarten did not ____ religious conservative groups.", "Opt_1": "impress", "Opt_2": "demonstrate", "Opt_3": "inspect", "Opt_4": "donate", "Answer": "impress", "Opt_1_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to give (usually money)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The company has the liberty to ____ employees without giving a reason during the first 6 months of their employment.", "Opt_1": "dismiss", "Opt_2": "infer", "Opt_3": "publish", "Opt_4": "regret", "Answer": "dismiss", "Opt_1_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_2_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_3_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_4_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Research shows that earnings ____ strongly with IQ levels.", "Opt_1": "accompany", "Opt_2": "disrupt", "Opt_3": "specify", "Opt_4": "correlate", "Answer": "correlate", "Opt_1_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_3_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_4_def": "to have a close connection"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A few years ago a robot was lowered to the seabed to ____ some objects from the wreck of the Titanic.", "Opt_1": "arise", "Opt_2": "anticipate", "Opt_3": "attempt", "Opt_4": "recover", "Answer": "recover", "Opt_1_def": "to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to expect", "Opt_3_def": "to try", "Opt_4_def": "to get back"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The police had difficulty in trying to ____ the enormous crowd after the pop concert.", "Opt_1": "decline", "Opt_2": "confirm", "Opt_3": "disperse", "Opt_4": "suppress", "Answer": "disperse", "Opt_1_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_3_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Teachers and parents can learn and share ideas for helping to work for more successful outcomes in the ____ from school to adult life.", "Opt_1": "privilege", "Opt_2": "loss", "Opt_3": "transition", "Opt_4": "route", "Answer": "transition", "Opt_1_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_2_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_3_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_4_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The shortening of the lunch break caused ____ between the workers and the management.", "Opt_1": "directions", "Opt_2": "gap", "Opt_3": "friction", "Opt_4": "comment", "Answer": "friction", "Opt_1_def": "instructions", "Opt_2_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_3_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The study finds they are more likely than their non-Latino white neighbors to ____ another stroke in the first two years after living through one.", "Opt_1": "consult", "Opt_2": "expel", "Opt_3": "suffer", "Opt_4": "dominate", "Answer": "suffer", "Opt_1_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_2_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_3_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_4_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "When morality comes up against ____, it is seldom ____ that loses.", "Opt_1": "profit", "Opt_2": "sector", "Opt_3": "domain", "Opt_4": "materials", "Answer": "profit", "Opt_1_def": "money gained", "Opt_2_def": "part; area", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need to do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The North Viet Namese Army was not ____ enough to outflank southern forces.", "Opt_1": "competent", "Opt_2": "mobile", "Opt_3": "faint", "Opt_4": "confident", "Answer": "mobile", "Opt_1_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_2_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_3_def": "not strong", "Opt_4_def": "sure that something will happen"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Science teacher: Please ____ what happens when I pour water into the flask.", "Opt_1": "observe", "Opt_2": "exaggerate", "Opt_3": "fulfill", "Opt_4": "deliver", "Answer": "observe", "Opt_1_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It may well be that the two towers on Boynton Hill will soon become a familiar ____ of innovation to educators and students across the country.", "Opt_1": "symbol", "Opt_2": "rise", "Opt_3": "credit", "Opt_4": "apparatus", "Answer": "symbol", "Opt_1_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_2_def": "to go up", "Opt_3_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_4_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The teacher assistant was unable through various interactive ____ to hold class interest, handled questions poorly, and was generally unable to stimulate discussion.", "Opt_1": "means", "Opt_2": "scope", "Opt_3": "generation", "Opt_4": "goal", "Answer": "means", "Opt_1_def": "way", "Opt_2_def": "extent, range", "Opt_3_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_4_def": "aim or intention"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The drive to excel must be ____ in the culture of a university.", "Opt_1": "odd", "Opt_2": "inevitable", "Opt_3": "inherent", "Opt_4": "drastic", "Answer": "inherent", "Opt_1_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_3_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_4_def": "severe; great"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Using a computer program makes it easier to ____ long pieces of writing.", "Opt_1": "own", "Opt_2": "fulfill", "Opt_3": "admit", "Opt_4": "annotate", "Answer": "annotate", "Opt_1_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_2_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_4_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The scope of the project will include all processes, people, organizational structures, systems and ____ currently in place.", "Opt_1": "device", "Opt_2": "expert", "Opt_3": "majority", "Opt_4": "facilities", "Answer": "facilities", "Opt_1_def": "object; method", "Opt_2_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_3_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_4_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The university should not ____ students who take an extra year to complete their studies as lazy.", "Opt_1": "label", "Opt_2": "offend", "Opt_3": "isolate", "Opt_4": "differentiate", "Answer": "label", "Opt_1_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_3_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_4_def": "to make different; to see the difference"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Once the conference is over the government will turn its ____ to the problems of urban crime.", "Opt_1": "atmosphere", "Opt_2": "aspect", "Opt_3": "disaster", "Opt_4": "attention", "Answer": "attention", "Opt_1_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_3_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_4_def": "focus"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The course aims at helping students ____ a working familiarity with the Federal Rules of Evidence.", "Opt_1": "acquire", "Opt_2": "seek", "Opt_3": "cancel", "Opt_4": "assemble", "Answer": "acquire", "Opt_1_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_2_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_3_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_4_def": "to get, put or bring together"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "They further alleged that the removal of the soil would ____ the quality of the district's drinking water.", "Opt_1": "disturb", "Opt_2": "add", "Opt_3": "displace", "Opt_4": "collaborate", "Answer": "disturb", "Opt_1_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_2_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_3_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to work together"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Asian companies are good at building small cars but will never ____ the mainstream US car market.", "Opt_1": "achieve", "Opt_2": "dominate", "Opt_3": "imply", "Opt_4": "disturb", "Answer": "dominate", "Opt_1_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_2_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to interrupt, stop from working"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If your exam is closed book, you will want to prepare an outline that will ____ you in studying until the day of the exam.", "Opt_1": "circulate", "Opt_2": "modify", "Opt_3": "react", "Opt_4": "assist", "Answer": "assist", "Opt_1_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_2_def": "to change", "Opt_3_def": "to respond", "Opt_4_def": "to help"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Google uses a unique computer program to generate its lists of hits within a very short ____ of time.", "Opt_1": "defect", "Opt_2": "period", "Opt_3": "opinion", "Opt_4": "interval", "Answer": "period", "Opt_1_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_2_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_3_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "a period of time"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Does this report ____ to this year or last year?", "Opt_1": "combine", "Opt_2": "retire", "Opt_3": "create", "Opt_4": "refer", "Answer": "refer", "Opt_1_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_2_def": "to stop working", "Opt_3_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_4_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Congress is resolved to ____ online gambling in America.", "Opt_1": "prohibit", "Opt_2": "unite", "Opt_3": "dictate", "Opt_4": "warn", "Answer": "prohibit", "Opt_1_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_4_def": "to notify (of possible danger)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I need to speak to John's parents ____ his constant absence.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government should not ____ young unmarried mothers by giving them free housing.", "Opt_1": "encourage", "Opt_2": "reward", "Opt_3": "amend", "Opt_4": "apply", "Answer": "reward", "Opt_1_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_2_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_4_def": "to be relevant (to)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Students are leaving this week for the Dominican Republic to ____ extensive nurse practitioner training.", "Opt_1": "undertake", "Opt_2": "illustrate", "Opt_3": "share", "Opt_4": "organize", "Answer": "undertake", "Opt_1_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_2_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_4_def": "to put into (its proper) place"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We can ____ that China is unlikely to put significant pressure on Sudan, and that Sudan could and would easily resist such pressure.", "Opt_1": "conclude", "Opt_2": "trigger", "Opt_3": "form", "Opt_4": "refuse", "Answer": "conclude", "Opt_1_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_2_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_3_def": "to make (into a shape)", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government has decided to ____ financial aid to the African country until the civil war is over.", "Opt_1": "depart", "Opt_2": "achieve", "Opt_3": "prevail", "Opt_4": "block", "Answer": "block", "Opt_1_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_2_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_3_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_4_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I'm sorry, but I will ____ not be able to come to the meeting next week.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "perhaps", "Opt_3": "therefore", "Opt_4": "definitely", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_3_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_4_def": "certainly; without doubt"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "How can the traditional classroom and the technology in it ____ deeper learning?", "Opt_1": "encourage", "Opt_2": "realize", "Opt_3": "emphasize", "Opt_4": "implement", "Answer": "encourage", "Opt_1_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_2_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_3_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government failed to suppress street demonstrations ____ its decision to increase petrol tax.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Worse yet, 1992 was no ____ but the culmination of bad trends, most of them directly related to the company's lack of focus.", "Opt_1": "anomaly", "Opt_2": "procedure", "Opt_3": "quantity", "Opt_4": "objection", "Answer": "anomaly", "Opt_1_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_2_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We southerners, and especially we white southerners, ____ a huge debt to valiant civil rights leaders like Martin Luther King.", "Opt_1": "oppose", "Opt_2": "destroy", "Opt_3": "disturb", "Opt_4": "owe", "Answer": "owe", "Opt_1_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_2_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_4_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The past 20 years have seen a ____ increase in our understanding of the biology of cancer.", "Opt_1": "cautious", "Opt_2": "rapid", "Opt_3": "automatic", "Opt_4": "entire", "Answer": "rapid", "Opt_1_def": "careful", "Opt_2_def": "quick", "Opt_3_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_4_def": "whole, all"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If you wish to contribute material that is copyrighted by someone ____ yourself, then you will need to document that the copyright holder has agreed.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This note describes a scoring ____ for the co-reference task in MUC6.", "Opt_1": "opinion", "Opt_2": "benefit", "Opt_3": "scheme", "Opt_4": "dimension", "Answer": "scheme", "Opt_1_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_4_def": "importance; amount"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This is a controversial point that will ____ much debate in the classroom, mainly among graduate students.", "Opt_1": "generate", "Opt_2": "present", "Opt_3": "settle", "Opt_4": "suggest", "Answer": "generate", "Opt_1_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_2_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_3_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_4_def": "to say an idea; to recommend"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A small proportion of the government were ____ the Prime Minister's plan, but they were outvoted.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In history lessons we learn about many ____ peoples such as the Egyptians who built the pyramids, and Roman emperors like Julius Caesar.", "Opt_1": "invisible", "Opt_2": "sane", "Opt_3": "ancient", "Opt_4": "political", "Answer": "ancient", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_2_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_3_def": "very old", "Opt_4_def": "to do government and politics"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Thousands of farm families are being forced off the land, and we are being told that it is an ____ consequence of technological progress.", "Opt_1": "invisible", "Opt_2": "inevitable", "Opt_3": "entire", "Opt_4": "appropriate", "Answer": "inevitable", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_3_def": "whole, all", "Opt_4_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The department may admit students of superior promise but ____ preparation, provided that such students correct their deficiencies.", "Opt_1": "deficient", "Opt_2": "ambitious", "Opt_3": "immediate", "Opt_4": "homogeneous", "Answer": "deficient", "Opt_1_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_2_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_3_def": "first (without delay)", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "She didn't study for the vocabulary test, so ____ she got a low score.", "Opt_1": "naturally", "Opt_2": "respectively", "Opt_3": "generally", "Opt_4": "seldom", "Answer": "naturally", "Opt_1_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_2_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "usually", "Opt_4_def": "rare"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I ____ to put all of my lecture notes online because I do want students to attend the lectures.", "Opt_1": "hesitate", "Opt_2": "arrange", "Opt_3": "subsidize", "Opt_4": "prefer", "Answer": "hesitate", "Opt_1_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_3_def": "to support financially", "Opt_4_def": "to like better"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There is a sharp contrast between Japan's fairly rigid ____ of national and private universities with the United States, which has a wider variety of institutions.", "Opt_1": "hierarchy", "Opt_2": "quantity", "Opt_3": "concern", "Opt_4": "property", "Answer": "hierarchy", "Opt_1_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_4_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Many prisons cannot ____ with this law due to lack of space and inadequate facilities.", "Opt_1": "comply", "Opt_2": "tolerate", "Opt_3": "increase", "Opt_4": "suppress", "Answer": "comply", "Opt_1_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_2_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is a serious shortage of workers in the ____ of computer science. The government is hoping to attract qualified workers from overseas to fill the vacancies.", "Opt_1": "grant", "Opt_2": "sector", "Opt_3": "profession", "Opt_4": "habit", "Answer": "profession", "Opt_1_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_2_def": "part; area", "Opt_3_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_4_def": "something you do regularly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government needs to change its policies ____ the punishment of young criminals.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The aim of the proposal is to ____ people of the liberty to download songs and videos from the internet.", "Opt_1": "emphasize", "Opt_2": "respect", "Opt_3": "deprive", "Opt_4": "refuse", "Answer": "deprive", "Opt_1_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_2_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_3_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We should not ____ the costs, minimize the benefits of what we have already achieved, or downplay the risk of failure to persevere.", "Opt_1": "exaggerate", "Opt_2": "circulate", "Opt_3": "spread", "Opt_4": "strain", "Answer": "exaggerate", "Opt_1_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_2_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_3_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_4_def": "to put under stress or make difficult"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "In my school district it is emphasized that teachers must ____ instruction for students.", "Opt_1": "magnify", "Opt_2": "indicate", "Opt_3": "differentiate", "Opt_4": "tolerate", "Answer": "differentiate", "Opt_1_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_2_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_4_def": "to allow to happen; to bear"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ German family has 1.8 children.", "Opt_1": "slight", "Opt_2": "average", "Opt_3": "essential", "Opt_4": "tough", "Answer": "average", "Opt_1_def": "small", "Opt_2_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, strong"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "My ____ intention was to resign, but then I changed my mind.", "Opt_1": "royal", "Opt_2": "initial", "Opt_3": "harsh", "Opt_4": "outstanding", "Answer": "initial", "Opt_1_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_2_def": "starting, first", "Opt_3_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_4_def": "excellent"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She very ____ comes late to class. I hope there is nothing wrong.", "Opt_1": "barely", "Opt_2": "roughly", "Opt_3": "seldom", "Opt_4": "predominantly", "Answer": "seldom", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_2_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_3_def": "rare", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The business manager could not ____ the anomaly in the company's finances, and was asked to resign.", "Opt_1": "cooperate", "Opt_2": "assert", "Opt_3": "explain", "Opt_4": "arise", "Answer": "explain", "Opt_1_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_2_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to happen"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Preparing yourself for a ____ in oceanography is probably one of the most interesting and rewarding (yet difficult) paths to travel.", "Opt_1": "career", "Opt_2": "struggle", "Opt_3": "phenomenon", "Opt_4": "phrase", "Answer": "career", "Opt_1_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_2_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_3_def": "a happening (often unusual or unexpected)", "Opt_4_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure."}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We have a painting at home that's very valuable. It must be ____ more than a million dollars!", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "before"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Her problems are close to the ____ and tend to be expressed in more direct, less symbolic, behavioral and emotional terms.", "Opt_1": "surface", "Opt_2": "tool", "Opt_3": "doubt", "Opt_4": "battle", "Answer": "surface", "Opt_1_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_2_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_4_def": "fight, part of a war"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It was the result of his labour that Brazil could ____ scientific institutions.", "Opt_1": "blame", "Opt_2": "protest", "Opt_3": "speculate", "Opt_4": "afford", "Answer": "afford", "Opt_1_def": "to accuse", "Opt_2_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_3_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_4_def": "to be able to pay for something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We will not violate the personal ____ of co-workers and customers, and will respect their right to privacy.", "Opt_1": "level", "Opt_2": "property", "Opt_3": "context", "Opt_4": "defect", "Answer": "property", "Opt_1_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_2_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_3_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_4_def": "problem; mistake"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Our experience is that small businesses (especially those newly formed) tend to ____ unrealistically low indirect costs.", "Opt_1": "restrict", "Opt_2": "train", "Opt_3": "propose", "Opt_4": "manufacture", "Answer": "propose", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "to suggest", "Opt_4_def": "to produce (with machines)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Women often ____ less money that men doing the same job. This anomaly must be stopped.", "Opt_1": "earn", "Opt_2": "allocate", "Opt_3": "eliminate", "Opt_4": "trade", "Answer": "earn", "Opt_1_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_2_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_3_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_4_def": "to exchange products or services"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The business has decided to ____ a large reorganization in the attempt to increase profits.", "Opt_1": "refer", "Opt_2": "conclude", "Opt_3": "undergo", "Opt_4": "block", "Answer": "undergo", "Opt_1_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_2_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_3_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_4_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "David Malik maintains that most students are not able to ____ teaching effectiveness.", "Opt_1": "transfer", "Opt_2": "multiply", "Opt_3": "manage", "Opt_4": "evaluate", "Answer": "evaluate", "Opt_1_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_2_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_3_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She had a flash of ____ that she was going to fail her exams unless she started working.", "Opt_1": "hypothesis", "Opt_2": "insight", "Opt_3": "lack", "Opt_4": "interpretation", "Answer": "insight", "Opt_1_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_2_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_3_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_4_def": "explanation; assessment"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Many birds ____ south in the winter to find warmer temperatures.", "Opt_1": "migrate", "Opt_2": "revive", "Opt_3": "correlate", "Opt_4": "qualify", "Answer": "migrate", "Opt_1_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_2_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_3_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_4_def": "to become eligible"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "They did not ____ an attack. They responded to an attack from terrorists.", "Opt_1": "introduce", "Opt_2": "provoke", "Opt_3": "recur", "Opt_4": "contact", "Answer": "provoke", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_2_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to happen again", "Opt_4_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Nine tenths of an iceberg is under water and hence ____ to ships.", "Opt_1": "vital", "Opt_2": "random", "Opt_3": "massive", "Opt_4": "invisible", "Answer": "invisible", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "by chance; without any sequence", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be seen"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Studies have proven that taste is only a ____ consideration in the purchase decision for soft drinks.", "Opt_1": "complete", "Opt_2": "sane", "Opt_3": "major", "Opt_4": "minor", "Answer": "minor", "Opt_1_def": "full or finished", "Opt_2_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_3_def": "important, large", "Opt_4_def": "small, not important"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Students are encouraged to first ____ all possibilities for Federal and state financial aid programs before seeking alternative loans.", "Opt_1": "reverse", "Opt_2": "engage", "Opt_3": "exhaust", "Opt_4": "deprive", "Answer": "exhaust", "Opt_1_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_2_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_3_def": "to use up", "Opt_4_def": "to take away (the opportunity)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government thanked Greenpeace for the information but said that it wasn't ____ to its decision.", "Opt_1": "major", "Opt_2": "relevant", "Opt_3": "profound", "Opt_4": "annual", "Answer": "relevant", "Opt_1_def": "important, large", "Opt_2_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_3_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_4_def": "yearly"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The bank didn't think that her idea would ____ enough money so they refused to finance it.", "Opt_1": "avoid", "Opt_2": "suppose", "Opt_3": "threaten", "Opt_4": "generate", "Answer": "generate", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_2_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_3_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_4_def": "to make or produce"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This week's anniversary of the US-led war ____ Iraq is an appropriate occasion to ask: Are Americans safer than we were a year ago?", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A half century ago the conflict over state regulation of railroads was the ____ issue in Alabama politics.", "Opt_1": "previous", "Opt_2": "immense", "Opt_3": "chief", "Opt_4": "massive", "Answer": "chief", "Opt_1_def": "the one before", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "very large"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In the excitement of bringing the Internet into our classrooms, we sometimes forget to ____ our learners appropriately.", "Opt_1": "refute", "Opt_2": "decline", "Opt_3": "prepare", "Opt_4": "separate", "Answer": "prepare", "Opt_1_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_2_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_4_def": "to pull or put apart"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Campuses must ____ an annual security report detailing statistics regarding crimes committed on campus and at affiliated locations.", "Opt_1": "transform", "Opt_2": "publish", "Opt_3": "tolerate", "Opt_4": "realize", "Answer": "publish", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_2_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_4_def": "to come to know or understand"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "These ____ and assessment strategies meet the needs of learners who are diverse (e.g., in culture, ethnicity, race, language, special needs).", "Opt_1": "opinion", "Opt_2": "trend", "Opt_3": "instruction", "Opt_4": "record", "Answer": "instruction", "Opt_1_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_4_def": "evidence; documentation"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ criterion for successful teaching is the ability to interest the students.", "Opt_1": "essential", "Opt_2": "steady", "Opt_3": "obsolete", "Opt_4": "constant", "Answer": "essential", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_3_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_4_def": "not changing; long-lasting"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You will not be able to request a ____ name unless you provide the following information.", "Opt_1": "standard", "Opt_2": "point", "Opt_3": "domain", "Opt_4": "statement", "Answer": "domain", "Opt_1_def": "quality", "Opt_2_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_3_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She was able to ____ the Smartboard screen controls so that the presentation was visible to everyone.", "Opt_1": "manipulate", "Opt_2": "integrate", "Opt_3": "prosper", "Opt_4": "comply", "Answer": "manipulate", "Opt_1_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_2_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_3_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_4_def": "to do what someone asks or orders"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You can ____ this book until the end of the school year.", "Opt_1": "enumerate", "Opt_2": "fear", "Opt_3": "retain", "Opt_4": "discern", "Answer": "retain", "Opt_1_def": "to list", "Opt_2_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to perceive"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The village system made it almost impossible to ____ the amount of land available for pasture.", "Opt_1": "praise", "Opt_2": "enlarge", "Opt_3": "base", "Opt_4": "avoid", "Answer": "enlarge", "Opt_1_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_2_def": "to make larger", "Opt_3_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something or go somewhere"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "What is the ____ between continental and oceanic volcanic eruptions?", "Opt_1": "stage", "Opt_2": "comparison", "Opt_3": "shortage", "Opt_4": "surplus", "Answer": "comparison", "Opt_1_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_3_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_4_def": "to be, go or make all the way around"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "They further alleged that the removal of the soil would ____ the quality of the district's drinking water.", "Opt_1": "disturb", "Opt_2": "subsidize", "Opt_3": "displace", "Opt_4": "implement", "Answer": "disturb", "Opt_1_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_2_def": "to support financially", "Opt_3_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you decide to apply, you will need to ____ a full application including: cover sheet, goals and plan letter, and project statement.", "Opt_1": "dispose", "Opt_2": "reflect", "Opt_3": "compile", "Opt_4": "permit", "Answer": "compile", "Opt_1_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_2_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_3_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_4_def": "to allow"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Let us hope that the new government does not repeat the mistakes of the ____ one.", "Opt_1": "previous", "Opt_2": "immense", "Opt_3": "widespread", "Opt_4": "several", "Answer": "previous", "Opt_1_def": "the one before", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "common", "Opt_4_def": "many (about 6 or seven)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "One ____ of the internet that concerns many parents and teachers is that a huge amount of very offensive material is just a click away.", "Opt_1": "course", "Opt_2": "labour", "Opt_3": "feature", "Opt_4": "prospect", "Answer": "feature", "Opt_1_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_2_def": "work", "Opt_3_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_4_def": "chance, likelihood"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "These ____ and assessment strategies meet the needs of learners who are diverse (e.g., in culture, ethnicity, race, language, special needs).", "Opt_1": "habit", "Opt_2": "policy", "Opt_3": "instruction", "Opt_4": "obstacle", "Answer": "instruction", "Opt_1_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_2_def": "formal rules", "Opt_3_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_4_def": "barrier; problem"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The problem for France was that the population did not ____ of responsible citizens which were necessary for the desired liberal system.", "Opt_1": "imply", "Opt_2": "commit", "Opt_3": "consist", "Opt_4": "accumulate", "Answer": "consist", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_2_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_3_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_4_def": "to grow; to gather together"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The final ____ of rebuilding the school will be finished by the end of the vacation.", "Opt_1": "phase", "Opt_2": "lack", "Opt_3": "obligation", "Opt_4": "labour", "Answer": "phase", "Opt_1_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_2_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_3_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_4_def": "work"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Through much of the War, the U.S. and its Allies could not enforce a fully effective blockade ____ Germany.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Employees' levels of ____ motivation will decrease if they feel they are being controlled by their employers through extrinsic rewards.", "Opt_1": "sound", "Opt_2": "subsequent", "Opt_3": "consistent", "Opt_4": "intrinsic", "Answer": "intrinsic", "Opt_1_def": "good; strong", "Opt_2_def": "next, following", "Opt_3_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_4_def": "belonging to; inherent in"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is advisable that you put your name on these waiting lists ____ to your arrival.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Aschoff's trip failed because he was unable to defend his concept against the competitive ____ favored by German and Russian scientists.", "Opt_1": "highlight", "Opt_2": "approach", "Opt_3": "ensure", "Opt_4": "view", "Answer": "approach", "Opt_1_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_2_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_3_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_4_def": "to have an opinion"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A three-year Indian bachelor's degree is NOT ____ to a U.S. bachelor's degree.", "Opt_1": "regular", "Opt_2": "certain", "Opt_3": "equivalent", "Opt_4": "urban", "Answer": "equivalent", "Opt_1_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_2_def": "sure", "Opt_3_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_4_def": "of the town or city"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The company's ____ for the year was to expand sales by \ufffd\ufffd2 million. Now they expect to exceed this figure by 40%.", "Opt_1": "diagram", "Opt_2": "target", "Opt_3": "effort", "Opt_4": "extract", "Answer": "target", "Opt_1_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_2_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_3_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_4_def": "to remove; to take out and use"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The government does not ____ its citizens an explanation for every decision it makes.", "Opt_1": "owe", "Opt_2": "adjust", "Opt_3": "postpone", "Opt_4": "trust", "Answer": "owe", "Opt_1_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_3_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_4_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The doctor had to ____ the x-rays carefully to find any signs of abnormality.", "Opt_1": "terminate", "Opt_2": "inspect", "Opt_3": "refute", "Opt_4": "prepare", "Answer": "inspect", "Opt_1_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_4_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "One of the most common laments we hear from instructor is that they can't get their students to undertake ____ revisions.", "Opt_1": "substantial", "Opt_2": "superficial", "Opt_3": "evident", "Opt_4": "legal", "Answer": "substantial", "Opt_1_def": "large", "Opt_2_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_3_def": "clear", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Teenage alcohol abuse is an ____ problem in some UK cities.", "Opt_1": "explicit", "Opt_2": "enormous", "Opt_3": "steady", "Opt_4": "ambiguous", "Answer": "enormous", "Opt_1_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_2_def": "very big", "Opt_3_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_4_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "In decimal notation we ____ a negative number by writing a minus in front of a positive number.", "Opt_1": "decrease", "Opt_2": "represent", "Opt_3": "coordinate", "Opt_4": "neglect", "Answer": "represent", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_3_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_4_def": "to not think about or care for"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In this particular poem, Dalton, while asking what woman's ____ is, also advises man on woman's potential and her proper place in life.", "Opt_1": "contract", "Opt_2": "labour", "Opt_3": "version", "Opt_4": "sphere", "Answer": "sphere", "Opt_1_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_2_def": "work", "Opt_3_def": "form", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Some scientists claim that we cannot infer ____ warming on the basis of a just few years of hot weather.", "Opt_1": "distinct", "Opt_2": "urgent", "Opt_3": "superficial", "Opt_4": "global", "Answer": "global", "Opt_1_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_2_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_3_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_4_def": "world"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We designed an ____ to acquire blood from embryonic rats.", "Opt_1": "assent", "Opt_2": "assignment", "Opt_3": "member", "Opt_4": "experiment", "Answer": "experiment", "Opt_1_def": "agreement", "Opt_2_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_4_def": "test"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "My ____ to work every day takes me past my old school.", "Opt_1": "propensity", "Opt_2": "component", "Opt_3": "route", "Opt_4": "volume", "Answer": "route", "Opt_1_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_2_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_3_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government is thinking of passing a law that will require all house owners to ____ their oil heating system for one that runs on gas.", "Opt_1": "compel", "Opt_2": "exchange", "Opt_3": "transmit", "Opt_4": "interrupt", "Answer": "exchange", "Opt_1_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_2_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_3_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_4_def": "to stop something from happening"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ cause of the accident is that the driver fell asleep, but police are investigating the possibility of a terrorist attack.", "Opt_1": "probable", "Opt_2": "deliberate", "Opt_3": "poor", "Opt_4": "ultimate", "Answer": "probable", "Opt_1_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_2_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_3_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_4_def": "final or most important"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He told the members that he quickly called for a car and telephoned the White House to set up an urgent meeting in order to ____ what he had just learned.", "Opt_1": "generate", "Opt_2": "differentiate", "Opt_3": "share", "Opt_4": "train", "Answer": "share", "Opt_1_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_2_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_4_def": "to teach someone how to do a job"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Doctors are advising older patients to have an injection as a ____ against influenza this winter.", "Opt_1": "event", "Opt_2": "precaution", "Opt_3": "labour", "Opt_4": "programme", "Answer": "precaution", "Opt_1_def": "a happening", "Opt_2_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_3_def": "work", "Opt_4_def": "a course of lessons; a project"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The employees are ____ opposed to the management's plans to increase working hours.", "Opt_1": "namely", "Opt_2": "absolutely", "Opt_3": "fairly", "Opt_4": "conversely", "Answer": "absolutely", "Opt_1_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_2_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_3_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_4_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The word 'gay' did not come to ____ 'homosexual' until quite recently.", "Opt_1": "precede", "Opt_2": "diverge", "Opt_3": "degenerate", "Opt_4": "denote", "Answer": "denote", "Opt_1_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to be a sign of"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "She has no ____ of studying in peace at home. Her domestic life is too chaotic.", "Opt_1": "statement", "Opt_2": "mixture", "Opt_3": "issue", "Opt_4": "means", "Answer": "means", "Opt_1_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_2_def": "combination", "Opt_3_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_4_def": "way"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There is really no ____ in arguing which approach is better.", "Opt_1": "point", "Opt_2": "technique", "Opt_3": "surface", "Opt_4": "structure", "Answer": "point", "Opt_1_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_4_def": "the way something is made or organized"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "His idea is simply not ____ - no one is going to pay that kind of money.", "Opt_1": "numerous", "Opt_2": "feasible", "Opt_3": "intense", "Opt_4": "tough", "Answer": "feasible", "Opt_1_def": "very many", "Opt_2_def": "possible", "Opt_3_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, strong"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Carla Santos, a professor of leisure studies, says our perception of another culture is ____ shaped by accounts of travel writers, who tend to perpetuate cultural stereotypes.", "Opt_1": "harsh", "Opt_2": "likely", "Opt_3": "elaborate", "Opt_4": "immediate", "Answer": "likely", "Opt_1_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_2_def": "probable", "Opt_3_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_4_def": "first (without delay)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Most scientists are more interested in the ____ of winning the Nobel Prize than the money they get for doing so.", "Opt_1": "prestige", "Opt_2": "cause", "Opt_3": "bias", "Opt_4": "asset", "Answer": "prestige", "Opt_1_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_2_def": "the reason why something happens", "Opt_3_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_4_def": "advantage"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Lucy has been formed by the West Indies; she still is deeply influenced, yet she would resist and ____ that heritage.", "Opt_1": "request", "Opt_2": "reject", "Opt_3": "retain", "Opt_4": "resign", "Answer": "reject", "Opt_1_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_2_def": "to refuse", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to give up (one's job)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Next you need to formulate a search statement so you can ____ a database search.", "Opt_1": "harm", "Opt_2": "appeal", "Opt_3": "denote", "Opt_4": "conduct", "Answer": "conduct", "Opt_1_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_2_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to do or perform; to behave"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In those days it was not ____ that the brain operates on the information it receives, transforming it in such a way as to make it more useful.", "Opt_1": "obvious", "Opt_2": "perpetual", "Opt_3": "identical", "Opt_4": "proper", "Answer": "obvious", "Opt_1_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_2_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_3_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_4_def": "correct, appropriate"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Mobile phones have made it ____ to contact someone anytime and anywhere.", "Opt_1": "contemporary", "Opt_2": "instant", "Opt_3": "several", "Opt_4": "feasible", "Answer": "feasible", "Opt_1_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_2_def": "immediate", "Opt_3_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_4_def": "possible"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It seems probable that precise measurements of the ratio of positive to negative responses will help to decide between the ____ processes.", "Opt_1": "temporary", "Opt_2": "relevant", "Opt_3": "several", "Opt_4": "arbitrary", "Answer": "several", "Opt_1_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_2_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_3_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_4_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "People have been trying for decades or maybe even centuries in an attempt to bring this ____ problem to an end.", "Opt_1": "local", "Opt_2": "immense", "Opt_3": "abstract", "Opt_4": "considerable", "Answer": "immense", "Opt_1_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_4_def": "very big; very much"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government had to ____ that it had not succeeded in its plans to reduce child poverty.", "Opt_1": "trust", "Opt_2": "found", "Opt_3": "acknowledge", "Opt_4": "blame", "Answer": "acknowledge", "Opt_1_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_2_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_3_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_4_def": "to accuse"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Sitting too long in front of a computer may ____ headaches or back problems.", "Opt_1": "transmit", "Opt_2": "override", "Opt_3": "attempt", "Opt_4": "induce", "Answer": "induce", "Opt_1_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_2_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_3_def": "to try", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen; to force"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you wish to remain at this school, you will have to ____ to its rules.", "Opt_1": "disrupt", "Opt_2": "conform", "Opt_3": "submit", "Opt_4": "allocate", "Answer": "conform", "Opt_1_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_2_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_3_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_4_def": "to give to (to promise to give)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The political system must not be allowed to ____ into unlimited majority rule, which could result in the erosion of individual liberty.", "Opt_1": "advocate", "Opt_2": "justify", "Opt_3": "disturb", "Opt_4": "degenerate", "Answer": "degenerate", "Opt_1_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_4_def": "to get worse"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Discussion and analysis in this area has covered a number of ____ issues, including the effect of shifting trade patterns on employment levels.", "Opt_1": "wise", "Opt_2": "positive", "Opt_3": "prompt", "Opt_4": "discrete", "Answer": "discrete", "Opt_1_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_2_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_3_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_4_def": "separate"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You can be ____ certain what you read at the government site is accurate and up-to-date.", "Opt_1": "fairly", "Opt_2": "especially", "Opt_3": "conversely", "Opt_4": "thus", "Answer": "fairly", "Opt_1_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_2_def": "particularly", "Opt_3_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_4_def": "so"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The principle behind this policy is that the rights of the individuals should be respected; subjects must ____ to participation in research.", "Opt_1": "reserve", "Opt_2": "subsidize", "Opt_3": "consent", "Opt_4": "investigate", "Answer": "consent", "Opt_1_def": "to keep", "Opt_2_def": "to support financially", "Opt_3_def": "to agree", "Opt_4_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It was a time when priests were experiencing financial crisis and the Church was unable to ____ many of their expenses.", "Opt_1": "distort", "Opt_2": "subsidize", "Opt_3": "retire", "Opt_4": "migrate", "Answer": "subsidize", "Opt_1_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_2_def": "to support financially", "Opt_3_def": "to stop working", "Opt_4_def": "to go to another place"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Most people who use a wheelchair or mobility devices do not ____ them as confining. They are viewed as liberating; a means of getting around.", "Opt_1": "require", "Opt_2": "inhibit", "Opt_3": "belong", "Opt_4": "regard", "Answer": "regard", "Opt_1_def": "to need", "Opt_2_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_3_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_4_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "For reasons that are not yet completely clear, practice and ____ usually diverge at this point.", "Opt_1": "state", "Opt_2": "theory", "Opt_3": "interior", "Opt_4": "display", "Answer": "theory", "Opt_1_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_2_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_3_def": "inside", "Opt_4_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Your final course grade will ____ on your grades in the 3 trimester exams.", "Opt_1": "culminate", "Opt_2": "depend", "Opt_3": "appoint", "Opt_4": "convince", "Answer": "depend", "Opt_1_def": "to end", "Opt_2_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_3_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_4_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Photoshop provides you with techniques used to ____ the quality of graphics and photographs.", "Opt_1": "prohibit", "Opt_2": "force", "Opt_3": "correlate", "Opt_4": "adjust", "Answer": "adjust", "Opt_1_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_2_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_3_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Every year in Germany many people lose all their ____ when their houses burn down in a fire.", "Opt_1": "bond", "Opt_2": "quantity", "Opt_3": "defeat", "Opt_4": "property", "Answer": "property", "Opt_1_def": "link; tie", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_4_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Over the course of her journey in the program she has come a great ____ from her primary focus as an agent for FEMA.", "Opt_1": "distance", "Opt_2": "treatment", "Opt_3": "detriment", "Opt_4": "standard", "Answer": "distance", "Opt_1_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_2_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_4_def": "quality"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is not always possible to distinguish a cause of a ____ from a consequence of that ____.", "Opt_1": "course", "Opt_2": "resident", "Opt_3": "forecast", "Opt_4": "conflict", "Answer": "conflict", "Opt_1_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_2_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_3_def": "prediction", "Opt_4_def": "problem, struggle or battle"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The first of the allegations came from a woman who, in the opinion of the Committee, was not a ____ witness.", "Opt_1": "cautious", "Opt_2": "several", "Opt_3": "credible", "Opt_4": "numerous", "Answer": "credible", "Opt_1_def": "careful", "Opt_2_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_3_def": "believable", "Opt_4_def": "very many"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "These orders do much to ____ the significant need for better organization in terms of record-keeping.", "Opt_1": "express", "Opt_2": "illustrate", "Opt_3": "revise", "Opt_4": "complicate", "Answer": "illustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_2_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_3_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_4_def": "to make things more complex or difficult"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "These two-word verbs present one other problem, ____ not appearing as separate entries in the dictionary.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Can you ____ these dollars to Yen for me?", "Opt_1": "respect", "Opt_2": "convert", "Opt_3": "consume", "Opt_4": "extend", "Answer": "convert", "Opt_1_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_2_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_3_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_4_def": "to make longer in time or space"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "How can I ____ access to my Web pages?", "Opt_1": "restrict", "Opt_2": "succeed", "Opt_3": "criticize", "Opt_4": "protect", "Answer": "restrict", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to do well", "Opt_3_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to keep something out of danger"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is often necessary to revise a mathematical model several times in the course of an ____ operations research study.", "Opt_1": "latter", "Opt_2": "efficient", "Opt_3": "related", "Opt_4": "urban", "Answer": "urban", "Opt_1_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_2_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_3_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_4_def": "of the town or city"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The bottom of the Pacific Ocean is the most ____ region on Earth.", "Opt_1": "vital", "Opt_2": "substantial", "Opt_3": "remote", "Opt_4": "invisible", "Answer": "remote", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "large", "Opt_3_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be seen"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We are often right on the ____ of warm and cold or moist and dry air masses. So we get some very difficult weather conditions to try to forecast.", "Opt_1": "motive", "Opt_2": "truth", "Opt_3": "boundary", "Opt_4": "image", "Answer": "boundary", "Opt_1_def": "reason", "Opt_2_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_3_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_4_def": "picture"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It was the result of his labour that Brazil could ____ scientific institutions.", "Opt_1": "violate", "Opt_2": "ruin", "Opt_3": "afford", "Opt_4": "rotate", "Answer": "afford", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_3_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_4_def": "to turn or move (around)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In a ____ between the school and the parents, it is usually the school that will prevail.", "Opt_1": "benefit", "Opt_2": "dispute", "Opt_3": "argument", "Opt_4": "dimension", "Answer": "dispute", "Opt_1_def": "advantage", "Opt_2_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_3_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_4_def": "importance; amount"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Importantly, he ____ that the Wabash River population appears to be stable.", "Opt_1": "refer", "Opt_2": "postpone", "Opt_3": "condemn", "Opt_4": "found", "Answer": "found", "Opt_1_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_2_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_3_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "to begin (often an organization)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If you choose not to participate or to ____ from the study at any time, there will be no penalty.", "Opt_1": "govern", "Opt_2": "affect", "Opt_3": "withdraw", "Opt_4": "repeat", "Answer": "withdraw", "Opt_1_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_2_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_3_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_4_def": "to do or say again"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There is a ____ of toilets in the school. Every time I want to use one, it is occupied.", "Opt_1": "progress", "Opt_2": "shortage", "Opt_3": "scope", "Opt_4": "assignment", "Answer": "shortage", "Opt_1_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_2_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_3_def": "extent, range", "Opt_4_def": "a task; the giving of a task"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Mild pain and inflammation can often ____ an otherwise rewarding day of skiing.", "Opt_1": "attract", "Opt_2": "ruin", "Opt_3": "retire", "Opt_4": "trade", "Answer": "ruin", "Opt_1_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_3_def": "to stop working", "Opt_4_def": "to exchange products or services"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Discussion and analysis in this area has covered a number of ____ issues, including the effect of shifting trade patterns on employment levels.", "Opt_1": "discrete", "Opt_2": "harsh", "Opt_3": "confident", "Opt_4": "basic", "Answer": "discrete", "Opt_1_def": "separate", "Opt_2_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_3_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_4_def": "first or easy"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If you can ____ the problems you had with your last history project, I will be able to help you better with your current one.", "Opt_1": "commence", "Opt_2": "specify", "Opt_3": "participate", "Opt_4": "negotiate", "Answer": "specify", "Opt_1_def": "to start", "Opt_2_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_3_def": "to take part", "Opt_4_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "They knew the ____ was inappropriate, but they were not sure how to react.", "Opt_1": "pressure", "Opt_2": "phrase", "Opt_3": "privilege", "Opt_4": "image", "Answer": "phrase", "Opt_1_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_2_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_3_def": "a right (to do something)", "Opt_4_def": "picture"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Above all, World War II was an episode of American history in which more American people bonded together in a ____ cause than ever before or ever since.", "Opt_1": "explicit", "Opt_2": "common", "Opt_3": "competent", "Opt_4": "thorough", "Answer": "common", "Opt_1_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_2_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_3_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_4_def": "complete and careful"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If the student is determined to be independent of their parents, the student must be a ____ of Indiana since at least December 31 of the previous year.", "Opt_1": "obstacle", "Opt_2": "magnitude", "Opt_3": "resident", "Opt_4": "mechanism", "Answer": "resident", "Opt_1_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_2_def": "size; amount", "Opt_3_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_4_def": "procedure, process"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If authors realize there is a significant ____ in a published paper, they may correct their paper by submitting a short correction notice.", "Opt_1": "error", "Opt_2": "statement", "Opt_3": "advantage", "Opt_4": "strategy", "Answer": "error", "Opt_1_def": "a mistake", "Opt_2_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_3_def": "benefit", "Opt_4_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The study also ____ that both genders get a similar benefit from the therapy, which reduced mortality risk in women by an estimated 43%.", "Opt_1": "increase", "Opt_2": "lessen", "Opt_3": "abandon", "Opt_4": "found", "Answer": "found", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_2_def": "to reduce", "Opt_3_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_4_def": "to begin (often an organization)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Many Western businesses are finding it difficult to ____ with Asian companies which pay their workers far less money.", "Opt_1": "override", "Opt_2": "compete", "Opt_3": "denote", "Opt_4": "submit", "Answer": "compete", "Opt_1_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_2_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to give; to send"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "While I am not in favor of teaching creationism in public schools, I am also not ____ to having it presented and examined.", "Opt_1": "immense", "Opt_2": "automatic", "Opt_3": "liable", "Opt_4": "averse", "Answer": "averse", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_3_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_4_def": "against"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Our chief problem is how to ____ the governors that we are right.", "Opt_1": "convince", "Opt_2": "trigger", "Opt_3": "condemn", "Opt_4": "presume", "Answer": "convince", "Opt_1_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_2_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_3_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "to believe, assume"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "After massive criticism the government has decided to ____ language courses for immigrants to the country.", "Opt_1": "degenerate", "Opt_2": "restore", "Opt_3": "own", "Opt_4": "amend", "Answer": "restore", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_3_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_4_def": "to change (usually to improve something)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "A very ____ response in real time is needed to record the optical emission while the gamma-ray burst is in progress.", "Opt_1": "final", "Opt_2": "rapid", "Opt_3": "consistent", "Opt_4": "crucial", "Answer": "rapid", "Opt_1_def": "last", "Opt_2_def": "quick", "Opt_3_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_4_def": "extremely important"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Due to the severe shortage of highly trained nursing staff, Hopkins was unable to ____ a full team of qualified personnel.", "Opt_1": "collapse", "Opt_2": "assemble", "Opt_3": "presume", "Opt_4": "allege", "Answer": "assemble", "Opt_1_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_2_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_3_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_4_def": "to claim or state"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ of social work is based on the values of service, social and economic justice, dignity and worth of the person, importance of human relationships, and integrity and competence in practice.", "Opt_1": "volume", "Opt_2": "source", "Opt_3": "criterion", "Opt_4": "profession", "Answer": "profession", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_3_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_4_def": "job; occupation"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The use of this seemingly simple system does not ____ an undeveloped technological ability on the part of 9th century Hindus.", "Opt_1": "neglect", "Opt_2": "deteriorate", "Opt_3": "negotiate", "Opt_4": "denote", "Answer": "denote", "Opt_1_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_2_def": "to get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to be a sign of"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Due to a rapid increase in the number of students the school needs to ____ 4 new teachers.", "Opt_1": "commit", "Opt_2": "prevent", "Opt_3": "allocate", "Opt_4": "appoint", "Answer": "appoint", "Opt_1_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_2_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_3_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Once Windows Movie Maker has opened, you will need to ____ the video clip that you would like to edit.", "Opt_1": "inspect", "Opt_2": "realize", "Opt_3": "fade", "Opt_4": "import", "Answer": "import", "Opt_1_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to come to know or understand", "Opt_3_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_4_def": "to bring in (to a country)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "They are currently involved in a ____ against Occidental Petroleum to save their land and their way of life.", "Opt_1": "hierarchy", "Opt_2": "prospect", "Opt_3": "journey", "Opt_4": "battle", "Answer": "battle", "Opt_1_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_2_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_3_def": "a long trip to a different place", "Opt_4_def": "fight, part of a war"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you try to define something that is ____ the comprehension of your paper or your own experience, the task will become overwhelming.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You have made reasonable ____ in English this trimester.", "Opt_1": "surplus", "Opt_2": "progress", "Opt_3": "topic", "Opt_4": "exhibit", "Answer": "progress", "Opt_1_def": "to be, go or make all the way around", "Opt_2_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_4_def": "to show"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Please remember to ____ any rented vehicle before driving it and note any scratches or other damage to the vehicle on the rental form.", "Opt_1": "implement", "Opt_2": "share", "Opt_3": "amend", "Opt_4": "inspect", "Answer": "inspect", "Opt_1_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_2_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_3_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The difficulties that ____ from time to time in the business can be solved by good management.", "Opt_1": "absorb", "Opt_2": "convey", "Opt_3": "promote", "Opt_4": "arise", "Answer": "arise", "Opt_1_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_2_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_3_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_4_def": "to happen"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Students who are awarded an International Student Scholarship must ____ the following requirements each semester in order to continue receiving this award.", "Opt_1": "construct", "Opt_2": "tend", "Opt_3": "contain", "Opt_4": "fulfill", "Answer": "fulfill", "Opt_1_def": "to make", "Opt_2_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_3_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_4_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Luckily, ____ to total coincidence, the men's and women's basketball teams started most of their games on the road.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "although"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Once the conference is over the government will turn its attention to the problems of ____ crime.", "Opt_1": "urban", "Opt_2": "frequent", "Opt_3": "dense", "Opt_4": "urgent", "Answer": "urban", "Opt_1_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_2_def": "often", "Opt_3_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_4_def": "very important, must be done immediately"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "He questioned the security coordination that enabled the terrorists to ____ all their preparatory work. The authorities had failed to surround the school for three days.", "Opt_1": "convert", "Opt_2": "neglect", "Opt_3": "devise", "Opt_4": "accomplish", "Answer": "accomplish", "Opt_1_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_2_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_3_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_4_def": "to do or achieve"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Children ____ in classes where their teachers care about each of them as individuals.", "Opt_1": "prosper", "Opt_2": "conduct", "Opt_3": "suggest", "Opt_4": "adhere", "Answer": "prosper", "Opt_1_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_2_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_3_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_4_def": "to keep to; to follow"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Court asserted that education was perhaps the most significant ____ of state and local governments.", "Opt_1": "technique", "Opt_2": "function", "Opt_3": "term", "Opt_4": "duration", "Answer": "function", "Opt_1_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "job or role", "Opt_3_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some parents do not ____ how difficult it is to provide an education that will meet the needs of all students.", "Opt_1": "appreciate", "Opt_2": "ensure", "Opt_3": "cease", "Opt_4": "disturb", "Answer": "appreciate", "Opt_1_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_3_def": "to stop", "Opt_4_def": "to interrupt, stop from working"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "What is absent in your essay is any reference to the ____ of your ideas.", "Opt_1": "target", "Opt_2": "hypothesis", "Opt_3": "source", "Opt_4": "directions", "Answer": "source", "Opt_1_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_2_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_3_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_4_def": "instructions"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government received information but did not consider it ____ and therefore decided to ignore it.", "Opt_1": "current", "Opt_2": "massive", "Opt_3": "elementary", "Opt_4": "reliable", "Answer": "reliable", "Opt_1_def": "happening now", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "easy", "Opt_4_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Nowadays nobody attempts to ____ that smoking is bad for the health.", "Opt_1": "frustrate", "Opt_2": "refute", "Opt_3": "announce", "Opt_4": "discern", "Answer": "refute", "Opt_1_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_2_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_3_def": "to state (often in an official way)", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to perceive"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The continued presence of a huge ____ force in the Gulf area provides the necessary element of pressure to ensure implementation of obligations.", "Opt_1": "wise", "Opt_2": "military", "Opt_3": "elementary", "Opt_4": "spontaneous", "Answer": "military", "Opt_1_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_2_def": "to do with army", "Opt_3_def": "easy", "Opt_4_def": "happening without warning or planning"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Students engaging in scheduled curricular work have ____ over other students.", "Opt_1": "decade", "Opt_2": "priority", "Opt_3": "facilities", "Opt_4": "theory", "Answer": "priority", "Opt_1_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_2_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_3_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_4_def": "idea or hypothesis"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The strategy failed to ____ workers themselves to consider domestic service as anything other than a temporary transition.", "Opt_1": "deviate", "Opt_2": "resist", "Opt_3": "claim", "Opt_4": "persuade", "Answer": "persuade", "Opt_1_def": "to be different", "Opt_2_def": "to fight against", "Opt_3_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_4_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you fail the last test, this will seriously ____ your overall grade for the year.", "Opt_1": "provoke", "Opt_2": "affect", "Opt_3": "view", "Opt_4": "circulate", "Answer": "affect", "Opt_1_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_3_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ was not visible in its entirety on the computer screen.", "Opt_1": "shift", "Opt_2": "passage", "Opt_3": "region", "Opt_4": "mixture", "Answer": "passage", "Opt_1_def": "change", "Opt_2_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_3_def": "part of a place", "Opt_4_def": "combination"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Since most employers spend less than a minute scanning a resume, it is necessary to be brief and to ____ all that is important.", "Opt_1": "diverge", "Opt_2": "edit", "Opt_3": "highlight", "Opt_4": "associate", "Answer": "highlight", "Opt_1_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_2_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_4_def": "to link to; to make a connection to"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The doctor examined the patient carefully, ____ that he forgot to check blood pressure.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you are interested in checking out any of the books in the ____ case, please inquire at Circulation.", "Opt_1": "display", "Opt_2": "assent", "Opt_3": "magnitude", "Opt_4": "defeat", "Answer": "display", "Opt_1_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_2_def": "agreement", "Opt_3_def": "size; amount", "Opt_4_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "He told reporters that he did not want to ____ in the dispute over the prime minister.", "Opt_1": "edit", "Opt_2": "organize", "Opt_3": "detect", "Opt_4": "intervene", "Answer": "intervene", "Opt_1_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_3_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_4_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If authors realize there is a significant ____ in a published paper, they may correct their paper by submitting a short correction notice.", "Opt_1": "error", "Opt_2": "format", "Opt_3": "occasion", "Opt_4": "mixture", "Answer": "error", "Opt_1_def": "a mistake", "Opt_2_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_3_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_4_def": "combination"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If you are ____ and flexible, enjoy solving tasks independently and are committed to achieving outstanding performance, then this is the job for you.", "Opt_1": "reliable", "Opt_2": "credible", "Opt_3": "preliminary", "Opt_4": "obsolete", "Answer": "reliable", "Opt_1_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_2_def": "believable", "Opt_3_def": "first; initial", "Opt_4_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "While most people know that chest pain can signify the presence of heart disease, it is less well known that shortness of breath can also be a ____ cardiac symptom.", "Opt_1": "prime", "Opt_2": "obsolete", "Opt_3": "serious", "Opt_4": "preliminary", "Answer": "serious", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_3_def": "severe, large", "Opt_4_def": "first; initial"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You will analyze recurrent patterns of international political conflict, identify underlying issues, and ____ alternative resolutions.", "Opt_1": "negotiate", "Opt_2": "unite", "Opt_3": "consult", "Opt_4": "suggest", "Answer": "suggest", "Opt_1_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_4_def": "to say an idea; to recommend"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She discussed the schedule for implementing the system through April 2003 and outlined ____ potential advantages of the system.", "Opt_1": "numerous", "Opt_2": "adjacent", "Opt_3": "wise", "Opt_4": "several", "Answer": "several", "Opt_1_def": "very many", "Opt_2_def": "next to", "Opt_3_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_4_def": "many (about 6 or seven)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Teachers and parents can learn and share ideas for helping to work for more successful outcomes in the ____ from school to adult life.", "Opt_1": "career", "Opt_2": "transition", "Opt_3": "evidence", "Opt_4": "extract", "Answer": "transition", "Opt_1_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_2_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_3_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_4_def": "to remove; to take out and use"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Doctors are advising older patients to have an injection as a ____ against influenza this winter.", "Opt_1": "defeat", "Opt_2": "symbol", "Opt_3": "materials", "Opt_4": "precaution", "Answer": "precaution", "Opt_1_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_2_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_4_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Please note that section 5 is the most important, and ____ it should constitute the majority of your journal entry.", "Opt_1": "universally", "Opt_2": "hence", "Opt_3": "therefore", "Opt_4": "recently", "Answer": "hence", "Opt_1_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_2_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_3_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_4_def": "in the near past"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ goal of teaching is to teach students how to teach themselves.", "Opt_1": "ultimate", "Opt_2": "external", "Opt_3": "legitimate", "Opt_4": "ambiguous", "Answer": "ultimate", "Opt_1_def": "final or most important", "Opt_2_def": "outside", "Opt_3_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_4_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The Institute must take greater measures to ____ students that they need not fear consequences when seeking medical help for substance abuse.", "Opt_1": "decline", "Opt_2": "assure", "Opt_3": "communicate", "Opt_4": "ruin", "Answer": "assure", "Opt_1_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_3_def": "to convey information", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or damage"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The numbers of overweight and obese children worldwide are expected to climb ____ by 2010.", "Opt_1": "rather", "Opt_2": "roughly", "Opt_3": "dramatically", "Opt_4": "recently", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "instead", "Opt_2_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_3_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_4_def": "in the near past"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "When the models ____ the effects of pollution, they predict that rainfall will decrease even more in the next few decades.", "Opt_1": "praise", "Opt_2": "incorporate", "Opt_3": "conclude", "Opt_4": "persuade", "Answer": "incorporate", "Opt_1_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_2_def": "to include", "Opt_3_def": "to finish; to make a judgment", "Opt_4_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Class data will be collected to compare perceived overweight and attempt at dieting with ____ weight risk classification.", "Opt_1": "outstanding", "Opt_2": "genuine", "Opt_3": "actual", "Opt_4": "accurate", "Answer": "actual", "Opt_1_def": "excellent", "Opt_2_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_3_def": "real", "Opt_4_def": "exact, containing no mistakes"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The administrative ____ will inform the student supervisor when a student has failed to provide required documents and other information.", "Opt_1": "balance", "Opt_2": "staff", "Opt_3": "proportion", "Opt_4": "institution", "Answer": "staff", "Opt_1_def": "equalness", "Opt_2_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_3_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_4_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A nursing or household robot must be ____ in order to reach a variety of working sites within the house.", "Opt_1": "stable", "Opt_2": "global", "Opt_3": "mobile", "Opt_4": "genuine", "Answer": "mobile", "Opt_1_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_2_def": "world", "Opt_3_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_4_def": "real and authentic"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A negative ____ toward yourself as a writer can make you anxious and lead you to \"block.\"", "Opt_1": "attitude", "Opt_2": "detriment", "Opt_3": "error", "Opt_4": "minimum", "Answer": "attitude", "Opt_1_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_2_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_3_def": "a mistake", "Opt_4_def": "the smallest amount; the least"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Musicians are listed alphabetically, but for some ____ reason Carter, Benny is listed after Carter, Ron.", "Opt_1": "odd", "Opt_2": "annual", "Opt_3": "several", "Opt_4": "wise", "Answer": "odd", "Opt_1_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "yearly", "Opt_3_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_4_def": "intelligent; sensible"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Game reasoning is simply moral reasoning that occurs in the ____ of competitive sports, and perhaps elsewhere as well.", "Opt_1": "context", "Opt_2": "property", "Opt_3": "gain", "Opt_4": "sequence", "Answer": "context", "Opt_1_def": "the place or situation in which something is found", "Opt_2_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_3_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_4_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ____ of this study was to explore the internal and external factors influencing the career development of first generation Filipina Americans.", "Opt_1": "impulse", "Opt_2": "purpose", "Opt_3": "dispute", "Opt_4": "authority", "Answer": "purpose", "Opt_1_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_2_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_3_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_4_def": "control (right to control)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Before doing a longer piece of writing it is usually a good idea to make an outline to ____ your main ideas.", "Opt_1": "introduce", "Opt_2": "organize", "Opt_3": "adapt", "Opt_4": "inspect", "Answer": "organize", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_2_def": "to put into (its proper) place", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Consequently, the percentages will not sum to 100% because many students were ____ on the questions in the survey.", "Opt_1": "neutral", "Opt_2": "elaborate", "Opt_3": "official", "Opt_4": "current", "Answer": "neutral", "Opt_1_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_2_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_3_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_4_def": "happening now"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I am no expert in animal behavior, but anyone with even a ____ knowledge of the field must be impressed with their complex forms of social behavior.", "Opt_1": "thorough", "Opt_2": "slight", "Opt_3": "mobile", "Opt_4": "consistent", "Answer": "slight", "Opt_1_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_2_def": "small", "Opt_3_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_4_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ to a new school in a new country is a difficult one for most students.", "Opt_1": "factor", "Opt_2": "transition", "Opt_3": "controversy", "Opt_4": "trait", "Answer": "transition", "Opt_1_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_2_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_3_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_4_def": "characteristic; aspect"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is an opportunity to ____ a more demanding curriculum while having an equal opportunity to share in the full benefits of university life.", "Opt_1": "declare", "Opt_2": "pursue", "Opt_3": "publish", "Opt_4": "spread", "Answer": "pursue", "Opt_1_def": "to state", "Opt_2_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_3_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_4_def": "to move (over a wider area)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Spending months at a time in orbit, the scientists will be able to observe changes on the earth ____ them from day to day.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "before"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Discussion and analysis in this area has covered a number of discrete issues, including the ____ of shifting trade patterns on employment levels.", "Opt_1": "effect", "Opt_2": "gap", "Opt_3": "means", "Opt_4": "lack", "Answer": "effect", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_3_def": "way", "Opt_4_def": "absence of a thing"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The public are ____ satisfied with the government's performance.", "Opt_1": "perhaps", "Opt_2": "largely", "Opt_3": "rather", "Opt_4": "simultaneously", "Answer": "largely", "Opt_1_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "instead", "Opt_4_def": "at the same time"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The campus will be closed ____ for needed emergency services and essential work.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Rubin did not suffer ____ but learned to use anger and pride to fight for what was right.", "Opt_1": "defeat", "Opt_2": "procedure", "Opt_3": "statistic", "Opt_4": "credit", "Answer": "defeat", "Opt_1_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_2_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_4_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The purpose of the study is to examine the hypothesis that ____ life is more stressful than rural life.", "Opt_1": "local", "Opt_2": "smooth", "Opt_3": "superior", "Opt_4": "urban", "Answer": "urban", "Opt_1_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_2_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_3_def": "better", "Opt_4_def": "of the town or city"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ was for travel volume to increase by 1 percent to 2 percent compared to last year.", "Opt_1": "duty", "Opt_2": "penalty", "Opt_3": "outcome", "Opt_4": "forecast", "Answer": "forecast", "Opt_1_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_2_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "prediction"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A student who is in debt to the University at the end of any academic ____ shall not be permitted to register in the University again.", "Opt_1": "term", "Opt_2": "citizen", "Opt_3": "experiment", "Opt_4": "prejudice", "Answer": "term", "Opt_1_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_2_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_3_def": "test", "Opt_4_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The United Mine Workers was the recognized bargaining ____ for the coal miners in Illinois, Indiana, Ohio, and Pennsylvania.", "Opt_1": "manner", "Opt_2": "programme", "Opt_3": "agent", "Opt_4": "code", "Answer": "agent", "Opt_1_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_4_def": "a set of rules"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Television and the other news media have helped to ____ the person and the institution of the presidency.", "Opt_1": "fail", "Opt_2": "advance", "Opt_3": "magnify", "Opt_4": "convey", "Answer": "magnify", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_2_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_3_def": "to make or show larger", "Opt_4_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We can separate white light into its component colors with a prism and use an ____ prism to recombine the light.", "Opt_1": "identical", "Opt_2": "spare", "Opt_3": "artificial", "Opt_4": "certain", "Answer": "identical", "Opt_1_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_2_def": "not needed", "Opt_3_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_4_def": "sure"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A ____ problem for most western societies is how to integrate immigrants with different cultures and religious beliefs.", "Opt_1": "major", "Opt_2": "cautious", "Opt_3": "official", "Opt_4": "urgent", "Answer": "major", "Opt_1_def": "important, large", "Opt_2_def": "careful", "Opt_3_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_4_def": "very important, must be done immediately"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It's too easy to ____ all of the country's problems on the government.", "Opt_1": "migrate", "Opt_2": "blame", "Opt_3": "signify", "Opt_4": "exploit", "Answer": "blame", "Opt_1_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_2_def": "to accuse", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you are going on the field trip, do not forget to ____ if you need a special diet.", "Opt_1": "fail", "Opt_2": "diminish", "Opt_3": "mention", "Opt_4": "assess", "Answer": "mention", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_3_def": "to say; state", "Opt_4_def": "to judge or test"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "She thinks that the homeless children probably will ____ more poorly, educationally, than the children who come from homes.", "Opt_1": "assimilate", "Opt_2": "address", "Opt_3": "fare", "Opt_4": "discover", "Answer": "fare", "Opt_1_def": "to take in", "Opt_2_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_3_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_4_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The company made a ____ reduction in its workforce in order to improve its performance in the second part of the financial year.", "Opt_1": "vital", "Opt_2": "vast", "Opt_3": "radical", "Opt_4": "numerous", "Answer": "radical", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_4_def": "very many"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "What is your attitude to paying higher taxes in ____ that more schools and hospitals can be built?", "Opt_1": "extract", "Opt_2": "order", "Opt_3": "instance", "Opt_4": "progress", "Answer": "order", "Opt_1_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_2_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_3_def": "example", "Opt_4_def": "improvement or development"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "But mine was not a ____ Negro family. My grandmother never took in washing or worked in service or went much to church.", "Opt_1": "explicit", "Opt_2": "typical", "Opt_3": "basic", "Opt_4": "genuine", "Answer": "typical", "Opt_1_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_2_def": "usual", "Opt_3_def": "first or easy", "Opt_4_def": "real and authentic"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You need to ____ a little more on the books that you read. It's not enough to just write what happens.", "Opt_1": "generate", "Opt_2": "reflect", "Opt_3": "emphasize", "Opt_4": "manifest", "Answer": "reflect", "Opt_1_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_2_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_3_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_4_def": "show"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You should be able to ____ the answer if you think carefully enough.", "Opt_1": "embody", "Opt_2": "enumerate", "Opt_3": "protest", "Opt_4": "deduce", "Answer": "deduce", "Opt_1_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to list", "Opt_3_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_4_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "China is, indeed, going through a ____, but it is not a ____ from capitalism to communism.", "Opt_1": "dispute", "Opt_2": "trend", "Opt_3": "transition", "Opt_4": "drawback", "Answer": "transition", "Opt_1_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_2_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage, problem"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ of doctors are hard-working and competent, but there are some who are not.", "Opt_1": "bulk", "Opt_2": "property", "Opt_3": "contrast", "Opt_4": "symbol", "Answer": "bulk", "Opt_1_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_2_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_3_def": "difference", "Opt_4_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The B grade had come to ____ work that was barely acceptable.", "Opt_1": "examine", "Opt_2": "consider", "Opt_3": "transfer", "Opt_4": "signify", "Answer": "signify", "Opt_1_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to think", "Opt_3_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to be a sign of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It isn't the government's ____ if people ignore advice to live healthily.", "Opt_1": "materials", "Opt_2": "fault", "Opt_3": "background", "Opt_4": "penalty", "Answer": "fault", "Opt_1_def": "the things you need to do something", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_3_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "negative consequence; punishment"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Please ____ me a seat at the back of the school bus.", "Opt_1": "reserve", "Opt_2": "seek", "Opt_3": "represent", "Opt_4": "behave", "Answer": "reserve", "Opt_1_def": "to keep", "Opt_2_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_3_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_4_def": "to act or do things in a certain way"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You must ____ at the top of the page how many words you wrote.", "Opt_1": "advance", "Opt_2": "facilitate", "Opt_3": "reward", "Opt_4": "indicate", "Answer": "indicate", "Opt_1_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_3_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "to show or convey"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "One ____ reason for this persistent problem is that Europe is trailing behind the US in labour productivity growth.", "Opt_1": "medium", "Opt_2": "widespread", "Opt_3": "crucial", "Opt_4": "smooth", "Answer": "crucial", "Opt_1_def": "in the middle", "Opt_2_def": "common", "Opt_3_def": "extremely important", "Opt_4_def": "easy, unproblematic"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The museum plans to ____ a collection of late works by Picasso.", "Opt_1": "diagram", "Opt_2": "exhibit", "Opt_3": "source", "Opt_4": "attribute", "Answer": "exhibit", "Opt_1_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_4_def": "characteristic; property"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We will also tell you how the precaution to take if you decide to use email as an ____ means of communication.", "Opt_1": "compulsory", "Opt_2": "legitimate", "Opt_3": "official", "Opt_4": "actual", "Answer": "official", "Opt_1_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_2_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_3_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_4_def": "real"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Niehuss does much to illuminate the enormous ____ of consumer culture on West German women's lives.", "Opt_1": "battle", "Opt_2": "impact", "Opt_3": "limit", "Opt_4": "progress", "Answer": "impact", "Opt_1_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_2_def": "effect", "Opt_3_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_4_def": "improvement or development"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The word 'gay' did not come to ____ 'homosexual' until quite recently.", "Opt_1": "denote", "Opt_2": "prosper", "Opt_3": "emphasize", "Opt_4": "explore", "Answer": "denote", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_2_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_3_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The issue is not only a ____ problem, but must be dealt with on a national level.", "Opt_1": "preliminary", "Opt_2": "local", "Opt_3": "mobile", "Opt_4": "accurate", "Answer": "local", "Opt_1_def": "first; initial", "Opt_2_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_3_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_4_def": "exact, containing no mistakes"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The museum plans to ____ a collection of late works by Picasso.", "Opt_1": "prejudice", "Opt_2": "exhibit", "Opt_3": "balance", "Opt_4": "goal", "Answer": "exhibit", "Opt_1_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "equalness", "Opt_4_def": "aim or intention"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "However, you may also include a citation at a natural breaking point within the sentence, for ____ before a comma or a conjunction.", "Opt_1": "speed", "Opt_2": "bias", "Opt_3": "instance", "Opt_4": "disaster", "Answer": "instance", "Opt_1_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_2_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_3_def": "example", "Opt_4_def": "a huge problem or failure"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Computer hard disk cleaning is not an ____ that many people perform very frequently.", "Opt_1": "interior", "Opt_2": "outline", "Opt_3": "profit", "Opt_4": "operation", "Answer": "operation", "Opt_1_def": "inside", "Opt_2_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_3_def": "money gained", "Opt_4_def": "procedure; happening; process"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The lessons that ____ lunch today are cancelled for a special assembly.", "Opt_1": "precede", "Opt_2": "fade", "Opt_3": "introduce", "Opt_4": "occur", "Answer": "precede", "Opt_1_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_3_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_4_def": "to happen; take place"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In tomorrow's TV broadcast the government will declare its ____ to reduce taxes during its time in office.", "Opt_1": "category", "Opt_2": "phase", "Opt_3": "compensation", "Opt_4": "intention", "Answer": "intention", "Opt_1_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_2_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_3_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_4_def": "plan, aim"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "An important ____ of the course is the unit on grammar.", "Opt_1": "struggle", "Opt_2": "community", "Opt_3": "transition", "Opt_4": "component", "Answer": "component", "Opt_1_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people", "Opt_3_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_4_def": "part of; an element of"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Farmers rotate their crops. This means that they do not grow the same thing on the same ____ for more than one year.", "Opt_1": "operation", "Opt_2": "scope", "Opt_3": "field", "Opt_4": "programme", "Answer": "field", "Opt_1_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_2_def": "extent, range", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_4_def": "a course of lessons; a project"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The administrative staff will ____ the student supervisor when a student has failed to provide required documents and other ____ation.", "Opt_1": "represent", "Opt_2": "inform", "Opt_3": "assert", "Opt_4": "disperse", "Answer": "inform", "Opt_1_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_2_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_3_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_4_def": "to spread out; to move apart"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This has been the ____ of scientists and engineers for many years and has only recently been considered a hot research topic with real business potential.", "Opt_1": "deal", "Opt_2": "layer", "Opt_3": "outline", "Opt_4": "province", "Answer": "province", "Opt_1_def": "agreement", "Opt_2_def": "level", "Opt_3_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_4_def": "area (of interest)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The price of a raw material for a production ____ may be reduced if a sufficiently large quantity is purchased at each inventory replenishment.", "Opt_1": "effort", "Opt_2": "process", "Opt_3": "transition", "Opt_4": "generation", "Answer": "process", "Opt_1_def": "hard work; attempt", "Opt_2_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_3_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_4_def": "group of people all born around the same time"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The company directors made a ____ attempt to save the business by dismissing half the workforce.", "Opt_1": "drastic", "Opt_2": "legitimate", "Opt_3": "practical", "Opt_4": "current", "Answer": "drastic", "Opt_1_def": "severe; great", "Opt_2_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_3_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_4_def": "happening now"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "One study found that anemia was a strong predictor of other serious problems that were not ____ at the time anemia was first detected.", "Opt_1": "fare", "Opt_2": "attend", "Opt_3": "criticize", "Opt_4": "present", "Answer": "present", "Opt_1_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_2_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_3_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The men searched the entire camp, digging ____ the snow and even into the earth, but no paper was found, no diaries and no documents.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This is one of several errors that indicate that your ____ is not set up properly; this can be corrected only by University personnel.", "Opt_1": "situation", "Opt_2": "region", "Opt_3": "account", "Opt_4": "province", "Answer": "account", "Opt_1_def": "circumstances", "Opt_2_def": "part of a place", "Opt_3_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_4_def": "area (of interest)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It was ____ that the business would fail. It was badly run, and the products it sold were overpriced and of poor quality.", "Opt_1": "several", "Opt_2": "inevitable", "Opt_3": "accurate", "Opt_4": "stable", "Answer": "inevitable", "Opt_1_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_3_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_4_def": "not changing; not easy to change"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It's a serious attack on any community's authority to develop and ____ housing policies without consultation.", "Opt_1": "invent", "Opt_2": "dedicate", "Opt_3": "convey", "Opt_4": "implement", "Answer": "implement", "Opt_1_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_2_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_3_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_4_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We must hope that her heavy involvement in the school's sporting programme will not be to the ____ of her studies.", "Opt_1": "insight", "Opt_2": "prospect", "Opt_3": "detriment", "Opt_4": "quality", "Answer": "detriment", "Opt_1_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_2_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_4_def": "worth or value"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A major ____ in our decision is how long it will take.", "Opt_1": "factor", "Opt_2": "power", "Opt_3": "commodity", "Opt_4": "region", "Answer": "factor", "Opt_1_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_2_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_3_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_4_def": "part of a place"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is a sharp contrast between Japan's ____ rigid hierarchy of national and private universities with the United States, which has a wider variety of institutions.", "Opt_1": "fairly", "Opt_2": "perhaps", "Opt_3": "largely", "Opt_4": "especially", "Answer": "fairly", "Opt_1_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_2_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "particularly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "After the deadline, you will need to negotiate an extension with the TA ____ such cases, before taking it up with the professor.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Court asserted that education was ____ the most significant function of state and local governments.", "Opt_1": "perhaps", "Opt_2": "furthermore", "Opt_3": "extremely", "Opt_4": "virtually", "Answer": "perhaps", "Opt_1_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_2_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_3_def": "very", "Opt_4_def": "almost"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A respect for other cultures is ____ in the philosophy of our international school.", "Opt_1": "inherent", "Opt_2": "precise", "Opt_3": "verbal", "Opt_4": "discrete", "Answer": "inherent", "Opt_1_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_2_def": "exact", "Opt_3_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_4_def": "separate"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Various approaches to environmental justice are discussed, along with steps in the planning ____ when citizen involvement is particularly effective.", "Opt_1": "challenge", "Opt_2": "prestige", "Opt_3": "process", "Opt_4": "defect", "Answer": "process", "Opt_1_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_2_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_3_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_4_def": "problem; mistake"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "ESS is for students who envision getting involved in the social ____ in any capacity: as volunteer consultants, board members, managers, or entrepreneurs.", "Opt_1": "aid", "Opt_2": "sector", "Opt_3": "proportion", "Opt_4": "schedule", "Answer": "sector", "Opt_1_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_2_def": "part; area", "Opt_3_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_4_def": "timetable"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Lack of knowledge is not a suitable reason for failure to ____ with regulations.", "Opt_1": "fluctuate", "Opt_2": "deduce", "Opt_3": "obtain", "Opt_4": "comply", "Answer": "comply", "Opt_1_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_2_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to do what someone asks or orders"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "They failed to publicly ____ the message that climate change will having a direct negative impact on global security.", "Opt_1": "distribute", "Opt_2": "reinforce", "Opt_3": "broadcast", "Opt_4": "revive", "Answer": "reinforce", "Opt_1_def": "to give out", "Opt_2_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_3_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_4_def": "to bring back (to life)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I assume his strange behaviour ____ is the result of his parents' divorce.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "indeed", "Opt_3": "approximately", "Opt_4": "moreover", "Answer": "recently", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_3_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_4_def": "also .., what is more .."}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This statement does not ____ that the university will be responsible for any other expenses of the above-name student.", "Opt_1": "entitle", "Opt_2": "increase", "Opt_3": "imply", "Opt_4": "diminish", "Answer": "imply", "Opt_1_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller or less important"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The committee expects that as NOAA moves forward it will have to revise the plan on a regular basis to ____ new understanding.", "Opt_1": "refute", "Opt_2": "incorporate", "Opt_3": "modify", "Opt_4": "discover", "Answer": "incorporate", "Opt_1_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_2_def": "to include", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We have a painting at home that's very valuable. It must be ____ more than a million dollars!", "Opt_1": "prior", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "before", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Most schools do a lot to ____ their students of the dangers of smoking.", "Opt_1": "force", "Opt_2": "pursue", "Opt_3": "warn", "Opt_4": "unite", "Answer": "warn", "Opt_1_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_2_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_3_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or get together"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "We do not ____ a unilateral ban on cosmetic testing on animals, nor do we reject the use of animals in biomedical research.", "Opt_1": "advocate", "Opt_2": "impress", "Opt_3": "dictate", "Opt_4": "require", "Answer": "advocate", "Opt_1_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_3_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_4_def": "to need"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It was found, in a bad ____ of repair and covered with moss and rust.", "Opt_1": "figure", "Opt_2": "precaution", "Opt_3": "state", "Opt_4": "shift", "Answer": "state", "Opt_1_def": "number", "Opt_2_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_3_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_4_def": "change"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Every employee must submit an annual tax declaration to his or her ____ tax office.", "Opt_1": "various", "Opt_2": "valid", "Opt_3": "local", "Opt_4": "forthcoming", "Answer": "local", "Opt_1_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_2_def": "correct", "Opt_3_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_4_def": "coming soon"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government did not proceed with the recommendations regarding the disability program and decided to ____ changes to the program.", "Opt_1": "trust", "Opt_2": "descend", "Opt_3": "release", "Opt_4": "review", "Answer": "review", "Opt_1_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_2_def": "to go down", "Opt_3_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_4_def": "to check over (and make changes)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Bernstein thinks the survey is very important to students and that schools should not ____ it.", "Opt_1": "develop", "Opt_2": "disrupt", "Opt_3": "recommend", "Opt_4": "criticize", "Answer": "criticize", "Opt_1_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_2_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_3_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_4_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The school is planning to ____ its lunchtime sports program after hearing a request from the student council.", "Opt_1": "revive", "Opt_2": "evolve", "Opt_3": "override", "Opt_4": "postpone", "Answer": "revive", "Opt_1_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_2_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_3_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_4_def": "to put back in time"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Our teachers ____ the school's philosophy that only excellence is good enough.", "Opt_1": "revise", "Opt_2": "embody", "Opt_3": "distort", "Opt_4": "transmit", "Answer": "embody", "Opt_1_def": "to change (in order to improve)", "Opt_2_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_4_def": "to send or convey"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The text should contain a concise ____ of the aims and scope of your thesis.", "Opt_1": "description", "Opt_2": "evidence", "Opt_3": "perspective", "Opt_4": "stereotype", "Answer": "description", "Opt_1_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_2_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_3_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_4_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The contributors ____ the impact of rivers on humans and, conversely, the impact of humans on rivers.", "Opt_1": "examine", "Opt_2": "insert", "Opt_3": "depart", "Opt_4": "alter", "Answer": "examine", "Opt_1_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to put in", "Opt_3_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to change"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The last ____ on earth to be explored was Antarctica.", "Opt_1": "territory", "Opt_2": "demand", "Opt_3": "challenge", "Opt_4": "behalf", "Answer": "territory", "Opt_1_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_3_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_4_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The parents decided to ____ against the school's expulsion their son.", "Opt_1": "appeal", "Opt_2": "afford", "Opt_3": "comprehend", "Opt_4": "ban", "Answer": "appeal", "Opt_1_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_2_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_3_def": "to understand", "Opt_4_def": "to prohibit or forbid"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "We recognize that circumstances ____ a family's control may inhibit a family's ability to contribute to educational expenses.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "due", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The Bush ____ will not back down on pursuing new sanctions against Iran over its nuclear program despite questions about their effectiveness.", "Opt_1": "advantage", "Opt_2": "ratio", "Opt_3": "term", "Opt_4": "administration", "Answer": "administration", "Opt_1_def": "benefit", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_3_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_4_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Among male baboons, dominance rank is ____ of maternal rank, and changes markedly with age; males reach their highest rank between 8 and 10 years of age.", "Opt_1": "extraordinary", "Opt_2": "vast", "Opt_3": "independent", "Opt_4": "complete", "Answer": "independent", "Opt_1_def": "very unusual", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_4_def": "full or finished"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Adults who did not ____ nutrition very important when buying food, as compared to adults who ____ed nutrition very important, were less likely to eat a good quality diet.", "Opt_1": "evaluate", "Opt_2": "consider", "Opt_3": "add", "Opt_4": "migrate", "Answer": "consider", "Opt_1_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "to think", "Opt_3_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_4_def": "to go to another place"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "This is a controversial point that will ____ much debate in the classroom, mainly among graduate students.", "Opt_1": "contemplate", "Opt_2": "generate", "Opt_3": "prove", "Opt_4": "pursue", "Answer": "generate", "Opt_1_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_2_def": "to make or produce", "Opt_3_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_4_def": "to follow (or do)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is not usual that students ____ with their teachers whether they must do homework or not.", "Opt_1": "attract", "Opt_2": "assimilate", "Opt_3": "construct", "Opt_4": "negotiate", "Answer": "negotiate", "Opt_1_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_2_def": "to take in", "Opt_3_def": "to make", "Opt_4_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is no ____ of sentimentality in Weil's notion of the beauty and order of the world.", "Opt_1": "trace", "Opt_2": "directions", "Opt_3": "notion", "Opt_4": "site", "Answer": "trace", "Opt_1_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_2_def": "instructions", "Opt_3_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_4_def": "place"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Another significant ____ was provided by the results of the post-hoc test of Recognition Motivation.", "Opt_1": "staff", "Opt_2": "insight", "Opt_3": "fault", "Opt_4": "exponent", "Answer": "insight", "Opt_1_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_2_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_3_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_4_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Your English is ____ improving, but you'll have to make greater effort if you want to get better more quickly.", "Opt_1": "hardly", "Opt_2": "gradually", "Opt_3": "furthermore", "Opt_4": "universally", "Answer": "gradually", "Opt_1_def": "not very much", "Opt_2_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_3_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_4_def": "all over the world; by everyone"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There were many sane but ____ reasons why he gave up his well-paid job.", "Opt_1": "complex", "Opt_2": "thorough", "Opt_3": "vague", "Opt_4": "compatible", "Answer": "complex", "Opt_1_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_2_def": "complete and careful", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "able to work with someone or something else"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Above all, World War II was an ____ of American history in which more American people bonded together in a common cause than ever before or ever since.", "Opt_1": "vary", "Opt_2": "prestige", "Opt_3": "opportunity", "Opt_4": "episode", "Answer": "episode", "Opt_1_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_2_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_3_def": "chance", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Rumours about teachers ____ quickly through schools.", "Opt_1": "attain", "Opt_2": "circulate", "Opt_3": "manifest", "Opt_4": "focus", "Answer": "circulate", "Opt_1_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_2_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_3_def": "show", "Opt_4_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The different religious groups gradually came to realize that none of them could hope to ____ over all the others.", "Opt_1": "publish", "Opt_2": "prevail", "Opt_3": "assess", "Opt_4": "require", "Answer": "prevail", "Opt_1_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_3_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_4_def": "to need"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "An analysis of the historical causes of slavery is ____ the scope of this course.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The detective was able to ____ from the size of the footprints that the thief was probably a woman or child.", "Opt_1": "undergo", "Opt_2": "strain", "Opt_3": "add", "Opt_4": "deduce", "Answer": "deduce", "Opt_1_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_2_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_3_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_4_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The assignments and quizzes form an integral part of the course grade and you may not obtain a good grade if you ____ them.", "Opt_1": "ignore", "Opt_2": "resist", "Opt_3": "contact", "Opt_4": "compile", "Answer": "ignore", "Opt_1_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_2_def": "to fight against", "Opt_3_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_4_def": "to put together (often in a list"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The teachers ____ that the school administration is secretly planning to increase working hours.", "Opt_1": "allege", "Opt_2": "possess", "Opt_3": "refute", "Opt_4": "correspond", "Answer": "allege", "Opt_1_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_2_def": "to have or own", "Opt_3_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_4_def": "to be related to"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you are an individual with a permanent disability, you may be ____ to obtain a discount.", "Opt_1": "consistent", "Opt_2": "eligible", "Opt_3": "annual", "Opt_4": "novel", "Answer": "eligible", "Opt_1_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_2_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_3_def": "yearly", "Opt_4_def": "new"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "With noise levels of this magnitude, hearing ____ is a distinct problem unless some sort of hearing protection is used.", "Opt_1": "compile", "Opt_2": "cease", "Opt_3": "damage", "Opt_4": "define", "Answer": "damage", "Opt_1_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_4_def": "to state what something is or means"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Sunnis believe that the Prophet Mohammed did not appoint a successor and therefore gave permission to Muslims to ____ or choose their own leader after his death.", "Opt_1": "elect", "Opt_2": "allocate", "Opt_3": "share", "Opt_4": "reflect", "Answer": "elect", "Opt_1_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_2_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange; to give", "Opt_4_def": "to think or consider"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The minister gave an ____ answer when asked if the government intended to raise taxes.", "Opt_1": "compatible", "Opt_2": "concise", "Opt_3": "ambiguous", "Opt_4": "uniform", "Answer": "ambiguous", "Opt_1_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_2_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_3_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is difficult to ____ the importance of the internet.", "Opt_1": "exaggerate", "Opt_2": "include", "Opt_3": "expose", "Opt_4": "ruin", "Answer": "exaggerate", "Opt_1_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_2_def": "to put in; to have in", "Opt_3_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or damage"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government is finding it difficult to break the ____ of poverty and poor school performance.", "Opt_1": "task", "Opt_2": "cycle", "Opt_3": "diagnosis", "Opt_4": "plenty", "Answer": "cycle", "Opt_1_def": "job", "Opt_2_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_3_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_4_def": "many, lots of"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government set up a committee to ____ the reasons for the riots.", "Opt_1": "replace", "Opt_2": "investigate", "Opt_3": "tend", "Opt_4": "dismiss", "Answer": "investigate", "Opt_1_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_3_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The links between ____ price declines and food prices are not easy to discern.", "Opt_1": "bond", "Opt_2": "commodity", "Opt_3": "apparatus", "Opt_4": "phrase", "Answer": "commodity", "Opt_1_def": "link; tie", "Opt_2_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_3_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure."}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Dairy farmers have led the latest in a long series of protests by agricultural associations, ____ the record high prices for farm products.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Most companies ____ to replace machines, like refrigerators or computers, if they break down in the first year.", "Opt_1": "interpretation", "Opt_2": "member", "Opt_3": "guarantee", "Opt_4": "scope", "Answer": "guarantee", "Opt_1_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_3_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_4_def": "extent, range"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This illustrates the variety of rational choices that a criminal would make in the decision to ____ a crime.", "Opt_1": "modify", "Opt_2": "fulfill", "Opt_3": "produce", "Opt_4": "commit", "Answer": "commit", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_3_def": "to make or create", "Opt_4_def": "to do (often an offense)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The time when Hitler was leader of Germany is possibly the most terrible ____ in all of history.", "Opt_1": "period", "Opt_2": "criterion", "Opt_3": "lack", "Opt_4": "level", "Answer": "period", "Opt_1_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_2_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_4_def": "standard; layer; amount"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If we assume that the ____ of a hydrogen atom is about 0.2 nm, then the corresponding confinement energy is about 38 eV.", "Opt_1": "dimension", "Opt_2": "responsibility", "Opt_3": "precaution", "Opt_4": "sphere", "Answer": "dimension", "Opt_1_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_2_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_3_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Beyond this, if you have a credible reason for absence or coming in late, such as a documented medical excuse, you should ____ that information to the instructor.", "Opt_1": "possess", "Opt_2": "attain", "Opt_3": "presume", "Opt_4": "provide", "Answer": "provide", "Opt_1_def": "to have or own", "Opt_2_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_3_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_4_def": "to give"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The western end of the trade ____ appears to have developed earlier than the eastern end, principally because of the development of the empires in the west.", "Opt_1": "route", "Opt_2": "struggle", "Opt_3": "comment", "Opt_4": "incident", "Answer": "route", "Opt_1_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_2_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_3_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_4_def": "happening; event"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It will help to ____ the nuclear powers from developing more advanced and more dangerous weapons.", "Opt_1": "acquire", "Opt_2": "separate", "Opt_3": "prevent", "Opt_4": "constitute", "Answer": "prevent", "Opt_1_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_2_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_3_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_4_def": "to be; to make up"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The chairman decided to ____ the meeting when people started shouting at each other.", "Opt_1": "terminate", "Opt_2": "own", "Opt_3": "require", "Opt_4": "remain", "Answer": "terminate", "Opt_1_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_3_def": "to need", "Opt_4_def": "to stay; still exist"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She has no means of studying in peace at home. Her ____ life is too chaotic.", "Opt_1": "domestic", "Opt_2": "main", "Opt_3": "intense", "Opt_4": "original", "Answer": "domestic", "Opt_1_def": "home", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_4_def": "the first of its kind"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The scientists that constitute the ____ all work in the field of cancer research.", "Opt_1": "procedure", "Opt_2": "purpose", "Opt_3": "standard", "Opt_4": "committee", "Answer": "committee", "Opt_1_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_2_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_3_def": "quality", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ used for the actual campaign was somewhat different.", "Opt_1": "strategy", "Opt_2": "account", "Opt_3": "rank", "Opt_4": "legislation", "Answer": "strategy", "Opt_1_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_2_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_3_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_4_def": "governmental rule; law"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It is especially important to remember that parents as a group have not usually taken the riding lessons and are not ____ to supervise their children.", "Opt_1": "competent", "Opt_2": "hostile", "Opt_3": "military", "Opt_4": "optional", "Answer": "competent", "Opt_1_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_2_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_3_def": "to do with army", "Opt_4_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Ask the candidate to discuss what they believe to have been their most significant challenges and accomplishments in their ____ job or a previous job.", "Opt_1": "brief", "Opt_2": "willing", "Opt_3": "current", "Opt_4": "entire", "Answer": "current", "Opt_1_def": "short", "Opt_2_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_3_def": "happening now", "Opt_4_def": "whole, all"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She will be a great ____ to the school when she retires next month. She has been a wonderful teacher here for many years.", "Opt_1": "industry", "Opt_2": "agent", "Opt_3": "supply", "Opt_4": "loss", "Answer": "loss", "Opt_1_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_3_def": "provision, store", "Opt_4_def": "removal or reduction"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The conflict ended with a rebellion against the East India Company in 1857, and the firm ____ was nationalized.", "Opt_1": "eventually", "Opt_2": "barely", "Opt_3": "virtually", "Opt_4": "indeed", "Answer": "eventually", "Opt_1_def": "in the end", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_3_def": "almost", "Opt_4_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This is an important finding that has implications for the ____ and treatment of children with PTSD.", "Opt_1": "outline", "Opt_2": "loss", "Opt_3": "means", "Opt_4": "diagnosis", "Answer": "diagnosis", "Opt_1_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_2_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_3_def": "way", "Opt_4_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If the student is determined to be independent of their parents, the student must be a resident of Indiana since at least December 31 of the ____ year.", "Opt_1": "minor", "Opt_2": "drastic", "Opt_3": "scarce", "Opt_4": "previous", "Answer": "previous", "Opt_1_def": "small, not important", "Opt_2_def": "severe; great", "Opt_3_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_4_def": "the one before"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ____ must not exceed three pages in length.", "Opt_1": "summary", "Opt_2": "scope", "Opt_3": "revenue", "Opt_4": "forecast", "Answer": "summary", "Opt_1_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_2_def": "extent, range", "Opt_3_def": "money, income", "Opt_4_def": "prediction"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "They are quoted at length in Kornbluh's book, The Pinochet File, and ____ cited in the New York Times.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "occasionally", "Opt_3": "moreover", "Opt_4": "seldom", "Answer": "recently", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "sometimes", "Opt_3_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_4_def": "rare"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The U.S. firms selling steel in India must compete against the firms from not ____ India but Europe, Japan, Korea and China as well.", "Opt_1": "roughly", "Opt_2": "barely", "Opt_3": "seldom", "Opt_4": "merely", "Answer": "merely", "Opt_1_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_3_def": "rare", "Opt_4_def": "only, just, simply"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is no need to enumerate in ____ the contributions of science to that war effort.", "Opt_1": "detail", "Opt_2": "defect", "Opt_3": "consequence", "Opt_4": "section", "Answer": "detail", "Opt_1_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_2_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "part"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Typical conversations involve a huge amount of \"world knowledge\" or common facts about life which humans ____ as they grow.", "Opt_1": "discern", "Opt_2": "offend", "Opt_3": "shrink", "Opt_4": "accumulate", "Answer": "accumulate", "Opt_1_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_2_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_4_def": "to grow; to gather together"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The management is hoping that its new improved product will ____ increased profits.", "Opt_1": "coordinate", "Opt_2": "circulate", "Opt_3": "explain", "Opt_4": "yield", "Answer": "yield", "Opt_1_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_2_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_3_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to produce"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "They argued that the law did not apply to Cheney's ____ force, since all of its members were government officials, not outsiders.", "Opt_1": "shortage", "Opt_2": "task", "Opt_3": "facilities", "Opt_4": "field", "Answer": "task", "Opt_1_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_2_def": "job", "Opt_3_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or study"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The Bush administration will not back down on pursuing new sanctions against Iran over its nuclear program ____ questions about their effectiveness.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We would probably become engaged in discussions from which we could not ____ ourselves and therefore our freedom of action would be limited.", "Opt_1": "income", "Opt_2": "point", "Opt_3": "struggle", "Opt_4": "extract", "Answer": "extract", "Opt_1_def": "money earned", "Opt_2_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_3_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_4_def": "to remove; to take out and use"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The school wanted to raise money from its ex-students, but the attempt was an ____ failure.", "Opt_1": "utter", "Opt_2": "random", "Opt_3": "genuine", "Opt_4": "rapid", "Answer": "utter", "Opt_1_def": "complete, total", "Opt_2_def": "by chance; without any sequence", "Opt_3_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_4_def": "quick"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If he doesn't start to ____ his behaviour, he is in danger of being asked to leave the school.", "Opt_1": "label", "Opt_2": "settle", "Opt_3": "interfere", "Opt_4": "amend", "Answer": "amend", "Opt_1_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_3_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_4_def": "to change (usually to improve something)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The high price of oil will ____ much of the company's profits this year.", "Opt_1": "restrict", "Opt_2": "accept", "Opt_3": "exhaust", "Opt_4": "absorb", "Answer": "absorb", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_3_def": "to use up", "Opt_4_def": "to take in; to take up"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is ____ that she has a talent for languages. She has learned English very quickly this year.", "Opt_1": "fortunate", "Opt_2": "evident", "Opt_3": "genuine", "Opt_4": "mobile", "Answer": "evident", "Opt_1_def": "lucky", "Opt_2_def": "clear", "Opt_3_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_4_def": "moving; able to move"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The university should not ____ students who take an extra year to complete their studies as lazy.", "Opt_1": "appreciate", "Opt_2": "label", "Opt_3": "remain", "Opt_4": "decline", "Answer": "label", "Opt_1_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_2_def": "to give a name to someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_4_def": "to go down or get worse"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There is a strong ____ between what the government promised to do and what it has actually achieved.", "Opt_1": "contrast", "Opt_2": "defect", "Opt_3": "response", "Opt_4": "prejudice", "Answer": "contrast", "Opt_1_def": "difference", "Opt_2_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_3_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_4_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The satellite photographs seem to ____ that North Korea is moving much of its army to the border with China.", "Opt_1": "signify", "Opt_2": "view", "Opt_3": "entitle", "Opt_4": "interact", "Answer": "signify", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_2_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_3_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to react, to affect and be affected"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Close to 30% of students did not perceive it to be cheating to lie to an instructor about having an illness or some other emergency in order to ____ a work deadline.", "Opt_1": "extend", "Opt_2": "require", "Opt_3": "retreat", "Opt_4": "label", "Answer": "extend", "Opt_1_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_2_def": "to need", "Opt_3_def": "to go back", "Opt_4_def": "to give a name to someone or something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Each ____ of the book, is represented by a family, which was chosen as an average family representing that country.", "Opt_1": "section", "Opt_2": "formula", "Opt_3": "choice", "Opt_4": "shift", "Answer": "section", "Opt_1_def": "part", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_4_def": "change"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government has increased the tax on petrol, ____ making itself very unpopular with motorists.", "Opt_1": "furthermore", "Opt_2": "namely", "Opt_3": "perhaps", "Opt_4": "thereby", "Answer": "thereby", "Opt_1_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_2_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_3_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_4_def": "by doing this"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government failed to recognize the ____ of the public's unhappiness with the new law.", "Opt_1": "symptom", "Opt_2": "sum", "Opt_3": "dimension", "Opt_4": "community", "Answer": "dimension", "Opt_1_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_2_def": "an amount of money, total", "Opt_3_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "These tips do not relieve you of the ____ to read and follow the Instruction Booklet which is ONLY available on line this year!", "Opt_1": "rank", "Opt_2": "field", "Opt_3": "compensation", "Opt_4": "obligation", "Answer": "obligation", "Opt_1_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_3_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_4_def": "a requirement to do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "When used correctly and consistently, condoms are an ____ means of preventing pregnancy.", "Opt_1": "mobile", "Opt_2": "obsolete", "Opt_3": "effective", "Opt_4": "distinct", "Answer": "effective", "Opt_1_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_2_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_3_def": "good, working well", "Opt_4_def": "clear and strong"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The IGH claims that Preval's ____ was the result of more information coming through.", "Opt_1": "motivate", "Opt_2": "reform", "Opt_3": "decrease", "Opt_4": "monitor", "Answer": "decrease", "Opt_1_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_4_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Is anyone in class ____ with the terms 'subject' and 'predicate'?", "Opt_1": "flexible", "Opt_2": "formal", "Opt_3": "wise", "Opt_4": "familiar", "Answer": "familiar", "Opt_1_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_2_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_3_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_4_def": "known; well-known"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I have no ____ of being a teacher when I leave school. I want to earn more money!", "Opt_1": "remedy", "Opt_2": "alternative", "Opt_3": "intention", "Opt_4": "outline", "Answer": "intention", "Opt_1_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_2_def": "other possibility", "Opt_3_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_4_def": "plan or summary"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I do not feel that the possible applications of a line of research should be allowed to dictate the ____ of research in my laboratory.", "Opt_1": "directions", "Opt_2": "background", "Opt_3": "shift", "Opt_4": "liberty", "Answer": "directions", "Opt_1_def": "instructions", "Opt_2_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "change", "Opt_4_def": "freedom"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There was a revolution in language teaching about 40 years ago when the spoken language replaced writing and grammar as the main ____ of teaching.", "Opt_1": "commit", "Opt_2": "purchase", "Opt_3": "focus", "Opt_4": "comprehend", "Answer": "focus", "Opt_1_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_2_def": "to buy", "Opt_3_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_4_def": "to understand"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Even though you may know your housemates well, you should always take the ____ to lock the door. Windows should also be secured.", "Opt_1": "shortage", "Opt_2": "precaution", "Opt_3": "issue", "Opt_4": "task", "Answer": "precaution", "Opt_1_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_2_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_3_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_4_def": "job"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The school decided to ____ when the angry parent said that he would contact his lawyer.", "Opt_1": "retreat", "Opt_2": "assemble", "Opt_3": "permit", "Opt_4": "interfere", "Answer": "retreat", "Opt_1_def": "to go back", "Opt_2_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_3_def": "to allow", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent; to harm"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The Hershey Corporation, however, already had a ____ to provide chocolate for the troops.", "Opt_1": "deal", "Opt_2": "bias", "Opt_3": "ratio", "Opt_4": "tradition", "Answer": "deal", "Opt_1_def": "agreement", "Opt_2_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_4_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I do not feel that the possible applications of a line of research should be allowed to dictate the ____ of research in my laboratory.", "Opt_1": "rank", "Opt_2": "growth", "Opt_3": "series", "Opt_4": "directions", "Answer": "directions", "Opt_1_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_2_def": "development, increase", "Opt_3_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_4_def": "instructions"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The Tower of Hanoi is an ____ puzzle involving three pegs, and an arbitrary number of circular discs, each of a different size, and with holes in their centers.", "Opt_1": "firm", "Opt_2": "random", "Opt_3": "ordinary", "Opt_4": "ancient", "Answer": "ancient", "Opt_1_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_2_def": "by chance; without any sequence", "Opt_3_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_4_def": "very old"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The most important ____ of living near the school is that I can go home for lunch every day.", "Opt_1": "ability", "Opt_2": "advantage", "Opt_3": "performance", "Opt_4": "perspective", "Answer": "advantage", "Opt_1_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_2_def": "benefit", "Opt_3_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_4_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In the heat of election campaigning, it is in no-one's interest to impose an ____ crisis upon the economy.", "Opt_1": "artificial", "Opt_2": "superior", "Opt_3": "deliberate", "Opt_4": "crucial", "Answer": "artificial", "Opt_1_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_2_def": "better", "Opt_3_def": "intentional, not by accident", "Opt_4_def": "extremely important"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I'm sorry but the school has no ____ to educate children with severe learning problems.", "Opt_1": "affair", "Opt_2": "performance", "Opt_3": "ability", "Opt_4": "role", "Answer": "ability", "Opt_1_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_2_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_3_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_4_def": "job or function"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ advantage of living in the city is that you are close to good shopping and entertainment. Of course, city life has many disadvantages too.", "Opt_1": "ambitious", "Opt_2": "random", "Opt_3": "main", "Opt_4": "slight", "Answer": "main", "Opt_1_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_2_def": "by chance; without any sequence", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "small"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The word 'gay' did not come to ____ 'homosexual' until quite recently.", "Opt_1": "regret", "Opt_2": "permit", "Opt_3": "denote", "Opt_4": "consent", "Answer": "denote", "Opt_1_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_2_def": "to allow", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to agree"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "We should not ____ the costs, minimize the benefits of what we have already achieved, or downplay the risk of failure to persevere.", "Opt_1": "attend", "Opt_2": "disperse", "Opt_3": "exaggerate", "Opt_4": "separate", "Answer": "exaggerate", "Opt_1_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_2_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_3_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_4_def": "to pull or put apart"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The last ____ of the twentieth century started in 1990 and ended on 31 December 1999.", "Opt_1": "propensity", "Opt_2": "figure", "Opt_3": "scope", "Opt_4": "decade", "Answer": "decade", "Opt_1_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_2_def": "number", "Opt_3_def": "extent, range", "Opt_4_def": "a period of ten years"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Art is every artist's attempt to communicate in a way ____ words what they feel, see, and think about life.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Being under the ____ of illegal drugs or alcohol on the job may pose serious risks.", "Opt_1": "portion", "Opt_2": "interpretation", "Opt_3": "influence", "Opt_4": "truth", "Answer": "influence", "Opt_1_def": "part, amount", "Opt_2_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "actual reason or fact"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The University of Maryland team is particularly focused on using their ____ to test drugs that may block cell-to-cell \"quorum-sensing\".", "Opt_1": "device", "Opt_2": "gap", "Opt_3": "intention", "Opt_4": "scale", "Answer": "device", "Opt_1_def": "object; method", "Opt_2_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_3_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_4_def": "extent"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "When he left home he planned to ____ from Christianity to Buddhism, but then he decided he didn't believe in any god.", "Opt_1": "suspect", "Opt_2": "descend", "Opt_3": "offer", "Opt_4": "convert", "Answer": "convert", "Opt_1_def": "to believe", "Opt_2_def": "to go down", "Opt_3_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_4_def": "to change from one thing to another"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "An international school is a place that cannot ____ if there is prejudice that certain groups of students are better than others.", "Opt_1": "collaborate", "Opt_2": "contact", "Opt_3": "select", "Opt_4": "survive", "Answer": "survive", "Opt_1_def": "to work together", "Opt_2_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_3_def": "to choose", "Opt_4_def": "to not die"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "At weddings the speeches usually ____ the food.", "Opt_1": "expel", "Opt_2": "consult", "Opt_3": "precede", "Opt_4": "select", "Answer": "precede", "Opt_1_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_2_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_3_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to choose"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The last death occurred on Thursday morning when a deaf man apparently walking to work did not ____ a police order to halt and was shot.", "Opt_1": "force", "Opt_2": "obey", "Opt_3": "arrange", "Opt_4": "comprise", "Answer": "obey", "Opt_1_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_2_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_3_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_4_def": "to be made up of; to include"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The late bus will ____ at 5:30 today, not at 5:15 as usual.", "Opt_1": "attend", "Opt_2": "establish", "Opt_3": "depart", "Opt_4": "reveal", "Answer": "depart", "Opt_1_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_2_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_3_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to show or uncover"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The college is aggressively working to ____ engineering education and develop leaders for the 21st century workforce.", "Opt_1": "qualify", "Opt_2": "transform", "Opt_3": "cover", "Opt_4": "deteriorate", "Answer": "transform", "Opt_1_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_4_def": "to get worse"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is difficult to ____ how the government can hope to win the forthcoming election.", "Opt_1": "conserve", "Opt_2": "imply", "Opt_3": "transfer", "Opt_4": "perceive", "Answer": "perceive", "Opt_1_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_3_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Students who get in the athletic teams enjoy a high ____ in the school community.", "Opt_1": "prestige", "Opt_2": "background", "Opt_3": "route", "Opt_4": "sum", "Answer": "prestige", "Opt_1_def": "fame and respect", "Opt_2_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_4_def": "an amount of money, total"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Some people use unethical methods to create a ____ that says what they want it to say.", "Opt_1": "objection", "Opt_2": "command", "Opt_3": "statistic", "Opt_4": "occasion", "Answer": "statistic", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_2_def": "control", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_4_def": "time (opportunity)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Sunnis believe that the Prophet Mohammed did not ____ a successor and therefore gave permission to Muslims to elect or choose their own leader after his death.", "Opt_1": "contemplate", "Opt_2": "appeal", "Opt_3": "implement", "Opt_4": "appoint", "Answer": "appoint", "Opt_1_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_2_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_3_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government are concerned about the ____ small number of people who voted in the last election.", "Opt_1": "hence", "Opt_2": "approximately", "Opt_3": "dramatically", "Opt_4": "moreover", "Answer": "dramatically", "Opt_1_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_2_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_3_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_4_def": "also .., what is more .."}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Unidata is a diverse community of education and research institutions vested in the common ____ of sharing data, tools to access the data, and software to use and visualize the data.", "Opt_1": "goal", "Opt_2": "advantage", "Opt_3": "minimum", "Opt_4": "demand", "Answer": "goal", "Opt_1_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_2_def": "benefit", "Opt_3_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_4_def": "a need or desire for"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Almost everyone believes that terrorism should be fought, but there is little agreement about the ____ in which it should be done.", "Opt_1": "manner", "Opt_2": "loss", "Opt_3": "transition", "Opt_4": "mechanism", "Answer": "manner", "Opt_1_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_3_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_4_def": "procedure, process"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Mike is feeling very unwell. Can you please ____ him to the nurse?", "Opt_1": "underlie", "Opt_2": "accompany", "Opt_3": "suffer", "Opt_4": "enable", "Answer": "accompany", "Opt_1_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_2_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_3_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_4_def": "to make something or someone able to do something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Dogs keep dying: Too many owners ____ unaware of toxic dog food.", "Opt_1": "classify", "Opt_2": "motivate", "Opt_3": "encourage", "Opt_4": "remain", "Answer": "remain", "Opt_1_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_2_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_4_def": "to stay; still exist"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Imagine being surrounded by hundreds of people who are ____ convinced you can do anything.", "Opt_1": "overly", "Opt_2": "respectively", "Opt_3": "absolutely", "Opt_4": "namely", "Answer": "absolutely", "Opt_1_def": "too", "Opt_2_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_4_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The Waldorf Education method considers the teacher's own development to be a significant factor in the educational ____ of the children.", "Opt_1": "custom", "Opt_2": "process", "Opt_3": "function", "Opt_4": "factor", "Answer": "process", "Opt_1_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_2_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_3_def": "job or role", "Opt_4_def": "an aspect to be considered"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It has no alternative but to ____ to more sources and additional help from all those who are keen to support Palestinian education.", "Opt_1": "strive", "Opt_2": "appeal", "Opt_3": "accompany", "Opt_4": "repeat", "Answer": "appeal", "Opt_1_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_2_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_3_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_4_def": "to do or say again"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is less widely recognized, moreover, that growth and globalization also threaten to ____ environmental damage.", "Opt_1": "revive", "Opt_2": "receive", "Opt_3": "accelerate", "Opt_4": "realize", "Answer": "accelerate", "Opt_1_def": "to bring back (to life)", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_4_def": "to come to know or understand"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ problem results from the authors' basic misunderstanding of economics and politics.", "Opt_1": "satisfactory", "Opt_2": "imaginary", "Opt_3": "public", "Opt_4": "apparent", "Answer": "imaginary", "Opt_1_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_2_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_3_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_4_def": "clear; obvious"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Check your ____ to be sure that class times do not overlap.", "Opt_1": "schedule", "Opt_2": "circumstances", "Opt_3": "shortage", "Opt_4": "site", "Answer": "schedule", "Opt_1_def": "timetable", "Opt_2_def": "situation", "Opt_3_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_4_def": "place"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Aycock stated that he had looked over the horse before the ____ and did not observe any marks indicating that the horse had been cut.", "Opt_1": "migrate", "Opt_2": "analyze", "Opt_3": "decline", "Opt_4": "purchase", "Answer": "purchase", "Opt_1_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_2_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_3_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to buy"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "While we must oppose all terrorism, and we have many local enemies in ____ parts of the world.", "Opt_1": "firm", "Opt_2": "faint", "Opt_3": "various", "Opt_4": "bold", "Answer": "various", "Opt_1_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_2_def": "not strong", "Opt_3_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_4_def": "brave"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We would probably become engaged in discussions from which we could not extract ourselves and ____ our freedom of action would be limited.", "Opt_1": "thus", "Opt_2": "roughly", "Opt_3": "overly", "Opt_4": "therefore", "Answer": "therefore", "Opt_1_def": "so", "Opt_2_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_3_def": "too", "Opt_4_def": "so, as a result"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Take 3 grams of sodium chloride and an ____ amount of sugar.", "Opt_1": "ambiguous", "Opt_2": "contemporary", "Opt_3": "equivalent", "Opt_4": "aware", "Answer": "equivalent", "Opt_1_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_2_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_3_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_4_def": "knowing"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There is not an ____ supply of oil and natural gas.", "Opt_1": "infinite", "Opt_2": "imaginary", "Opt_3": "inherent", "Opt_4": "homogeneous", "Answer": "infinite", "Opt_1_def": "without an end", "Opt_2_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_3_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Scientists are working on a robot that can ____ to the deepest parts of the Pacific Ocean.", "Opt_1": "owe", "Opt_2": "postpone", "Opt_3": "descend", "Opt_4": "integrate", "Answer": "descend", "Opt_1_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_2_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_3_def": "to go down", "Opt_4_def": "to fit into a new situation"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Nazi paramilitary organization was compulsory, although he was never a ____ of the Nazi party and his family opposed Hitler's regime.", "Opt_1": "guide", "Opt_2": "member", "Opt_3": "structure", "Opt_4": "quantity", "Answer": "member", "Opt_1_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_2_def": "a person who is part of a team or other organization", "Opt_3_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You are recommended to ____ quickly throughout the classroom to make sure that everyone understands the task, then return to help students who are having difficulty.", "Opt_1": "advance", "Opt_2": "assume", "Opt_3": "circulate", "Opt_4": "publish", "Answer": "circulate", "Opt_1_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to believe to be true; to presume or predict", "Opt_3_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_4_def": "to make available in paper or online form"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "John has many strong opinions. You have to be sure not to let him ____ groupwork in class.", "Opt_1": "dominate", "Opt_2": "regret", "Opt_3": "negotiate", "Opt_4": "suffer", "Answer": "dominate", "Opt_1_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_2_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_3_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_4_def": "to experience something bad or painful"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If we learn to ____ effectively with others and are willing to risk sharing our own feelings and respect other's feelings, many rewards will await us.", "Opt_1": "align", "Opt_2": "communicate", "Opt_3": "amend", "Opt_4": "create", "Answer": "communicate", "Opt_1_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_2_def": "to convey information", "Opt_3_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_4_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Children ____ in classes where their teachers care about each of them as individuals.", "Opt_1": "reward", "Opt_2": "prosper", "Opt_3": "transform", "Opt_4": "monitor", "Answer": "prosper", "Opt_1_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_2_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to watch ( someone's or something's behaviour )"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A major ____ in the proposal is that there is not sufficient money to finance it.", "Opt_1": "research", "Opt_2": "course", "Opt_3": "drawback", "Opt_4": "defect", "Answer": "defect", "Opt_1_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_2_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_4_def": "problem; mistake"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Most companies ____ to replace machines, like refrigerators or computers, if they break down in the first year.", "Opt_1": "proportion", "Opt_2": "procedure", "Opt_3": "guarantee", "Opt_4": "district", "Answer": "guarantee", "Opt_1_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_2_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_4_def": "region of a city"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "He has a ____ chance of getting in to Oxford University if he gets top scores in all his exams.", "Opt_1": "concise", "Opt_2": "subjective", "Opt_3": "subsequent", "Opt_4": "slight", "Answer": "slight", "Opt_1_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_2_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_3_def": "next, following", "Opt_4_def": "small"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Carla Santos, a professor of leisure studies, says our perception of another culture is likely shaped by accounts of travel writers, who ____ to perpetuate cultural stereotypes.", "Opt_1": "present", "Opt_2": "tend", "Opt_3": "increase", "Opt_4": "interact", "Answer": "tend", "Opt_1_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_2_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_4_def": "to react, to affect and be affected"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ problem results from the authors' basic misunderstanding of economics and politics.", "Opt_1": "ultimate", "Opt_2": "unique", "Opt_3": "imaginary", "Opt_4": "elementary", "Answer": "imaginary", "Opt_1_def": "final or most important", "Opt_2_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_3_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We all have to ____ differences of opinion in the political world and, in order to do that, we have to understand that there are real reasons for these differences.", "Opt_1": "insist", "Opt_2": "review", "Opt_3": "tolerate", "Opt_4": "estimate", "Answer": "tolerate", "Opt_1_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_2_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_4_def": "to make an intelligent guess"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It would not be wise to ____ from our planned course of action.", "Opt_1": "succeed", "Opt_2": "deviate", "Opt_3": "estimate", "Opt_4": "inhibit", "Answer": "deviate", "Opt_1_def": "to do well", "Opt_2_def": "to be different", "Opt_3_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent or stop"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The technology to ____ carbon monoxide into liquid fuel has been around a long time.", "Opt_1": "convert", "Opt_2": "multiply", "Opt_3": "advocate", "Opt_4": "halt", "Answer": "convert", "Opt_1_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_2_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_3_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The police were not ____ of controlling the street demonstrations. They had to call in the army.", "Opt_1": "explicit", "Opt_2": "imaginary", "Opt_3": "capable", "Opt_4": "satisfactory", "Answer": "capable", "Opt_1_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_2_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_3_def": "able", "Opt_4_def": "enough;OK"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Many people believe that the invasion of Iraq was a ____ mistake.", "Opt_1": "final", "Opt_2": "minor", "Opt_3": "mental", "Opt_4": "fundamental", "Answer": "fundamental", "Opt_1_def": "last", "Opt_2_def": "small, not important", "Opt_3_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She is unlikely to ____ above the rank of teacher helper; she is not very hard-working, and too often absent.", "Opt_1": "occasion", "Opt_2": "coincidence", "Opt_3": "rise", "Opt_4": "incentive", "Answer": "rise", "Opt_1_def": "time (opportunity)", "Opt_2_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_3_def": "to go up", "Opt_4_def": "reason to do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The police have not been able to establish a ____ for the brutal killing.", "Opt_1": "disaster", "Opt_2": "scheme", "Opt_3": "motive", "Opt_4": "friction", "Answer": "motive", "Opt_1_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_2_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_3_def": "reason", "Opt_4_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Spending months at a time in orbit, the scientists will be able to observe changes on the earth ____ them from day to day.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Many people do not ____ a top engineering education with a liberal arts setting.", "Opt_1": "communicate", "Opt_2": "stimulate", "Opt_3": "associate", "Opt_4": "address", "Answer": "associate", "Opt_1_def": "to convey information", "Opt_2_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_3_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_4_def": "to give attention to (an issue)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Once a language has less than about a hundred speakers, it is almost impossible to ____ it.", "Opt_1": "establish", "Opt_2": "preserve", "Opt_3": "increase", "Opt_4": "shrink", "Answer": "preserve", "Opt_1_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_2_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The Dartmouth has received a number of complaints, specifically ____ their poor fact-checking.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "On the back of this form or on a separate sheet, write a thorough ____ describing yourself, your interests, and why you have applied.", "Opt_1": "treatment", "Opt_2": "symbol", "Opt_3": "territory", "Opt_4": "statement", "Answer": "statement", "Opt_1_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_2_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_3_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_4_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The goal of the Program is to train students to investigate ____ problems in human physiology using modern technology.", "Opt_1": "significant", "Opt_2": "automatic", "Opt_3": "slight", "Opt_4": "confident", "Answer": "significant", "Opt_1_def": "important, large", "Opt_2_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_3_def": "small", "Opt_4_def": "sure that something will happen"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Typically held the 3rd week of February, this is an annual event that helps College of Fine Arts students explore careers, ____ strategies to pursue career and artistic goals successfully.", "Opt_1": "earn", "Opt_2": "undergo", "Opt_3": "develop", "Opt_4": "dismiss", "Answer": "develop", "Opt_1_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_2_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_4_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Her consistent efforts throughout the school year are ____ to yield excellent results in her final examinations.", "Opt_1": "radical", "Opt_2": "certain", "Opt_3": "domestic", "Opt_4": "official", "Answer": "certain", "Opt_1_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_2_def": "sure", "Opt_3_def": "home", "Opt_4_def": "approved by an authority"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Describe the study in detail sufficient to ____ the reviewer that the problem is worth investigation.", "Opt_1": "examine", "Opt_2": "ruin", "Opt_3": "produce", "Opt_4": "convince", "Answer": "convince", "Opt_1_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_3_def": "to make or create", "Opt_4_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is important to ____ language that reinforces the dominant culture's attitude to disability.", "Opt_1": "review", "Opt_2": "adhere", "Opt_3": "intervene", "Opt_4": "suffer", "Answer": "review", "Opt_1_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_2_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_3_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_4_def": "to experience something bad or painful"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The school has employed an ____ to advise on the best way to use computer technology in the classroom.", "Opt_1": "category", "Opt_2": "rank", "Opt_3": "diagnosis", "Opt_4": "expert", "Answer": "expert", "Opt_1_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_2_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_3_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_4_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Transportation is not an important ____ in the marketing cost of the new product.", "Opt_1": "comparison", "Opt_2": "target", "Opt_3": "innovation", "Opt_4": "element", "Answer": "element", "Opt_1_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_2_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_3_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_4_def": "aspect, part"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I usually keep a ____ of spare pencils in my desk, so that I can lend one to any student who comes without.", "Opt_1": "supply", "Opt_2": "term", "Opt_3": "district", "Opt_4": "method", "Answer": "supply", "Opt_1_def": "provision, store", "Opt_2_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_3_def": "region of a city", "Opt_4_def": "a way of doing something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We are focused on creating the technology and applications that will ____ daily media consumers to become daily media producers.", "Opt_1": "deteriorate", "Opt_2": "enable", "Opt_3": "procure", "Opt_4": "receive", "Answer": "enable", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If they want to ____ more business, they will have to reduce their prices.", "Opt_1": "frustrate", "Opt_2": "undertake", "Opt_3": "presume", "Opt_4": "ensure", "Answer": "ensure", "Opt_1_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_2_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_3_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_4_def": "to make sure (of)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The course aims at helping students ____ a working familiarity with the Federal Rules of Evidence.", "Opt_1": "spread", "Opt_2": "maintain", "Opt_3": "acquire", "Opt_4": "produce", "Answer": "acquire", "Opt_1_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to make or create"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is no ____ that the early proponents of so-called public education were socialists.", "Opt_1": "legislation", "Opt_2": "justice", "Opt_3": "coincidence", "Opt_4": "sum", "Answer": "coincidence", "Opt_1_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_2_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_3_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_4_def": "an amount of money, total"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Some assignments will be graded; others will ____ receive a check-mark.", "Opt_1": "barely", "Opt_2": "rather", "Opt_3": "nevertheless", "Opt_4": "merely", "Answer": "merely", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_2_def": "instead", "Opt_3_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_4_def": "only, just, simply"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you are an ____ with a permanent disability, you may be eligible to obtain a discount.", "Opt_1": "consequence", "Opt_2": "pressure", "Opt_3": "resident", "Opt_4": "individual", "Answer": "individual", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_3_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_4_def": "one person"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Please do not ____ me. I know what I said is correct.", "Opt_1": "remove", "Opt_2": "commit", "Opt_3": "comply", "Opt_4": "contradict", "Answer": "contradict", "Opt_1_def": "to take away", "Opt_2_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_3_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_4_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The Commission was unable to estimate the cost of complying with new requirements ____ data recording.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The police chief gave a very different version of the ____ than the TV reporter the previous day.", "Opt_1": "scope", "Opt_2": "shift", "Opt_3": "portion", "Opt_4": "incident", "Answer": "incident", "Opt_1_def": "extent, range", "Opt_2_def": "change", "Opt_3_def": "part, amount", "Opt_4_def": "happening; event"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There are ____ students from Korea at Frankfurt International School.", "Opt_1": "spontaneous", "Opt_2": "complete", "Opt_3": "conscious", "Opt_4": "numerous", "Answer": "numerous", "Opt_1_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_2_def": "full or finished", "Opt_3_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_4_def": "very many"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Many stores have special offers to ____ new customers.", "Opt_1": "adopt", "Opt_2": "consider", "Opt_3": "attract", "Opt_4": "depart", "Answer": "attract", "Opt_1_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_2_def": "to think", "Opt_3_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_4_def": "to leave; to be different from"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "These orders do much to ____ the significant need for better organization in terms of record-keeping.", "Opt_1": "contemplate", "Opt_2": "illustrate", "Opt_3": "reveal", "Opt_4": "append", "Answer": "illustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_2_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_3_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_4_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Women often ____ less money that men doing the same job. This anomaly must be stopped.", "Opt_1": "manufacture", "Opt_2": "modify", "Opt_3": "earn", "Opt_4": "prosper", "Answer": "earn", "Opt_1_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_2_def": "to change", "Opt_3_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_4_def": "to do well; to become rich"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Television and the other news media have helped to magnify the person and the ____ of the presidency.", "Opt_1": "institution", "Opt_2": "comparison", "Opt_3": "prospect", "Opt_4": "skill", "Answer": "institution", "Opt_1_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of how two things are similar or different", "Opt_3_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_4_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You are ____ to fail unless you put in more effort.", "Opt_1": "latter", "Opt_2": "valuable", "Opt_3": "tough", "Opt_4": "certain", "Answer": "certain", "Opt_1_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_2_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_3_def": "difficult, strong", "Opt_4_def": "sure"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Recent research has investigated the traits that may ____ the development of drug addiction.", "Opt_1": "hesitate", "Opt_2": "deviate", "Opt_3": "underlie", "Opt_4": "define", "Answer": "underlie", "Opt_1_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to be different", "Opt_3_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_4_def": "to state what something is or means"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The population of a country will ____ if more people die than are born.", "Opt_1": "align", "Opt_2": "constitute", "Opt_3": "confront", "Opt_4": "decrease", "Answer": "decrease", "Opt_1_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_3_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller, to go down"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is now obvious to almost everyone that the decision to invade Iraq was a very ____ error of judgment.", "Opt_1": "scarce", "Opt_2": "serious", "Opt_3": "mobile", "Opt_4": "positive", "Answer": "serious", "Opt_1_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_2_def": "severe, large", "Opt_3_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_4_def": "good; optimistic"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Students have been invited to comment on the ____ of the school's new sports facility.", "Opt_1": "design", "Opt_2": "detriment", "Opt_3": "skill", "Opt_4": "category", "Answer": "design", "Opt_1_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_2_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_3_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_4_def": "group of similar items"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There has been a recent ____ in language teaching towards more grammar and vocabulary.", "Opt_1": "vary", "Opt_2": "shift", "Opt_3": "administration", "Opt_4": "advantage", "Answer": "shift", "Opt_1_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_2_def": "change", "Opt_3_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_4_def": "benefit"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Very ____ water does not conduct electricity well compared with contaminated water because it contains no inorganic ions.", "Opt_1": "abstract", "Opt_2": "slight", "Opt_3": "pure", "Opt_4": "numerous", "Answer": "pure", "Opt_1_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_2_def": "small", "Opt_3_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_4_def": "very many"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "To include an image on your website, you will need to ____ the image into your webpage using an HTML editor.", "Opt_1": "insert", "Opt_2": "judge", "Opt_3": "commit", "Opt_4": "communicate", "Answer": "insert", "Opt_1_def": "to put in", "Opt_2_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_4_def": "to convey information"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ of native-English speakers and non-native-English speakers at the school is about 40% : 60%.", "Opt_1": "domain", "Opt_2": "distance", "Opt_3": "ratio", "Opt_4": "tradition", "Answer": "ratio", "Opt_1_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_3_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_4_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "She is being ____ concerned about the exams. She will certainly pass.", "Opt_1": "indeed", "Opt_2": "naturally", "Opt_3": "overly", "Opt_4": "occasionally", "Answer": "overly", "Opt_1_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_2_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_3_def": "too", "Opt_4_def": "sometimes"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Therefore, it is important to ____ low birth weight infants according to their weight for their gestational age.", "Opt_1": "consider", "Opt_2": "advance", "Opt_3": "stipulate", "Opt_4": "classify", "Answer": "classify", "Opt_1_def": "to think", "Opt_2_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_3_def": "to require", "Opt_4_def": "to put into a category or class"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "We spent the ____ lesson talking about the past continuous tense. It was so boring.", "Opt_1": "numerous", "Opt_2": "entire", "Opt_3": "infinite", "Opt_4": "capable", "Answer": "entire", "Opt_1_def": "very many", "Opt_2_def": "whole, all", "Opt_3_def": "without an end", "Opt_4_def": "able"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "In a densely populated area, an earthquake may do far more damage than one of greater magnitude that occurs in a ____ area.", "Opt_1": "widespread", "Opt_2": "remote", "Opt_3": "exact", "Opt_4": "drastic", "Answer": "remote", "Opt_1_def": "common", "Opt_2_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_3_def": "precise, opposite of approximate", "Opt_4_def": "severe; great"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Computers are a much more ____ way of storing and retrieving large amounts of data than keeping it on paper in huge cabinets.", "Opt_1": "artificial", "Opt_2": "efficient", "Opt_3": "practical", "Opt_4": "likely", "Answer": "efficient", "Opt_1_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_2_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_3_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_4_def": "probable"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The Committee is concerned that children dropping out of school during the ____ stage of education have insufficient alternative educational opportunities.", "Opt_1": "compulsory", "Opt_2": "supplementary", "Opt_3": "loose", "Opt_4": "subsequent", "Answer": "compulsory", "Opt_1_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_2_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_3_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_4_def": "next, following"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "TSU Employees who ____ University network and computing resources may be subject to disciplinary action.", "Opt_1": "qualify", "Opt_2": "exhaust", "Opt_3": "control", "Opt_4": "abuse", "Answer": "abuse", "Opt_1_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_2_def": "to use up", "Opt_3_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to treat someone or something badly"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The most serious objection raised ____ the survey questions the use of self-report scales to assess prejudice.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She thinks that the homeless children probably will ____ more poorly, educationally, than the children who come from homes.", "Opt_1": "fare", "Opt_2": "suspect", "Opt_3": "owe", "Opt_4": "criticize", "Answer": "fare", "Opt_1_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_2_def": "to believe", "Opt_3_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_4_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She made it clear many times throughout the work that she did not believe in and did not want to ____ in the concept and institution of marriage.", "Opt_1": "participate", "Opt_2": "edit", "Opt_3": "recognize", "Opt_4": "degenerate", "Answer": "participate", "Opt_1_def": "to take part", "Opt_2_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_4_def": "to get worse"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There have been ____ attempts to build an intelligent robot, but so far no-one has been successful.", "Opt_1": "complex", "Opt_2": "accurate", "Opt_3": "numerous", "Opt_4": "subtle", "Answer": "numerous", "Opt_1_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_2_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_3_def": "very many", "Opt_4_def": "not clear or strong"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is a sharp contrast between Japan's fairly rigid ____ of national and private universities with the United States, which has a wider variety of institutions.", "Opt_1": "anomaly", "Opt_2": "interior", "Opt_3": "institution", "Opt_4": "hierarchy", "Answer": "hierarchy", "Opt_1_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_2_def": "inside", "Opt_3_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_4_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He is an American citizen which obviously puts him in a different ____ from the kinds of individuals that the president has suggested might be suitable.", "Opt_1": "drawback", "Opt_2": "category", "Opt_3": "potential", "Opt_4": "administration", "Answer": "category", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_2_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_3_def": "good possibility", "Opt_4_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Your report is good, but you need to ____ a paragraph on the causes of the accident.", "Opt_1": "add", "Opt_2": "govern", "Opt_3": "contemplate", "Opt_4": "formulate", "Answer": "add", "Opt_1_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_2_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_3_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_4_def": "to express"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "His examination failure did not occur through lack of effort or ____ but because of serious illness in the weeks before.", "Opt_1": "ignorance", "Opt_2": "outcome", "Opt_3": "ability", "Opt_4": "attribute", "Answer": "ability", "Opt_1_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_4_def": "characteristic; property"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Stopping work to look after a new-born child must not be allowed to ____ with a woman's career chances.", "Opt_1": "approve", "Opt_2": "detect", "Opt_3": "cease", "Opt_4": "interfere", "Answer": "interfere", "Opt_1_def": "to agree to", "Opt_2_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_3_def": "to stop", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent; to harm"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The more powerful computers will continue to ____ all aspects of life.", "Opt_1": "undergo", "Opt_2": "transform", "Opt_3": "inform", "Opt_4": "connect", "Answer": "transform", "Opt_1_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_3_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or put together"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "People are right to be suspicious of any diet that promises ____ success.", "Opt_1": "external", "Opt_2": "spontaneous", "Opt_3": "sole", "Opt_4": "instant", "Answer": "instant", "Opt_1_def": "outside", "Opt_2_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_3_def": "only", "Opt_4_def": "immediate"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Her ____ efforts throughout the school year are certain to yield excellent results in her final examinations.", "Opt_1": "consistent", "Opt_2": "reliable", "Opt_3": "effective", "Opt_4": "initial", "Answer": "consistent", "Opt_1_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_2_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n", "Opt_3_def": "good, working well", "Opt_4_def": "starting, first"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Please note that section 5 is the most important, and ____ it should constitute the majority of your journal entry.", "Opt_1": "roughly", "Opt_2": "accordingly", "Opt_3": "hence", "Opt_4": "indirectly", "Answer": "hence", "Opt_1_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_2_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_3_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_4_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "After 11 years at the helm of the Scientific Computing Division, Bill Buzbee recently announced his ____ to retire at the end of this year.", "Opt_1": "boundary", "Opt_2": "code", "Opt_3": "circumstances", "Opt_4": "intention", "Answer": "intention", "Opt_1_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_2_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_3_def": "situation", "Opt_4_def": "plan, aim"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "They argued that the law did not ____ to Cheney's task force, since all of its members were government officials, not outsiders.", "Opt_1": "arise", "Opt_2": "apply", "Opt_3": "demonstrate", "Opt_4": "prosper", "Answer": "apply", "Opt_1_def": "to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_3_def": "to show", "Opt_4_def": "to do well; to become rich"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Among male baboons, dominance ____ is independent of maternal ____, and changes markedly with age; males reach their highest ____ between 8 and 10 years of age.", "Opt_1": "code", "Opt_2": "property", "Opt_3": "route", "Opt_4": "rank", "Answer": "rank", "Opt_1_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_2_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_3_def": "the way to get to a place or a thing", "Opt_4_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We got some very ____ results in our science experiment. I think the thermometer was not working correctly.", "Opt_1": "accurate", "Opt_2": "related", "Opt_3": "automatic", "Opt_4": "abnormal", "Answer": "abnormal", "Opt_1_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_2_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_3_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_4_def": "not normal, unusual"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In this article, a novel way of teaching chemistry is presented that uses ____ music and chemical lyrics to educate.", "Opt_1": "efficient", "Opt_2": "slight", "Opt_3": "neutral", "Opt_4": "contemporary", "Answer": "contemporary", "Opt_1_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_2_def": "small", "Opt_3_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_4_def": "of this time, happening now"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "University staff will notice the new look and feel because information will be presented on Web pages ____ of on bulletin boards.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You are advised to undertake serious language study both before and during the course of the program but prior language study is not a ____ for selection.", "Opt_1": "series", "Opt_2": "impulse", "Opt_3": "criterion", "Opt_4": "instinct", "Answer": "criterion", "Opt_1_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_3_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_4_def": "natural feeling or reaction"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Your grades will continue to ____ unless you start working harder.", "Opt_1": "warn", "Opt_2": "displace", "Opt_3": "deteriorate", "Opt_4": "facilitate", "Answer": "deteriorate", "Opt_1_def": "to notify (of possible danger)", "Opt_2_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to make something easier"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In this section of the course, we cover less familiar territory, ____ the equations of relativistic acceleration.", "Opt_1": "namely", "Opt_2": "simply", "Opt_3": "nevertheless", "Opt_4": "thereby", "Answer": "namely", "Opt_1_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_2_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_3_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_4_def": "by doing this"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A half century ago the conflict over state regulation of railroads was the ____ issue in Alabama politics.", "Opt_1": "slight", "Opt_2": "invisible", "Opt_3": "chief", "Opt_4": "temporary", "Answer": "chief", "Opt_1_def": "small", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "for a short or limited time"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The drugs are used to enhance ____ artificially to the degree that they give athletes a competitive edge.", "Opt_1": "asset", "Opt_2": "trend", "Opt_3": "extract", "Opt_4": "performance", "Answer": "performance", "Opt_1_def": "advantage", "Opt_2_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_4_def": "action or achievement"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "To prevent this from happening, it is very helpful for patients to avoid talking unless ____ necessary for three days following surgery.", "Opt_1": "roughly", "Opt_2": "seldom", "Opt_3": "absolutely", "Opt_4": "naturally", "Answer": "absolutely", "Opt_1_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_2_def": "rare", "Opt_3_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_4_def": "of course, obviously"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The work involves some lifting and bending, and ____ requires travel away from the normal duty station.", "Opt_1": "largely", "Opt_2": "occasionally", "Opt_3": "nevertheless", "Opt_4": "conversely", "Answer": "occasionally", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "sometimes", "Opt_3_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_4_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Most leadership training programs leave out the key question, ____ how leaders actually affect their groups.", "Opt_1": "greatly", "Opt_2": "namely", "Opt_3": "hence", "Opt_4": "approximately", "Answer": "namely", "Opt_1_def": "very much", "Opt_2_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_3_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_4_def": "about; not exactly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government has succeeded in reducing unemployment ____ older people; conversely, young people are having ever more difficulty finding a job.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Perhaps the most elaborate example of an arthropod joint, ____ one of the most complex skeletal structures known, is the wing hinge of insects.", "Opt_1": "indeed", "Opt_2": "dramatically", "Opt_3": "gradually", "Opt_4": "generally", "Answer": "indeed", "Opt_1_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_2_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_3_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_4_def": "usually"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The (German) invention of the dynamo brought a ____ in electrical energy leading to the construction of power stations serving cities and towns.", "Opt_1": "episode", "Opt_2": "deal", "Opt_3": "substitute", "Opt_4": "revolution", "Answer": "revolution", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "agreement", "Opt_3_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_4_def": "a time of great change"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This validation will ____ him/her as a \"special student\" and will entitle him/her to the use of additional university facilities, such as the union building and the gym, and to free admissions for selected lectures.", "Opt_1": "submit", "Opt_2": "identify", "Opt_3": "invent", "Opt_4": "utilize", "Answer": "identify", "Opt_1_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_2_def": "to know or say who or what something is", "Opt_3_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_4_def": "to use"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Microsoft's new operating system will not be ____ until the beginning of September.", "Opt_1": "particular", "Opt_2": "initial", "Opt_3": "available", "Opt_4": "intrinsic", "Answer": "available", "Opt_1_def": "specific", "Opt_2_def": "starting, first", "Opt_3_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_4_def": "belonging to; inherent in"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The monks found it difficult to adapt to changes in society and in the economy, and they also found it difficult to adapt to challenges presented by the new learning made available through translations of ____ Greek texts by way of Arabic.", "Opt_1": "uniform", "Opt_2": "legitimate", "Opt_3": "superficial", "Opt_4": "ancient", "Answer": "ancient", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_2_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_3_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_4_def": "very old"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Many people buy ____ vitamin pills because they do not believe that they get enough vitamins from their regular food.", "Opt_1": "absent", "Opt_2": "supplementary", "Opt_3": "harsh", "Opt_4": "brief", "Answer": "supplementary", "Opt_1_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_2_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_3_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_4_def": "short"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There are so many careers that ____ Astronomy.", "Opt_1": "gather", "Opt_2": "explain", "Opt_3": "involve", "Opt_4": "inhibit", "Answer": "involve", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_2_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent or stop"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Thus, while we do not wish to speculate on future developments, we need to consider the ____ and potential effects of the decision.", "Opt_1": "actual", "Opt_2": "feasible", "Opt_3": "complete", "Opt_4": "proper", "Answer": "actual", "Opt_1_def": "real", "Opt_2_def": "possible", "Opt_3_def": "full or finished", "Opt_4_def": "correct, appropriate"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Not everyone is fortunate enough to have internet ____ at home.", "Opt_1": "access", "Opt_2": "precaution", "Opt_3": "format", "Opt_4": "phase", "Answer": "access", "Opt_1_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_2_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_3_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_4_def": "a (short) period of time; stage"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "He did not ____ to develop a particularly good balance in his own life until he was able to stop worrying about what others thought of him.", "Opt_1": "manage", "Opt_2": "reveal", "Opt_3": "require", "Opt_4": "dictate", "Answer": "manage", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_3_def": "to need", "Opt_4_def": "to tell someone what to do"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The equator is an ____ line that divides the earth into a northern and southern hemisphere.", "Opt_1": "smooth", "Opt_2": "actual", "Opt_3": "imaginary", "Opt_4": "spare", "Answer": "imaginary", "Opt_1_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_2_def": "real", "Opt_3_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_4_def": "not needed"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government needs to do more to ____ people without jobs to business that are looking for workers.", "Opt_1": "connect", "Opt_2": "degenerate", "Opt_3": "reform", "Opt_4": "react", "Answer": "connect", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_2_def": "to get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_4_def": "to respond"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "She is trying to ____ a new way to open tin cans.", "Opt_1": "dictate", "Opt_2": "contribute", "Opt_3": "devise", "Opt_4": "restore", "Answer": "devise", "Opt_1_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_2_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_3_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_4_def": "to put back, create again"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The current ____ of our anatomy information system has evolved from several previous systems.", "Opt_1": "version", "Opt_2": "drawback", "Opt_3": "passage", "Opt_4": "function", "Answer": "version", "Opt_1_def": "form", "Opt_2_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_3_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_4_def": "job or role"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Germany is no longer a ____ society. Between 15 - 20% of its population is non-German.", "Opt_1": "reasonable", "Opt_2": "homogeneous", "Opt_3": "mental", "Opt_4": "immediate", "Answer": "homogeneous", "Opt_1_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_3_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_4_def": "first (without delay)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The White House has been engaged in an ____ war, trying to conceal the motives and strategies of the real war on Iraq.", "Opt_1": "decade", "Opt_2": "duty", "Opt_3": "shortage", "Opt_4": "image", "Answer": "image", "Opt_1_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_3_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_4_def": "picture"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Please remember to ____ any rented vehicle before driving it and note any scratches or other damage to the vehicle on the rental form.", "Opt_1": "disrupt", "Opt_2": "preserve", "Opt_3": "inspect", "Opt_4": "announce", "Answer": "inspect", "Opt_1_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_2_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_3_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to state (often in an official way)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Computer scan technology can enhance the ____ of many sports injuries.", "Opt_1": "obstacle", "Opt_2": "custom", "Opt_3": "diagnosis", "Opt_4": "speed", "Answer": "diagnosis", "Opt_1_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_2_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_3_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_4_def": "how quickly something moves or changes"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Ours is the only generation that can prevent a ____ loss of biological diversity.", "Opt_1": "ultimate", "Opt_2": "massive", "Opt_3": "substantial", "Opt_4": "willing", "Answer": "massive", "Opt_1_def": "final or most important", "Opt_2_def": "very large", "Opt_3_def": "large", "Opt_4_def": "happy or prepared to do something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "From the end of the Great Depression to the mid-1970s economic growth was ____ and its benefits were widely spread throughout the society.", "Opt_1": "rapid", "Opt_2": "efficient", "Opt_3": "typical", "Opt_4": "neutral", "Answer": "rapid", "Opt_1_def": "quick", "Opt_2_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_3_def": "usual", "Opt_4_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is the duty of educators to ____ themselves carefully for each and every lesson.", "Opt_1": "examine", "Opt_2": "prepare", "Opt_3": "tend", "Opt_4": "deserve", "Answer": "prepare", "Opt_1_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_3_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to have the right to something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This report contains ____ problems, the most important of which is that it is not up to date.", "Opt_1": "principal", "Opt_2": "various", "Opt_3": "outstanding", "Opt_4": "numerous", "Answer": "various", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_3_def": "excellent", "Opt_4_def": "very many"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Almost everyone believes that terrorism should be fought, but there is little agreement about the ____ in which it should be done.", "Opt_1": "belief", "Opt_2": "extract", "Opt_3": "manner", "Opt_4": "skill", "Answer": "manner", "Opt_1_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_2_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_3_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "An ____ of English that many learners find difficult is verb grammar.", "Opt_1": "counsel", "Opt_2": "progress", "Opt_3": "friction", "Opt_4": "aspect", "Answer": "aspect", "Opt_1_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_2_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_3_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain."}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "One portion of the essay is good, but the rest is of ____ quality.", "Opt_1": "abnormal", "Opt_2": "discrete", "Opt_3": "poor", "Opt_4": "brief", "Answer": "poor", "Opt_1_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "separate", "Opt_3_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_4_def": "short"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government intends to ____ the information for itself. The public will not have access to it until the end of the decade.", "Opt_1": "risk", "Opt_2": "promote", "Opt_3": "reserve", "Opt_4": "accuse", "Answer": "reserve", "Opt_1_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_2_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to blame"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You may need to ____ to the terms and scope of the permission (i.e., duration, purpose, etc.).", "Opt_1": "occupy", "Opt_2": "refer", "Opt_3": "arrange", "Opt_4": "identify", "Answer": "refer", "Opt_1_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_2_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_3_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_4_def": "to know or say who or what something is"}]]